<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2008" id="01">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[August 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- August = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[08]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[01]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[American Queen Steamboat Company®]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[aqs]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Stay Close & Go Far]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[American Queen Steamboat Company®]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Rivers truly are the very heart of America, and 2021 is the perfect time explore them.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/article/advertorial-01-01.png" style="width: 300px; height: auto;">
			</figure>
			
			<p>Join <strong>American Queen Steamboat Company</strong>&reg; on a journey that will open the mind &ndash; and the heart &ndash; aboard America&rsquo;s most beautiful and most authentic paddlewheel riverboats. On these cruises, a collection of modern, elegant paddlewheelers introduce guests to the Mississippi, Ohio, Tennessee and Cumberland Rivers in America&rsquo;s heartland and the Columbia and Snake Rivers in the Pacific Northwest.</p>
			<p>Long before people made their mark on this continent, rivers shaped it. Carved paths from Northern forests through mountain gaps and deep cliff-lined gorges, winding thousands of miles to join the oceans. From these rivers, America first looked West. And it is here, on her great rivers, that America found her unique national rhythm. The mesmerizing beat of jazz...the pulsing cadence of commerce...the gentle tempo of the rivers&rsquo; own currents.</p>
			<p>Take time to explore American Queen Steamboat Company&rsquo;s 2021 Paddlewheel Collection and discover the many different options available. You&rsquo;ll find all the classic routes that make paddlewheeling America&rsquo;s favorite river pastime, as well as exciting new itineraries you&rsquo;ll want to explore.</p>
			<p>Guests might enjoy cruising the length of the mighty Mississippi River, where the story of an entire nation unfolds. Or encounter the magnificent beauty of the Pacific Northwest. Or experience the thrill of being at Churchill Downs on Derby Day. The options are endless.</p>
			
			<br>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/article/advertorial-01-02.jpg">
			</figure>
			<h4>An Authentic Collection of Paddlewheelers</h4>
			<p>There&rsquo;s nothing in the world quite like the feel of a real paddlewheeler. No matter which voyage, each of American Queen Steamboat Company&rsquo;s four beautiful paddlewheelers brings her own character to the journey.</p>
			<ul>
				<li><span style="font-style: italic;">American Queen</span>&reg; &ndash; Their flagship is the largest overnight passenger steamboat ever built. Welcoming 417 guests, her authentic design and style can never be duplicated. Her melodic steam calliope can be heard along the full length of the Mississippi, from Red Wing to New Orleans. She truly is the queen of the river.</li>
				<li><span style="font-style: italic;">American Duchess</span>&trade; &ndash; Smaller, more intimate and offering unprecedented views from her two-story loft suites, she is the only riverboat of her kind. She welcomes just 166 guests on each voyage. Enjoy her fashionable charm, authentic Murano glass and grand spaces as you explore the Mississippi, Ohio and Cumberland Rivers.</li>
				<li><span style="font-style: italic;">American Countess&trade; &ndash; </span>The newest gem in America's premier riverboat fleet's sleek contemporary styling welcomes 245 guests along the Tennessee, Ohio, Cumberland, Illinois and Mississippi rivers. With plenty of open space for gathering and sharing the fun, guests will love the great forward-facing windows and the portside bar with an 80-foot view.</li>
				<li><span style="font-style: italic;">American Empress&reg;</span> &ndash; Showcasing the art and culture of her Pacific Northwest origins, she will dazzle you with her art collection alone. Unique paintings, wildlife and Native American art and a collection of exclusive pieces are rivaled only by authentic Fabergé eggs. Travelers experience all U.S. climate zones on a seven-day Columbia and Snake river cruise.</li>
			</ul>
			
			<br>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/article/advertorial-01-03.jpg">
			</figure>
			<h4>So, what exactly is new in 2021?</h4>
			<p>American Queen Steamboat Company will be embarking on a new route up the Illinois. History is built by those standing on the shoulders of giants. On these cruises, explore the legacy of an American legend &ndash; President Abraham Lincoln &ndash; partly a product of this heartland full of patriots born of solid stock and bred to rely on steely reserve. The hospitality of these quaint Illinois river towns touches the spirit of all who visit.</p>
			<p>And they&rsquo;ve introduced The Queen&rsquo;s Collection&trade;. These thoughtfully planned journeys feature a diverse collection of specially crafted experiences. From culinary cruises to special events, like the Kentucky Derby, they invite you to find one that will excite your interests and join them on these unique voyages.</p>
			<p>Cruise fares for all vessels include a pre-voyage hotel night, masterful regional cuisine, world-class entertainment, comprehensive Hop-On Hop-Off shore excursions, onboard enrichment programs, select wine and beer with dinner, 24-hour room service, Wi-Fi service, and soft drinks and specialty coffees throughout the trip.</p>
			<p>Rivers truly are the very heart of America, and 2021 is the perfect time explore them. American Queen Steamboat Company looks forward to welcoming you on board &ndash; again, or for the very first time &ndash; to stay close and go far.</p>
			
			<br>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/article/advertorial-01-04.jpg">
			</figure>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/hero/advertorial-01.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Stay Close & Go Far]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[American Queen Steamboat Company®]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/article/advertorial-01.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Stay Close & Go Far]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[American Queen Steamboat Company®]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
	
	<article date="2008" id="02">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[August 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- August = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[08]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[02]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Transat]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[trh]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Transat's Traveller Care]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Transat]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Enhanced health measures and a new comprehensive practical guide for a simple and safe travel experience.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>As it prepared to gradually resume operations on July 23, 2020, Transat has been committed to providing a simple and safe travel experience at every step. To that end, it invites travellers to familiarize themselves with the health and safety measures of its&nbsp;<em>Traveller Care</em>&nbsp;program, which are regularly updated in compliance with recommendations issued by regulatory authorities. It has also assembled a new comprehensive practical guide full of tips to help travellers prepare for their trips and travel with peace of mind.</p>
			<p>&ldquo;We know that travelling in the age of COVID-19 raises all sorts of questions and concerns that can hinder the traveller,&rdquo; says Annick Gu&eacute;rard, Chief Operating Officer of Transat. &ldquo;Therefore, as part of our health and safety program, we are giving easy access to all the resources and information needed to simplify the planning of a trip, reinforcing our status as a leader in leisure travel.&rdquo;</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/article/advertorial-02-01.jpg">
			</figure>
			<h4>A practical guide to facilitate the travel experience</h4>
			<p>It can be difficult for travellers and travel agents to navigate all the changes and recommendations resulting from COVID-19. To help them prepare for trips and familiarize themselves with the new practices to adopt, Transat presents a guide as a practical tool.</p>
			<p>Through a series of tips and a recap of the health measures to follow, the guide answers the most common questions travellers might have, including what to check before departure, how to ensure that check-in and boarding go smoothly, what to do if they are denied boarding, how to limit contact, and what new procedures to respect at destination.</p>
			<p>The guide is available now on&nbsp;<a href="https://www.airtransat.com/en-CA/travel-information/traveller-care-practical-guide?_ga=2.119108425.115350342.1595344983-1678981736.1595344983" target="_blank"><strong>Transat&rsquo;s website</strong></a>.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/article/advertorial-02-02.jpg">
			</figure>
			<h4>Updates to the&nbsp;<em>Traveller Care</em>&nbsp;health and safety program</h4>
			<p>Transat assiduously follows the recommendations of regulatory authorities and adjusts its health measures accordingly to ensure the safety of its customers and employees. Travellers and travel agents are encouraged to regularly check&nbsp;<a href="https://www.airtransat.com/en-CA/travel-information/traveller-care?_ga=2.119108425.115350342.1595344983-1678981736.1595344983"><strong>the&nbsp;<em>Traveller Care</em>&nbsp;web page</strong></a>&nbsp;for the latest updates.</p>
			<p>Here is a reminder of the measures that will be put in place:</p>
			<ul>
				<li><strong>At the airport</strong>: Among the new measures implemented at the airport, passengers will be asked health-related questions, their temperature will be taken, and counters and self-service kiosks will be regularly disinfected.</li>
				<li><strong>On board</strong>: All necessary precautions will be taken to provide a safe inflight experience. Frequently touched cabin surfaces will be thoroughly cleaned with hospital-grade disinfectant before each flight, and the aircraft will be thoroughly cleaned with an electrostatic disinfectant sprayer every 24 hours. Passengers will receive a complimentary Traveller Care kit (including a face covering, gloves, hand sanitizer and disinfecting wipes). Passengers and crew will be required to wear face coverings throughout the flight. And the inflight service will be revised to reduce handling and contact.</li>
			</ul>
			<p>In addition, on board all aircraft, reliable HEPA (High Efficiency Particulate Air) filters will eliminate 99.995% of small particles, such as bacteria and viruses, refreshing cabin air every three minutes.</p>
			<ul>
				<li><strong>At destination</strong>: Reinforced preventive measures during transfers and excursions will be put in place for customers who have purchased a South or Europe package. In addition, Transat&rsquo;s hotel partners will be implementing rigorous health and safety protocols so that travellers can enjoy their vacations with complete peace of mind. To provide support at destination, Transat representatives will be available at all times, by phone or via the Air Transat app.&nbsp;</li>
			</ul>
			
			<br>
			<br>
			
			<h4>Traveller Care at a glance</h4>
			<p>Discover Transat&rsquo;s health and safety program summarized in this short video.</p>
			<br/>
			<div class="videoWrapper" style="padding-bottom: 45%;">
				<figure>
					<iframe width="560" height="315" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/tnkjrSgu9GU" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
				</figure>
			</div>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/hero/advertorial-02.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Transat's Traveller Care]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Transat]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/article/advertorial-02.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Transat's Traveller Care]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Transat]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>
