<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2008" id="01">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[August 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- August = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[08]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[01]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[American Queen Steamboat Company®]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[aqs]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Stay Close & Go Far]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[American Queen Steamboat Company®]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Rivers truly are the very heart of America, and 2021 is the perfect time explore them.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/article/advertorial-01-01.png" style="width: 200px; height: auto;">
			</figure>
			
			<br>
			
			<p>Join <strong>American Queen Steamboat Company</strong>&reg; on a journey that will open the mind &ndash; and the heart &ndash; aboard America&rsquo;s most beautiful and most authentic paddlewheel riverboats. On these cruises, a collection of modern, elegant paddlewheelers introduce guests to the Mississippi, Ohio, Tennessee and Cumberland Rivers in America&rsquo;s heartland and the Columbia and Snake Rivers in the Pacific Northwest.</p>
			<p>Long before people made their mark on this continent, rivers shaped it. Carved paths from Northern forests through mountain gaps and deep cliff-lined gorges, winding thousands of miles to join the oceans. From these rivers, America first looked West. And it is here, on her great rivers, that America found her unique national rhythm. The mesmerizing beat of jazz...the pulsing cadence of commerce...the gentle tempo of the rivers&rsquo; own currents.</p>
			<p>Take time to explore American Queen Steamboat Company&rsquo;s 2021 Paddlewheel Collection and discover the many different options available. You&rsquo;ll find all the classic routes that make paddlewheeling America&rsquo;s favorite river pastime, as well as exciting new itineraries you&rsquo;ll want to explore.</p>
			<p>Guests might enjoy cruising the length of the mighty Mississippi River, where the story of an entire nation unfolds. Or encounter the magnificent beauty of the Pacific Northwest. Or experience the thrill of being at Churchill Downs on Derby Day. The options are endless.</p>
			
			<br>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/article/advertorial-01-02.jpg">
			</figure>
			<h4>An Authentic Collection of Paddlewheelers</h4>
			<p>There&rsquo;s nothing in the world quite like the feel of a real paddlewheeler. No matter which voyage, each of American Queen Steamboat Company&rsquo;s four beautiful paddlewheelers brings her own character to the journey.</p>
			<ul>
				<li><span style="font-style: italic;">American Queen</span>&reg; &ndash; Their flagship is the largest overnight passenger steamboat ever built. Welcoming 417 guests, her authentic design and style can never be duplicated. Her melodic steam calliope can be heard along the full length of the Mississippi, from Red Wing to New Orleans. She truly is the queen of the river.</li>
				<li><span style="font-style: italic;">American Duchess</span>&trade; &ndash; Smaller, more intimate and offering unprecedented views from her two-story loft suites, she is the only riverboat of her kind. She welcomes just 166 guests on each voyage. Enjoy her fashionable charm, authentic Murano glass and grand spaces as you explore the Mississippi, Ohio and Cumberland Rivers.</li>
				<li><span style="font-style: italic;">American Countess&trade; &ndash; </span>The newest gem in America's premier riverboat fleet's sleek contemporary styling welcomes 245 guests along the Tennessee, Ohio, Cumberland, Illinois and Mississippi rivers. With plenty of open space for gathering and sharing the fun, guests will love the great forward-facing windows and the portside bar with an 80-foot view.</li>
				<li><span style="font-style: italic;">American Empress&reg;</span> &ndash; Showcasing the art and culture of her Pacific Northwest origins, she will dazzle you with her art collection alone. Unique paintings, wildlife and Native American art and a collection of exclusive pieces are rivaled only by authentic Fabergé eggs. Travelers experience all U.S. climate zones on a seven-day Columbia and Snake river cruise.</li>
			</ul>
			
			<br>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/article/advertorial-01-03.jpg">
			</figure>
			<h4>So, what exactly is new in 2021?</h4>
			<p>American Queen Steamboat Company will be embarking on a new route up the Illinois. History is built by those standing on the shoulders of giants. On these cruises, explore the legacy of an American legend &ndash; President Abraham Lincoln &ndash; partly a product of this heartland full of patriots born of solid stock and bred to rely on steely reserve. The hospitality of these quaint Illinois river towns touches the spirit of all who visit.</p>
			<p>And they&rsquo;ve introduced The Queen&rsquo;s Collection&trade;. These thoughtfully planned journeys feature a diverse collection of specially crafted experiences. From culinary cruises to special events, like the Kentucky Derby, they invite you to find one that will excite your interests and join them on these unique voyages.</p>
			<p>Cruise fares for all vessels include a pre-voyage hotel night, masterful regional cuisine, world-class entertainment, comprehensive Hop-On Hop-Off shore excursions, onboard enrichment programs, select wine and beer with dinner, 24-hour room service, Wi-Fi service, and soft drinks and specialty coffees throughout the trip.</p>
			<p>Rivers truly are the very heart of America, and 2021 is the perfect time explore them. American Queen Steamboat Company looks forward to welcoming you on board &ndash; again, or for the very first time &ndash; to stay close and go far.</p>
			
			<br>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/article/advertorial-01-04.jpg">
			</figure>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/hero/advertorial-01.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Stay Close & Go Far]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[American Queen Steamboat Company®]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/08/article/advertorial-01.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Stay Close & Go Far]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[American Queen Steamboat Company®]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>
