<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2011" id="01">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[November 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- November = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[11]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[01]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Princess® Cruises]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[pri]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Princess® MedallionClass Vacations™]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Princess® Cruises]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			The easiest way to cruise, exclusively on Princess®
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>It&rsquo;s been called the next wave of travel, but you&rsquo;ll call it the most relaxing vacation you&rsquo;ve ever had &mdash; Discover all the ways Princess&reg; MedallionClass&trade; gives you more time for &ldquo;me time.&rdquo;</p>
			<p>Exclusively on Princess, MedallionClass &trade; offers the fastest way to an easy, personalized and smooth-sailing vacation, all enabled by OceanMedallion&trade;, a free, quarter-size device, that is key to opening doors: to your stateroom, the ship and to an array of enhanced experiences.</p>
			<p>On board, the Medallion replaces the traditional cruise card and pairs with cutting edge IoT-driven innovation to significantly expand contactless options and personalization including:</p>
			<ul>
			<li>TrulyTouchless embarkation and disembarkation</li>
			<li>Keyless stateroom entry</li>
			<li>Contactless payment</li>
			<li>On-demand food, beverages and retail items delivered anywhere on board</li>
			<li>Planning, wagering and other entertainment features available via smart devices using the MedallionClass app</li>
			</ul>
			
			<br>
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-01-01.png" style="width: 250px; height: auto;">
			</figure>
			<br>
			
			<h4>CURBSIDE TO POOLSIDE IN A BREEZE</h4>
			<p>The MedallionClass experience begins soon after you book your cruise when you upload your essential travel information using the OceanReady&trade; App. And once you arrive to board at the Cruise terminal, you&rsquo;ll go from curbside to poolside in a breeze, and start your vacation sooner.&nbsp;</p>
			<h4>BEST WI-FI AT SEA</h4>
			<p>Even if you are on vacation to get away from it all, you can still stay connected. Princess MedallionNet&trade; delivers land-like connectivity so guests can post photos, text, video chat, and stream their favorite shows and sports and more.</p>
			<h4>DRINKS AND MORE DELIVERED ON DEMAND</h4>
			<p>Once you&rsquo;re on board, you&rsquo;ll discover a world of enhanced features, like drinks on demand. Using your smartphone, you can order your drinks, food, even sunscreen anytime, anywhere and have it delivered to right to your location &ndash; even to your stateroom!&nbsp;</p>
			<h4>FIND YOUR WAY &ndash; OR TRAVEL MATES</h4>
			<p>Don&rsquo;t waste your vacation wandering&mdash;you&rsquo;ll never get lost on board with our way-finding directions that guide you exactly where you want to go. And if you need to find a travel companion, you&rsquo;ll be able to locate them anywhere on board &ndash; all using your smart phone or touch screens around the ship!</p>
			<p>All Caribbean sailings will offer Princess MedallionClass in 2021 and this cruise innovation will also be available in Alaska, Europe, Canada &amp; New England, Mexico, the Panama Canal or along the California Coast in 2022. Book your MedallionClass vacation today.</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/hero/advertorial-01.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Princess® MedallionClass Vacations™]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Princess® Cruises]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-01.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Princess® MedallionClass Vacations™]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Princess® Cruises]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
	
	<article date="2011" id="02">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[November 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- November = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[11]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[02]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Club Med]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[cmd]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Let's Dream of the Beach]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Club Med]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Club Med is ready to welcome you back for a safe and unforgettable getaway.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p><strong>This is it!</strong> Two of Club Med&rsquo;s most emblematic resorts in Mexico and in the Caribbean have reopened their doors a few weeks ago: Club Med Canc&uacute;n Yucat&aacute;n and Club Med Punta Cana, Dominican Republic.</p>
			<p><strong>Club Med&rsquo;s amazing team is ready to welcome you for a stay as safe as unforgettable, when you will be ready to travel again.</strong></p>
			
			<br>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-02-01.jpg">
			</figure>
			<h4><strong>Club Med</strong><strong>Canc&uacute;n, Mexico &ndash; Now Open</strong></h4>
			<p>Rediscover a fully redesigned Club Med Canc&uacute;n Yucat&aacute;n, the ultimate all-inclusive family resort located at the tip of the iconic Riviera Maya. With three white sand beaches next to the world&rsquo;s second largest coral reef, this magnificent resort offers an extensive array of water and land sports, a variety of activities for families and kids of all ages, and direct access to ancient Mayan wonders. Enjoy an authentic Mexican dining experience, a new wine cellar, and a totally revamped resort center including a new main pool and lounge area. <strong>The perfect family getaway!</strong></p>
			<p>A world of the Chief of Village, Olivier Sanchez<em>: &ldquo;The Village is beautiful, the team did a fantastic job, we are ready and excited to welcome our guests. Sea, Sports, Spa, Sunset... are waiting for you!&rdquo;</em></p>
			
			<br>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-02-02.jpg">
			</figure>
			<h4><strong>Club Med Punta Cana, Dominican Republic - Now Open</strong></h4>
			<p>Located on the breathtaking island of Hispaniola, Club Med&rsquo;s all-inclusive Punta Cana resort welcomes couples and families alike for an unforgettable and safe vacation. Enjoy premium services and partake in unique activities alongside a stunning panoramic stretch of turquoise beach. Head to the new Zen Oasis, a sophisticated adults-exclusive hideaway, perfect for moments of relaxation during your stay. Looking for a little excitement? Experience CREACTIVE by Cirque du Soleil; a creative playground inspired by the world-renowned acrobatic shows. <strong>Leisure, fun, or sun, no matter what you&rsquo;re craving, this resort is sure to have it!</strong></p>
			<p>A world of the Chief of Village, Abdel Osmani: <em>&ldquo;The whole Team of Punta Cana is delighted to welcome you back in this amazing Village with new safety and hygiene measures! We hope to see you soon!&rdquo;</em>&nbsp;</p>
			
			<br>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-02-03.jpg">
			</figure>
			<h4><strong>Splash into Winter!</strong></h4>
			<p>Winter is coming&hellip; This year more than ever we need to escape from daily life and reconnect with our loved ones and ourselves. What better way to do so than on a white sand beach, laying down under the sunshine in a safe and secure environment where everything is taking care of?</p>
			<p>Make up for 2020 with a sunny all-inclusive getaway at Club Med this winter, and at the best rates!</p>
			<p>Air inclusive escapes from&nbsp;$1,599&nbsp;<sup>(1)</sup>&nbsp;per adult, per week.&nbsp;</p>
			<p>Plus, great perks:&nbsp;</p>
			<ul>
			<li>FREE Cancellation up to 15 days prior to departure <sup>(2)</sup></li>
			<li>FREE&nbsp;1st checked luggage&nbsp;<sup>(3)</sup></li>
			<li>No single supplement&nbsp;<sup>(4)</sup></li>
			<li>Kids under 4 stay FREE&nbsp;<sup>(5)</sup></li>
			</ul>
			<p>Book by&nbsp;January 4, 2021.</p>
			
			<br>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-02-04.jpg">
			</figure>
			<h4><strong>Book &amp; Travel with Peace of Mind at Club Med </strong></h4>
			<p><strong>Free Cancellations</strong><br>
			At Club Med, you can cancel your stay up to 15 days prior to departure and receive a full refund of your all-inclusive package. For departures through July 2, 2021.<sup>(2)</sup></p>
			<p><strong>Enhanced&nbsp;Hygiene &amp; Safety&nbsp;Measures</strong><br>
			Club Med have&nbsp;gathered a committee of specialized doctors and professors to bring you&nbsp;<strong><em>Safe Together</em></strong>, a series of resort-wide health &amp; safety measures.&nbsp;Among&nbsp;the&nbsp;changes you'll find&nbsp;<strong>elevated hygiene protocols</strong>&nbsp;and housekeeping standards,&nbsp;<strong>safe distancing</strong>&nbsp;guides, limited-contact check-in, reduced resort capacity, temperature checks, and much more.&nbsp;</p>
			<p><strong>Emergency Assistance Program</strong><br>
			Club Med&nbsp;new Emergency Assistance Program provides all guests traveling by <strong>April 30, 2021</strong> with coverage for emergency medical expenses during their stay, including those related to COVID-19.<sup>(6)</sup></p>
			
			<br>
			<br>
			<br>
			
			<p style="font-size: 75%;">(1)&nbsp;Sample price is per adult, based on a 7-night stay on double occupancy in a Superior category room at&nbsp;Club Med Punta Cana, Dominican Republic, for a departure on September 3, 2020 from Montreal or Toronto, flights and transfers to/from the resort included. Guests must book a 1-night stay to qualify. Valid for new individual bookings only for select travel dates with check-in on or after November 4, 2020 and check-out on or before May 1, 2021 and must be booked by January 4, 2021. Subject to capacity control and may increase at any time. &nbsp;</p>
			<p style="font-size: 75%;">(2) For new bookings made between May 18, 2020 and December 31, 2020 on any Club Med resort worldwide, you can modify or cancel for free and receive a full refund on your package (land and air portions) if your flights were booked with Air Canada, Air Transat or Westjet:</p>
			<p style="font-size: 75%;">Up to 15 days prior to departure for stays on and prior to July 2nd, 2021 (100% charge if 14 or less)</p>
			<p style="font-size: 75%;">Up to 61 days prior to departure for specific 2020 2021 Holiday weeks, including Christmas 2020, New Year&rsquo;s 2020, Spring Break 2021, and stays starting July 3rd, 2021 (25% charge if cancellation between 60 &amp; 31 days. 50% charge if cancellation between 30 &amp; 15 days. 100% if 14 or less).</p>
			<p style="font-size: 75%;">Up to 91 days prior to departure for 2021 Holiday weeks (including but not limited to Thanksgiving, Christmas 2021, New Year&rsquo;s 2021 and other weeks) (100% charge if 91 or less)</p>
			<p style="font-size: 75%;">Refund excludes membership fees and optional insurance. All refunds will go back on the same form of payment. If the cancelled booking was paid using a future travel credit, the refund will be issued as a credit for future travel to be used prior to the expiration date of the original future travel credit. If your flights were not booked with Air Canada, Air Transat or Westjet, the air portion will follow the airlines&rsquo; policy in effect.</p>
			<p style="font-size: 75%;">(3)&nbsp;Free checked luggage: One luggage per person is free, when flights are purchased with Club Med for Air Canada, Westjet and Air Transat to the Club Med destinations in Mexico, the Caribbean and Florida. Must respect the airline company&rsquo;s luggage policy. This offer is not valid for Westjet flights to Fort Lauderdale. &nbsp;</p>
			<p style="font-size: 75%;">(4)&nbsp;Kids under 4 Stay Free: Children aged under 4 years stay for free at our family destinations (exclusion for Holiday weeks: children 3 years stay at 50% of the adult price). Children aged 4-11 years stay at 50% off adult price at select family resorts. Children aged 12-15 years stay at 20% off adult price at select family resorts. For flights that are booked through Club Med, tickets for children must be paid for by the client. Children who are eligible to stay for free must be lodged in the same room as the adults who are paying for their stay, or in a connecting room. Blackout dates apply. Costs associated with Baby &amp; Petit Club Med are at full day rate during entire stay&nbsp;booked.&nbsp;</p>
			<p style="font-size: 75%;">(5)&nbsp;No Single Supplement: Offer available only at Club Med Cancun Yucatan, Mexico;&nbsp;Ixtapa&nbsp;Pacific, Mexico; Sandpiper Bay, Florida; Columbus Isle, Bahamas; Punta Cana, Dominican Republic,&nbsp;Mich&egrave;s&nbsp;Playa Esmeralda, Dominican Republic and&nbsp;Turkoise, Turks &amp; Caicos. Valid for new individual bookings only for select travel dates. Blackout dates apply. &nbsp;</p>
			<p style="font-size: 75%;">(6) Club Med Emergency Assistance Program provides all guests traveling before April 30th, 2021 with coverage for emergency medical expenses during their stay, including those related to COVID-19. This Assistance Agreement constitutes the general conditions of the contract concluded between EUROP ASSISTANCE, a business governed by the Insurance Code, and CLUB MEDITERRANEE, on behalf of its clients. It specifies the content of and the limits on the services to be provided by EUROP ASSISTANCE for CLUB MEDITERRANEE clients. The Assistance is provided by EUROP ASSISTANCE, and not by Club Med . Any enrollment in Club Med , or through the intermediary of a travel agent, makes the G.M eligible for EUROP ASSISTANCE services, which cover assistance for persons. Applicable only to Canadian members (G.Ms ) who are Canadian residents and have booked and paid for their trip in Canada. This coverage supercedes any previously existing coverage and is subject to change without notice. A complete description of coverage is available upon request with Club Med Sales Canada Inc., and also in the Basic Insurance document you will receive by electronic mail before departure if you made a reservation. Call your Travel Agent or our Club Med call center for more details.</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/hero/advertorial-02.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Let's Dream of the Beach]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Club Med]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-02.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Let's Dream of the Beach]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Club Med]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
	
	<article date="2011" id="03">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[November 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- November = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[11]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[03]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[ALG Vacations]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[alg]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Here Comes the Sun (and Sand)]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[ALG Vacations]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Dreaming of a vacation by the sea? We shine the light on safe harbors for beach lovers.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>There&rsquo;s something about the beach that gives you a certain peace of mind you can&rsquo;t find anywhere else. You can&rsquo;t imitate it, and you can&rsquo;t mistake it. Sadly, if 2020&rsquo;s been anything, it&rsquo;s short on the above &hellip; But that doesn&rsquo;t mean you can&rsquo;t turn it around.</p>
			<p>After months of research and innovation, we&rsquo;ve found new ways to do the things we love again safely &mdash; including travel. In fact, with hygiene protocols rolled out globally and airlines and hotels sparkling, in many ways, destinations and modes of travel have never <em>been</em> so clean! So, if you&rsquo;re in desperate need of an escape &mdash;relaxing vibes, tropical weather, <em>beaches &mdash; </em>know that, with the help of a travel advisor, you can seek refuge in retreats that are prioritizing sanitation.&nbsp;</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-03-01.jpg">
			</figure>
			
			<br>
			
			<h4>A Stunning Port of Safety</h4>
			<p>Set along the Pacific Coast and lining Banderas Bay, one of the largest and most beautiful bays in the world, Puerto Vallarta-Riviera Nayarit has long been considered one of Mexico&rsquo;s lesser-known gems. Now, however, this second city is basking in a well-deserved moment in the sun. Certified by the World Travel and Tourism Council as a &ldquo;Safe Travels&rdquo; destination&mdash;and maintaining a safely reduced occupancy level for hotels (less than 34% as of August, according to hospitality data company STR)&mdash; Puerto Vallarta-Riviera Nayarit has become our southern neighbor&rsquo;s leading destination.</p>
			<p>As people seek havens off the beaten path, it&rsquo;s really quite easy to see why.</p>
			<p>A 90% likelihood of sunny days alone gives Puerto Vallarta-Riviera Nayarit a winning hand &hellip; but it takes more than just clear skies to make a destination worth traveling for. Sure, laying around on a beach for days on end has its appeal. No one ever gets tired of that! But, especially now, it&rsquo;s only natural to want to seek even more nature<em>. </em>And that&rsquo;s where Puerto Vallarta-Riviera Nayarit <em>really</em> shines.</p>
			<p>Biodiversity is one of this region&rsquo;s greatest strengths, as you&rsquo;ll discover in its open pockets of wilderness. Immense mangroves in mysterious forests, rivers and lagoons home to tropical fish and wild dolphins, islands alight with bougainvillea, orchids, wild mango, papaya, orange, and lime trees&mdash;these features are all alive and well here.</p>
			<p>Of course, that&rsquo;s not to say that it&rsquo;s all a wild time in Puerto Vallarta-Riviera Nayarit. Golfers get outdoorsy their own way, on master-designed golf courses, and the more adventurous zipline, quad, hike, sail, kayak, and surf their way through the area. Dining in Puerto Vallarta-Riviera Nayarit is a treat as well, with the region considered one of the most important in Mexico for food.</p>
			<p>&hellip; But that&rsquo;s not the only heritage that&rsquo;s well-protected. The indigenous Huichol, Cora, Tepehuanos, and Mexicaneros have an open-door policy to their communities, making it easy to turn a romantic getaway or family beach vacation into a cultural journey.&nbsp;</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-03-02.jpg">
			</figure>
			
			<br>
			
			<h4>Rest Assured with RIU</h4>
			<p>New favorites like Puerto Vallarta-Riviera Nayarit aren&rsquo;t the only ones sunning in the spotlight, however. Tried-and-true all-inclusive brand RIU Hotels &amp; Resorts, known from coast to coast in Mexico for their cheerful service and nonstop entertainment, is branching out to even more friendly shores. Reopening properties in Dominican Republic, Jamaica, Aruba, and the Bahamas are putting those golden-pick destinations &mdash; and sands! &mdash; back on the map.</p>
			<p>A long-time go-to for beach lovers, these Caribbean islands are known all over the world for checking every box on a vacationer&rsquo;s list: soft sands and warm waters, views worth traveling for, and exceptional experiences.</p>
			<p>It&rsquo;s the latter where RIU really stands out, earning guest loyalty year after year. Musicians, actors, and enthusiastic staff fill days and nights with performances, activities, and games for every age. Sit in a restaurant&mdash;socially distanced, of course&mdash;by the sea and let the sounds of a violin somehow make every bite you take taste even sweeter. See the kids grin wide as they show off their arts and crafts &hellip; and even a few facts they learned. Finally find yourself free of all those kinks and knots after a morning at Renova Spa, where exchangeable massage bed covers gave you even more peace of mind.</p>
			<p>And that&rsquo;s the theme you&rsquo;ll notice over and over again, at any RIU hotel. New guidelines, developed with international consulting company Preverisk Group, have been introduced from Mexico to the Caribbean, to keep health and hygiene practices as high as their standards for guest satisfaction. It&rsquo;s why they&rsquo;ve earned Apple Vacations&rsquo; and Travel Impressions&rsquo; TripTrust&trade; badge of safety, reserved strictly for resorts reporting the highest levels of sanitation.</p>
			<p>So, in the storm that is this tumultuous time, when you&rsquo;re ready to set out again, ask your advisor about finding a safe harbor that suits <em>you</em>. Because if &ldquo;it seems like years&rdquo; since you&rsquo;ve seen your family smile, it&rsquo;s time to let the sun shine again.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-03-03.jpg">
			</figure>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/hero/advertorial-03.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Here Comes the Sun (and Sand)]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[ALG Vacations]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-03.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Here Comes the Sun (and Sand)]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[ALG Vacations]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
	
	<article date="2011" id="04">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[November 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- November = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[11]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[04]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Royal Caribbean International]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[rci]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Soak Up The Sun And The Adventure]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Royal Caribbean International]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Vacations are ready for a comeback. So get ready for some epic fun in the sun with a Royal Caribbean cruise to private destinations like no other &ndash; the experience-loaded Perfect Day at CocoCay or the beautiful getaway, Labadee. Between the best of land and sea, you&rsquo;ll be hard pressed to find a more memory-maxed getaway.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<h4>PERFECT DAY AT COCOCAY</h4>
			<p>Perfect Day at CocoCay isn&rsquo;t just a Royal Caribbean private island &mdash; it&rsquo;s a Bahamian paradise where mind-blowing thrills meet incredible ways to chill.&nbsp;</p>
			
			<br>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-04-01.jpg">
			</figure>
			<p><strong>THRILL WATERPARK &mdash; DAREDEVILS WANTED<br /></strong>This is a drench a minute thrill-a-thon for every adventurer. From giggle-worthy tides to shriek-inducing slides towering high into the clouds. Bounce, climb and swing your way through the obstacles in Adventure Pool. Get swept up by the biggest wave pool in the Caribbean. Or if you&rsquo;re up for a true rush, take on the tallest waterslide in North America &mdash; Daredevil&rsquo;s Peak.&nbsp;</p>
			<p><strong>ELEVATE YOUR BEACH DAY<br /></strong>At the exclusive Coco Beach Club, drift along the finest line between poolside and seaside, in an oceanfront infinity pool. Don&rsquo;t lift a finger to refuel, with complimentary concierge service in a private cabana. And for the ultimate beach day upgrade, indulge in a Floating Cabana where you can spread out across plenty of comfortable lounge seating, unwind in your overwater hammock and splash into the sea on your own slide.</p>
			<p><strong>PLAY IT COOL</strong><br /> Take the ultimate dip &mdash; in the Caribbean&rsquo;s largest freshwater pool. Make your way through the different coves of Oasis Lagoon, each with a vibe all its own. Splash right in at the kid-friendly sloping entry. Take your first sip of a cold Coco Loco at the swim-up bar. Or treat yourself to total relaxation in the privacy of your own cabana, complete with attendant service.</p>
			<p><strong>IT&rsquo;S ALL SUN AND GAMES</strong><br /> Get ready to fuel your competitive fire, because this is the best place to amp up and wind down. Volleyball, beachside basketball &mdash; it&rsquo;s all here. And once you&rsquo;ve worked up an appetite, grab a bite at the Snack Shack or wade out to the floating bar and cool off with a drink. Or kick back in your own beachfront cabana, perfect for lounging in the shade.</p>
			<p><strong>YOUR RECHARGING STATION</strong><br /> Chill Island offers the beach day you&rsquo;ve been dreaming about &mdash; crystal clear tropical waters and powdery sands. Kicking back with your whole crew in a private cabana. And just steps away, you can fill up your plate with tasty BBQ right on the beach at Chill Grill. Once you&rsquo;re feeling recharged, check out the island sights from a jet ski or on a guided snorkel tour.</p>
			<p><strong>LABADEE, HAITI</strong><br /> Situated on the northern shore of Haiti, there&rsquo;s nowhere quite like the private destination Labadee &mdash; where you can chase an adrenaline rush on an alpine coaster one minute and do some sun soaking the next. All right in the middle of rolling jungles and sparkling beaches. Cruise to Labadee and trek to the mountaintop to catch serious air on the world's longest zip line over water&mdash; the Dragon's Breath Flight Line&mdash; or the mountainside rollercoaster. Climb the only icebergs in the Caribbean at Arawak Aqua Park. If you just want to kick back and relax, grab our signature drink&mdash; the Labadoozie&mdash; and your own beach bungalow overlooking Nellie&rsquo;s Beach.&nbsp;</p>
			
			<br>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-04-02.jpg">
			</figure>
			<h4>Navigator Goes Next Level</h4>
			<p>The adventure starts before you even reach the island onboard an incredible ship with no shortage of ways to keep your vacation sunny side up &mdash; the Amplified <em>Navigator of the Seas</em>.</p>
			<p><strong>POOL DECKS<br /></strong>H2OH YES WE DID<br /> Onboard, the pool is overflowing with ways to spend your day in the sun, with tons of space to lounge, swim, and keep connected to the water. A signature bar, The Lime and Coconut, introduces a Caribbean cool vibe across three decks overlooking the poolside action. And with two casual spots to grab burgers and tacos nearby, you&rsquo;ll never have to wander far from your chair, hammock or shady casita.</p>
			<p><strong>SPORTS DECK<br /></strong>PUT ON YOUR GAME FACE<br /> We&rsquo;ll bring the balls &mdash; you bring your A game. Whether it&rsquo;s a pick-up game or one-or-one, go all in for basketball and volleyball action at sea, but with an awesome, energizing ocean view.</p>
			<p><strong>SOLARIUM</strong><br /> SUN AND SERENITY<br /> Check your watch &mdash; it&rsquo;s me time. Discover the Solarium, a relaxing indoor-outdoor retreat just for our adult guests. Perfectly positioned at the front of every Royal Caribbean ship, the crystal canopy area presents fantastic views and stays warm while you enjoy swimming pools, whirlpools and lounge areas.</p>
			
			<br>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-04-03.jpg">
			</figure>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/hero/advertorial-04.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Soak Up The Sun And The Adventure]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Royal Caribbean International]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-04.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Soak Up The Sun And The Adventure]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Royal Caribbean International]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>
