<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2011" id="01">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[November 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- November = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[11]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[01]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Princess® Cruises]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[pri]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Princess® MedallionClass Vacations™]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Princess® Cruises]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			The easiest way to cruise, exclusively on Princess®
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>It&rsquo;s been called the next wave of travel, but you&rsquo;ll call it the most relaxing vacation you&rsquo;ve ever had &mdash; Discover all the ways Princess&reg; MedallionClass&trade; gives you more time for &ldquo;me time.&rdquo;</p>
			<p>Exclusively on Princess, MedallionClass &trade; offers the fastest way to an easy, personalized and smooth-sailing vacation, all enabled by OceanMedallion&trade;, a free, quarter-size device, that is key to opening doors: to your stateroom, the ship and to an array of enhanced experiences.</p>
			<p>On board, the Medallion replaces the traditional cruise card and pairs with IoT-driven innovation to significantly expand contactless options and personalization including:</p>
			<ul>
			<li>TrulyTouchless embarkation and disembarkation</li>
			<li>Keyless stateroom entry</li>
			<li>Contactless payment</li>
			<li>On-demand food, beverages and retail items delivered anywhere on board</li>
			<li>Planning, wagering and other entertainment features available via smart devices using the MedallionClass app</li>
			</ul>
			
			<br>
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-01-01.png" style="width: 250px; height: auto;">
			</figure>
			<br>
			
			<h4>CURBSIDE TO POOLSIDE IN A BREEZE</h4>
			<p>The MedallionClass experience begins soon after you book your cruise when you upload your essential travel information using the OceanReady&trade; App. And once you arrive to board at the Cruise terminal, you&rsquo;ll go from curbside to poolside in a breeze, and start your vacation sooner.&nbsp;</p>
			<h4>BEST WI-FI AT SEA</h4>
			<p>Even if you are on vacation to get away from it all, you can still stay connected. Princess MedallionNet&trade; delivers land-like connectivity so guests can post photos, text, video chat, and stream their favorite shows and sports and more.</p>
			<h4>DRINKS DELIVERED ON DEMAND</h4>
			<p>Once you&rsquo;re on board, you&rsquo;ll discover a world of enhanced features, like drinks on demand. Using your smartphone, you can order your drinks anytime, anywhere and have them delivered to right to your location &ndash; even to your stateroom!&nbsp;</p>
			<h4>FIND YOUR WAY &ndash; OR TRAVEL MATES</h4>
			<p>Don&rsquo;t waste your vacation wandering&mdash;you&rsquo;ll never get lost on board with our way-finding directions that guide you exactly where you want to go. And if you need to find a travel companion, you&rsquo;ll be able to locate them anywhere on board &ndash; all using your smart phone or touch screens around the ship!</p>
			<p>All Caribbean sailings will offer Princess MedallionClass in 2021 and this cruise innovation will also be available in Alaska, Europe, Canada &amp; New England, Mexico, the Panama Canal or along the California Coast in 2022. Book your MedallionClass vacation today.</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/hero/advertorial-01.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Princess® MedallionClass Vacations™]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Princess® Cruises]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/advertorial-01.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Princess® MedallionClass Vacations™]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Princess® Cruises]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>
