<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2011">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[spotlight]]></dir_name> <!-- spotlight, style, insider -->
		<pub_date><![CDATA[November 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- November = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[11]]></dir_month>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Fairmont Mayakoba]]></author>
		<translator><![CDATA[]]></translator>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Riviera Maya - A Destination of Healing Experiences]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[
			Gain energy, heal and find balance through the wonders of mother nature.
		]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			As locals, we see Riviera Maya as a spiritual destination where you can energize, relieve your daily stress, and reconnect with your loved ones. During times of uncertainty, when unexpected events impact our lives, there are various ways in which we reconnect with the wonders of mother nature to gain energy, heal and find balance.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p></p>

			<!-- Full width image tile -->
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/spotlight-01.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Temazcal</h4>
					<p>Temazcal, meaning &ldquo;house of hot stones,&rdquo; is a group ceremony where participants enter a sweat lodge similar to an igloo-shaped hut where they experience high temperatures through hot stones and water to release tensions and toxins, and to purify their souls.&nbsp;It also clears skin and aids blood flow.</p>
					<p>According to the scientific journal Age and Ageing, the Temazcal practice can also help decrease the risk of dementia and Alzheimer&rsquo;s disease.</p>
					<p><strong>Tip:&nbsp;</strong>Forget about your makeup because the steam will take it all off. Once you complete the ceremony, you will feel your skin and your body differently as the ceremony includes aromatherapy with healing plants allowing your mind to reach optimal clarity.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/spotlight-02.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Cenotes (Sinkholes)</h4>
					<p>&ldquo;Cenote&rdquo; is derived from the Yucatec Mayan word &ldquo;dz&rsquo;onot,&rdquo; which is used to indicate where water is accessible.</p>
					<p>There are over 6,000 cenotes in the Yucatan peninsula, and most of us locals, as well as tourists, go swimming in them because they are rich in nutrients with an excellent source of minerals, vitamins, and protein that nourish the body. When traveling to Riviera Maya, we suggest visiting the Cenote Ik Kil, in Chichen Itza, not far from the ruins, Cenote Dos Ojos in Tulum, and the Grand Cenote.</p>
					<p><strong>Tip:</strong>&nbsp;If you are getting married in Riviera Maya, visit a cenote during a full moon and ask to receive a blessing of cenote water to pray for thankfulness and harmony in your marriage.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/spotlight-03.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Chichen Itza</h4>
					<p>Chichen Itza is not just another archeological place; it is a wonder of the world. The Pyramid of Kukulkan, the 80-foot stone, is set where the sun creates shadows down the steps of the pyramid resembling a snake descending. This event drags big crowds during the March and September equinox.</p>
					<p>For those who have traveled the world connecting to sacred spiritual places, Chichen Itza is a magical place where many ask for humanity and for individuals who struggle in life.</p>
					<p><strong>Tip:</strong>&nbsp;We suggest visiting Chichen Itza during the equinox as some people say the sacred energy expands and contracts then. And, they claim that is when you can manifest incredible healing or well-being for others.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<div class="videoWrapper" style="padding-bottom: 45%;">
					<figure>
						<iframe width="853" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/ryIjMCiNYgE?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe>
					</figure>
				</div>
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Mayakoba</h4>
					<p>When visiting the Riviera Maya, make sure to visit Mayakoba. Enjoy family dinners at our El Puerto overlooking the waterways. Enjoy yacht charters and catamaran tours. Go snorkeling and kayaking in the Caribbean Sea. Shop in downtown Playa del Carmen for that perfect souvenir. A vacation in Mayakoba comes naturally!</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Top Things to Do on Vacation in Mayakoba</h4>
					<p>Whether you want to hang at the beach, play championship fairways, or dive in the colorful coral reef, a vacation in Mayakoba is a magical experience. Create your own family traditions and feel the Mayan spirit rejuvenate your soul.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Water Sports in the Caribbean Sea</h4>
					<p>Play in the clear turquoise waters of the Caribbean Sea with complimentary stand-up paddleboards and kayaks. Enjoy jet skiing, reef snorkeling, sailing, windsurfing, boogie boarding and kitesurfing, or go on a guided catamaran tour. Swim with green turtles and dolphins, dive in cenotes, and spot corals, rays, and giant sponges for miles along the Riviera Maya coast.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Private Yacht Charters</h4>
					<p>Cruise the Caribbean Sea on a private yacht charter. Enjoy the ultimate adventure with family and friends on Mayakoba’s luxurious 55’ VanDutch Yacht. Sail into the sea and enjoy water activities, snorkeling stops, food and drink experiences, and amazing Riviera Maya scenery. Fairmont Mayakoba offers three yacht packages and custom excursions.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>
			
			<br>
			
			<p>For more information about Fairmont Mayakoba activities&nbsp;<a href="https://www.fairmont-mayakoba.com/play/seasonal-activities/" target="_blank">click here</a>.</p>
			
			<br>
			<hr>
			<br>
			
			<h4>About Fairmont</h4>
			<p>Fairmont Hotels &amp; Resorts is where occasions are celebrated and history is made. Landmark hotels with unrivalled presence, authentic experiences and unforgettable moments have attracted visitors to Fairmont and its destinations since 1907. The Plaza in New York City, The Savoy in London, Fairmont San Francisco, Fairmont Banff Springs and Fairmont Peace Hotel in Shanghai are but a few of these iconic luxury hotels, forever linked to the special places where they reside. Famous for its engaging service, grand public spaces, locally inspired cuisine and celebrated bars and lounges, Fairmont promises a special brand of thoughtful luxury that will be remembered long after any visit. With a worldwide portfolio of more than 80 hotels, Fairmont also takes great pride in its deep community roots and leadership in sustainability. Fairmont is part of Accor, a world leading hospitality group consisting of more than 5,000 properties and 10,000 food and beverage venues throughout 110 countries.</p>
			<p><a href="https://www.fairmont.com/">fairmont.com</a> | <a href="https://all.accor.com/">all.accor.com</a> | <a href="https://all.accor.com">group.accor.com</a></p>
			
			<br>
			
			<h4>About Accor</h4>
			<p><a href="https://group.accor.com/en">Accor</a> is a world leading hospitality group consisting of more than 5,000 properties and 10,000 food and beverage venues throughout 110 countries. The group has one of the industry&rsquo;s most diverse and fully-integrated hospitality ecosystems encompassing luxury and premium brands, midscale and economy offerings, unique lifestyle concepts, entertainment and nightlife venues, restaurants and bars, branded private residences, shared accommodation properties, concierge services, co-working spaces and more. Accor also boasts an unrivalled portfolio of distinctive brands and approximately 300,000 team members worldwide. Over 65 million members benefit from the company&rsquo;s comprehensive loyalty program <a href="https://all.accor.com/">ALL - Accor Live Limitless</a> - a daily lifestyle companion&nbsp;that provides access to a wide variety of rewards, services and experiences. Through its Planet 21 &ndash; Acting Here, Accor Solidarity, RiiSE and ALL Heartist Fund initiatives, the group is focused on driving positive action through business ethics,&nbsp;responsible tourism, environmental sustainability, community engagement, diversity and inclusivity. Founded in 1967, Accor SA is headquartered in France and publicly listed on the Euronext Paris Stock Exchange (ISIN code: FR0000120404) and on the OTC Market (Ticker: ACRFY) in the United States. For more information visit&nbsp;<a href="https://group.accor.com/en">group.accor.com</a>&nbsp;or follow Accor on&nbsp;<a href="https://twitter.com/Accor">Twitter</a>, <a href="https://www.facebook.com/Accor/">Facebook</a>, <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/accor/">LinkedIn</a> and <a href="https://www.instagram.com/accor">Instagram</a>.</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/hero/spotlight.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Riviera Maya - A Destination of Healing Experiences]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[sectionTitle]]></hero_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/article/spotlight.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Riviera Maya - A Destination of Healing Experiences]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[sectionTitle]]></article_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<email_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/11/email/spotlight.jpg</email_src>
		
		<tile_color>C8232C</tile_color> <!--Spotlight:C8232C, Insider:FA6900, Travel Style:00B9F2 -->
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="north-america"><![CDATA[north-america]]></tag>
			<tag slug="escorted-tours"><![CDATA[escorted-tours]]></tag>
			<tag slug="luxury-hotels-resorts"><![CDATA[luxury-hotels-resorts]]></tag>
			<tag slug="adventure"><![CDATA[adventure]]></tag>
			<tag slug="beach-sun"><![CDATA[beach-sun]]></tag>
			<tag slug="culture-history"><![CDATA[culture-history]]></tag>
			<tag slug="faithreligious"><![CDATA[faithreligious]]></tag>
			<tag slug="family-vacations"><![CDATA[family-vacations]]></tag>
			<tag slug="sports-outdoors"><![CDATA[sports-outdoors]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>
