<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="1912">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[style]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[December 2019]]></pub_date>
		<dir_year><![CDATA[19]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[12]]></dir_month>
​
		<author><![CDATA[Lucas Aykroyd]]></author>
		<translator><![CDATA[]]></translator>
​
		<title><![CDATA[Hawaii by Bike: Where to Find the Best Rides]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[
			From volcanic mountain slopes to twisty single tracks, there&rsquo;s no shortage of routes in Hawaii.
		]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Biking &ndash; a growing sport in Hawaii &ndash; is compelling, refreshing, and exciting. While island-hopping, you&rsquo;ll discover a rich variety of biking terrain, from volcanic mountain slopes to twisty single tracks. Whether you prefer riding mountain bikes, city bikes, or hybrid bikes, there&rsquo;s no shortage of routes. With fresh air, lush greenery, and stunning views of the Pacific Ocean, bike trips in Hawaii make for an unforgettable workout. For both competitive cyclists and casual riders, it&rsquo;s worth booking a trip with a reputable travel agency and coming to Hawaii to find the best rides.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<h4>Haleakala, Maui</h4>

			<p>Book a mountain bike tour with Bike Maui and ride 23 miles down the iconic Haleakala volcano after watching a magnificent sunrise. This outing starts off early, as you check in between 3:00 am and 4:00 am. You&rsquo;ll first head up in a vehicle driven by a guide and check out the volcanic crater, learning about Maui nature and geology and admiring the heavenly rays of purple and orange to the east. The total elevation change is 6,500 feet as you bike back to sea level, and it&rsquo;s a comfortable pace, as the average grade of the route is just five per cent. In all, it takes about eight hours.</p>

			<h4>Old Mamaloa Highway, the Big Island</h4>

			<p>Ranches teeming with cattle and cowboys give Waimea its character, just south of the Kohala Forest Reserve in the northern part of the Big Island. Bike east on the Old Mamaloa Highway, riding through the historic, 1847-founded Parker Ranch and old sugar plantation lands, and checking out the Mauna Kea volcano. Stop at the Tex Drive-In to refuel with a hearty grilled ahi burger. Another 20 miles will bring you to the magnificent Waipio Valley Lookout, overlooking where the legendary Hawaiian king Kamehameha I lived as a child.</p>

			<h4>Ke Ala Hele Makalae Trail, Kauai</h4>

			<p>If you have no desire to climb Mont Ventoux as a Tour de France competitor but love relaxing, scenic coastal bike rides, the Ke Ala Hele Makalae Trail in Kaui is for you. Extending more than seven miles, the multi-use, paved trail follows Kauai&rsquo;s eastern shores, known as the &ldquo;Coconut Coast.&rdquo; Check out interpretive signs along the route, which highlight local nature, archeology, and history. Or stop for a swim at Lydgate Park, which offers two enclosed lagoons and a picnic area. Bikes can be rented at Kauai Cycle.</p>

			<h4>Peacock Flats, Oahu</h4>

			<p>Are you an avid mountain biker who&rsquo;s looking for some challenging, technical single tracks? Then it&rsquo;s time to bike Peacock Flats. Nestled in the northwest corner of Oahu in the Kuaokala Forest Reserve, the route includes a thigh-burning 1,500-foot climb that kicks off at the Mokuleia Access Road. Tight switchbacks on the cliffside Kealia Trail command your attention even when there are views of huge surfing waves and Dillingham Air Field to be enjoyed.</p>

			<h4>Honolulu Century Ride, Oahu</h4>

			<p>Biking in Hawaii is a wonderful solo escape, but it can be even more enjoyable when you do it in a group. Check out panoramas of Kapiolani Park and Diamond Head on the coastal Honolulu Century Ride. Hawaii&rsquo;s largest annual bike ride, with more than 2,000 participants, will celebrate its 40th anniversary in 2021. It&rsquo;s a fun event, and you can choose to bike anywhere from five to 100 miles.</p>
		]]></body>
​
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/12/hero/style.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Hawaii by Bike: Where to Find the Best Rides]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Travel Style]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/12/article/style.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Hawaii by Bike: Where to Find the Best Rides]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Travel Style]]></article_credit>
		<email_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/12/email/style.jpg</email_src>
​
		<tile_color>00B9F2</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
​
		<tags>
			<tag slug="australia-south-pacific"><![CDATA[australia-south-pacific]]></tag>
			<tag slug="hawaii"><![CDATA[hawaii]]></tag>
			<tag slug="bicycle"><![CDATA[bicycle]]></tag>
			<tag slug="independent-travel"><![CDATA[independent-travel]]></tag>
			<tag slug="adventure"><![CDATA[adventure]]></tag>
			<tag slug="sports-outdoors"><![CDATA[sports-outdoors]]></tag>
			<tag slug="beach-sun"><![CDATA[beach-sun]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>