<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2007">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[insider]]></dir_name> <!-- spotlight, style, insider -->
		<pub_date><![CDATA[July 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- July = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[07]]></dir_month>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Delta Vacations]]></author>
		<translator><![CDATA[]]></translator>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Getting Back Out There with Delta Vacations]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[
			It’s time to get back out there, and Delta Vacations is here to make your vacation planning seamless.
		]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Whether exploring national parks or soaking in the summer sun on a gorgeous beach, the benefits of booking with Delta Vacations are endless. We caught up with Tammy Heitsman, National Account Manager at Delta Vacations, to learn more about what Delta Vacations offers and what steps they’re taking to make travelers feel safe during this time.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p class="question"><strong>Q:</strong> What are the benefits of booking with Delta Vacations?</p>
			<p>There are so many benefits to booking with Delta Vacations, but the one that stands out is that we&rsquo;re the official vacation provider of Delta Air Lines. SkyMiles&reg; members will receive up to 7,500 bonus SkyMiles on top of the earned miles flown as well as full medallion-qualifying benefits with every vacation package. Travelers can fly on Delta Air Lines as well as Delta&rsquo;s air partners including Air France, KLM, Virgin Atlantic, Virgin Australia, Aeromexico, Korean Air, and more.</p>
			<p>Delta Vacations offers vacation packages to over 300 destinations worldwide with stays at more than 5,000 hotels and resorts, boutique properties, condominiums, vacation homes, and serviced apartments to accommodate any budget. Rental cars, transfers, and hundreds of exciting activities, tours and excursions can also be added to vacation packages.</p>
			
			<p class="question"><strong>Q:</strong> What type of vacation packages does Delta Vacations offer?</p>
			<p>Delta Vacations offers air/land, land only, and fly/drive vacation packages. Special Getaway packages are also available including:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Luxury Vacations</li>
				<li>Destination Weddings</li>
				<li>Honeymoons</li>
				<li>All-Inclusive Vacations</li>
				<li>Flexible Getaways (10+ travelers)</li>
				<li>Traditional Groups (20+ travelers)</li>
				<li>Walt Disney World&reg; Resort Vacations</li>
				<li>Ski Vacations</li>
				<li>Dive Vacations</li>
			</ul>
			
			<p class="question"><strong>Q:</strong> Domestic travel is becoming quite popular this year. Does Delta Vacations offer vacations throughout North America?</p>
			<p>Yes! Delta Vacations is well prepared to welcome you to hundreds of destinations, properties and activities throughout the U.S., Canada, Mexico and the Caribbean. We offer 141 unique destinations across 45 states in the U.S., 17 across seven provinces in Canada, 18 throughout Mexico, and 32 throughout the Caribbean.</p>
			<p>In the U.S., we&rsquo;re adding properties in neighboring towns of several national parks including:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Kalispell, MT &ndash; Glacier National Park</li>
				<li>Bozeman, MT &amp; Cody, WY &ndash; Yellowstone/Grand Teton National Park</li>
				<li>Rapid City, SD &ndash; Black Hills/Mt. Rushmore</li>
				<li>Denver, CO &ndash; Rocky Mountain National Park</li>
				<li>Palm Springs, CA &ndash; Joshua Tree National Park</li>
				<li>Tucson, AZ &ndash; Saguaro National Park</li>
				<li>Knoxville, TN &ndash; Great Smoky Mountains National Park</li>
				<li>Big Island, HI &ndash; Volcanos National Park</li>
				<li>Phoenix, Scottsdale and Sedona, AZ &ndash; Grand Canyon</li>
			</ul>
			
			<p class="question"><strong>Q:</strong> What are some of the most popular beach destinations offered by Delta Vacations?</p>
			<p>Delta Vacations&rsquo; most popular beach destinations include beaches throughout the Caribbean, Mexico, Central America, and the U.S. Some of our top destinations are:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Cancun/Riviera Maya, Mexico</li>
				<li>Montego Bay, Jamaica</li>
				<li>Punta Cana, Dominican Republic</li>
				<li>Maui, Hawaii</li>
				<li>Honolulu, Hawaii</li>
				<li>Nassau, Bahamas</li>
				<li>Aruba</li>
				<li>Puerto Vallarta, Mexico</li>
				<li>Liberia, Costa Rica</li>
				<li>Turks and Caicos</li>
			</ul>
			
			<p class="question"><strong>Q:</strong> Does Delta Air Lines have a new standard of clean so travelers feel comfortable and safe while flying?</p>
			<p>Delta is transforming expectations for cleanliness across airports and on aircraft to deliver a new standard of clean for customers:&nbsp;<strong>Delta Care Standard.</strong></p>
			<p>Aircraft will be fogged before every flight in Delta&rsquo;s network.&nbsp;The disinfectant used in fogging is immediately safe to breathe and is&nbsp;similar to&nbsp;what hospitals and restaurants use to sanitize.&nbsp;Before every flight, aircraft will be cleaned using the same extensive checklist used during overnight cleanings. This industry-leading work disinfects high-touch areas&nbsp;customers care most about being clean, like&nbsp;tray tables, entertainment screens, seat backs, arm rests, and seat-back pockets.&nbsp;Spot checks will take place before each flight by a Customer Service Agent and a Flight Leader to ensure the aircraft is up to the Delta Clean standard. They can resolve any issues immediately and can request a cleaning crew to return to the aircraft for additional cleaning. Non-essential items, including&nbsp;Sky magazine, will be removed from seat-back pockets until&nbsp;further&nbsp;notice. Minimized&nbsp;touchpoints between customers&nbsp;and employees&nbsp;have been implemented, including temporarily moving&nbsp;to&nbsp;only essential&nbsp;food and beverage service&nbsp;onboard all U.S. domestic and short-haul international flights,&nbsp;and at our&nbsp;Sky Clubs. Customers will also be offered hand sanitizer at various touchpoints, and surfaces will be disinfected across the airport experience.&nbsp;</p>
			<p>Through September&nbsp;30, Delta will ensure more space for customers on all aircraft by capping seating at 50% in First Class; 60% in Main Cabin, Delta Comfort+, and Delta Premium Select; and 75% in Delta One to reduce the total number of customers on board. Through September&nbsp;30, all middle seats will be unavailable / not assignable when selecting seats via the Fly Delta app or online. We&rsquo;ll also continue to block the selection of some aisle seats in aircraft with 2x2 seating configurations.</p>
			
			<p class="question"><strong>Q:</strong> What travel protection is offered to travelers when booking a Delta Vacations package?</p>
			<p>It&rsquo;s important to protect yourself and your vacation investments. Delta Vacations offers two Travel Protection Plans to protect your travel investment from unforeseen circumstances.</p>
			<p>Our Travel Protection Plans allow Pre-Departure cancelation for any reason. Post-Departure Coverage provides Medical and Emergency assistance, trip interruption, trip delay, baggage delay and loss or damage to baggage or personal effects. Your Ensemble Travel Advisor can provide complete details of each plan.</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/07/hero/insider.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Getting Back Out There with Delta Vacations]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[On Location]]></hero_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/07/article/insider.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Getting Back Out There with Delta Vacations]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[On Location]]></article_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<email_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/07/email/insider.jpg</email_src>
		
		<tile_color>FA6900</tile_color> <!--Spotlight:C8232C, Insider:FA6900, Travel Style:00B9F2 -->
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="caribbean"><![CDATA[caribbean]]></tag>
			<tag slug="north-america"><![CDATA[north-america]]></tag>
			<tag slug="all-inclusive"><![CDATA[all-inclusive]]></tag>
			<tag slug="escorted-tours"><![CDATA[escorted-tours]]></tag>
			<tag slug="luxury-hotels-resorts"><![CDATA[luxury-hotels-resorts]]></tag>
			<tag slug="beach-sun"><![CDATA[beach-sun]]></tag>
			<tag slug="family-vacations"><![CDATA[family-vacations]]></tag>
			<tag slug="honeymoons"><![CDATA[honeymoons]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>
