<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>

<!--BEGIN: 2001 CEL-->​
	<element date="2001" id="banner-2001-cel">
		<country><![CDATA[ca]]></country>
		<tactic><![CDATA[banner]]></tactic>
		<year><![CDATA[12]]></year>
		<month><![CDATA[01]]></month>
		<id_live><![CDATA[01]]></id_live>
​
		<supplier><![CDATA[Celebrity Cruises<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></supplier>
		<directory><![CDATA[cel]]></directory>
​
		<title><![CDATA[Sail Beyond Event]]></title>
		<intro><![CDATA[During Celebrity&rsquo;s biggest event of the year, everyone in &mdash;any stateroom&mdash;saves.]]></intro>
		<offer><![CDATA[
			We invite you to Elevate &amp; Save with a FREE 2-Category Suite Upgrade and Up To 20% Savings* on select voyages.
		]]></offer>
		<content><![CDATA[
			<p>During the Sail Beyond Event everyone saves in any stateroom. Plus, the first two guests enjoy a bonus perk!<p>

			<p>The Perks:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Classic Beverage Package</li>
				<li>Prepaid Tips</li>
				<li>Unlimited Wi-Fi </li>
				<li>$150 to spend on board</li>
			</ul>

			<p>Cruise Fare Savings Per Person (1st/2nd Guest only)</p>
			<ul>
				<li>$100 per person Inside and Ocean View </li>
				<li>$200 per person Veranda, Concierge Class, AquaClass&reg; </li>
				<li>$500 per person Suites  </li>
			</ul>

			<p>50% Reduced Cruise Fare for additional guests (3rd/4th/5th) in triple, quad, family staterooms</p>

			<p>Simply book by March 4, 2020, almost any sailing departing January 1, 2020, through May 3, 2022.</p>
		]]></content>
​
		<terms id="banner-2001-cel">
			<consumer><![CDATA[
				Cruise must be booked December. 19, 2019 -March 04, 2020 (the &ldquo;Offer Period&rdquo;). Offer applies to select 4-night and longer sailings departing 01/01/20 &ndash; 05/03/22   Offer excludes Galapagos cruises. Full deposit must be paid by deposit payment required due date. Standard full deposit penalty is applied if booking is cancelled within final payment period; see Celebrity&rsquo;s cancellation policy for details. Nonrefundable Deposit:  To qualify for the lowest available cruise fare, guest must choose a non-refundable deposit.  Non-refundable deposit booking (&ldquo;NRDB&rdquo;) cancelled prior to final payment due date will receive a future cruise credit in the amount of the deposit minus a $100 per person service fee. FCC is non-transferable and expires after 12-months from issue date. $100 per person service fee applies to changes to NRDB ship or sail date.  Applicable to groups at prevailing rates. Not applicable to incentive, contract, or charter groups. Nonrefundable deposit offers are not applicable to sailings within final payment. Sail Beyond Event:  Each of the first two guests in a qualifying inside, ocean view, veranda, Concierge Class or AquaClass stateroom are eligible to receive one amenity with the choice of a &ldquo;Price Only Rate&rdquo; or one additional amenity (for a total of three) with a &ldquo;Two Perks Included Rate&rdquo;: Classic Beverage Package, Unlimited Internet Package, $150 OBC or Prepaid Gratuities. Savings amounts are per person and vary by stateroom category:  $100 for inside and ocean view; $200 for veranda, Concierge Class, and AquaClass&reg;; $500 for Suites.  Offer applies to first two guests in the stateroom and will be applied automatically. 50% Off Savings:  Savings applies to the cruise fare of the third and fourth passengers booked in any stateroom category type.  Not applicable to Cruisetours. Suite Perks Offer: Each of the first two guests in a suite receive four amenities: Premium Beverage Package, Unlimited Internet Package, Prepaid Gratuities, and $150 per person onboard credit (&ldquo;OBC&rdquo;). Promo codes are not required. Guests with Internet Packages will receive instructions for Internet access in their staterooms on the first day of the cruise.  OBC: Guests&rsquo; onboard account will be credited with an OBC. OBC has no cash value, is applicable to cruise only, non-transferable, not redeemable for cash, and will expire if not used by 10:00 PM on the final night of the cruise. Prepaid Gratuities option provides for prepaid stateroom, waiter, assistant waiter, and headwaiter gratuities in the amount suggested by Celebrity&rsquo;s guidelines. Gratuities will be applied to the reservation within 10 days of booking date. Offer applies to new individual bookings and to staterooms in non-contracted group bookings, which must be named and deposited during the Offer Period. Offer is capacity controlled; availability varies by sailing, and eligible staterooms may sell out. All offers are non-transferable and applicable only to the Offer Cruise. Offer is not combinable with Exciting Deals, Interline, Senior, Loyalty, Resident, Net, Travel Partner or Employee Rates. No refunds or credits will be granted for unused options. Offer and prices are subject to availability and change without notice, capacity controlled, and not applicable to charters or contracted groups. Single occupancy bookings are eligible for the Offer. Changes to booking may result in removal of Offer. Refer to the Cruise Ticket Contract for additional terms and conditions. Celebrity reserves the right to cancel the Offer at any time, correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions, and change or update fares, fees and surcharges at any time without prior notice. &copy;2019 Celebrity Cruises. Ships&rsquo; registry: Malta and Ecuador.11/2019
<br><br>
Ensemble Xtra: Offer applies to 4-night and longer itineraries that depart Oct. 1st, 2019 through December 31st, 2021. Bookings must be made between Oct. 1st, 2019 and December 31, 2020. Offer excludes Galapagos and Future cruise bookings. $100 per stateroom Shore Excursion credit will be applied in the form of an onboard credit. Offer is $100 Onboard credit &ldquo;OBC&rdquo; per stateroom for Concierge, and Aqua class cabins. Offers are applicable to new individual bookings and to staterooms in non-contracted group bookings, which must be named and deposited. Guests&rsquo; stateroom folios will be credited with an OBC. OBC has no cash value, is applicable to cruise only, non-transferable, not redeemable for cash, and will expire if not used by 10:00 PM on the final night of the cruise. Offer excludes interior, oceanview, standard veranda and suite staterooms. Offer is not combinable with any other offer, promotion or discounted fare other than Sail Your Way. Single occupancy bookings are eligible for the Offer. Refer to Cruise Ticket Contract for additional terms and conditions. Celebrity reserves the right to cancel the Offer at any time, correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions, and change or update fares, fees and surcharges at any time without prior notice &copy;2019 Celebrity Cruises Inc. Ships&rsquo; registry: Malta
			]]></consumer>
​
			<agent><![CDATA[
				Travel Agents: Group bookings that are named prior to the start date of the Offer cannot be cancelled and rebooked under this Offer.
				<br><br>
				Ensemble Xtra:<br>
				Bookings should be made through Espresso and/or normal reservations methods but must select/request the ENSEMBLEXTRA.]]></agent>
		</terms>
​
		<products>
			<!-- PRODUCT ONE -->
			<product id="banner-2001-cel">
				<title><![CDATA[Alaska Hubbard Glacier]]></title>
				<offer><![CDATA[Our Agency Exclusive Offer: Book an Aqua Class or Concierge Class cabin and receive an additional $100 Shore Excursion Credit on applicable sailings.]]></offer>
				<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
​
				<cost><![CDATA[1,929]]></cost>
				<taxes><![CDATA[190.78]]></taxes>
				<departing><![CDATA[Jul 12, 2020]]></departing>
				<duration><![CDATA[7 nights]]></duration>
				<pricing><![CDATA[Price is per person based on double occupancy.]]></pricing>
				<currency><![CDATA[USD]]></currency>
​
				<ship><![CDATA[Celebrity Eclipse]]></ship>
				<category><![CDATA[Concierge Class]]></category>
				<embarkation><![CDATA[Roundtrip]]></embarkation>
				<disembarkation><![CDATA[Vancouver]]></disembarkation>
​
				<img_hero><![CDATA[prod-cel-01-ca.jpg]]></img_hero>
​
				<amenities_title><![CDATA[]]></amenities_title>
				<amenities_desc><![CDATA[]]></amenities_desc>
				<exclusives_title><![CDATA[Ports of Call]]></exclusives_title>
				<exclusives_desc>
				<![CDATA[
					<ul>
						<li>Vancouver; Icy Strait Point, Alaska;  Juneau, Alaska; Ketchikan, Alaska; Vancouver</li>
					</ul>
				]]></exclusives_desc>
				<inclusions_title><![CDATA[Inclusions]]></inclusions_title>
				<inclusions_desc>
				<![CDATA[
					<ul>
						<li>Accommodation</li>
						<li>Award-winning cuisine</li>
						<li>Pools</li>
						<li>Fitness centre &amp; classes</li>
						<li>Entertainment</li>
						<li>Children&rsquo;s clubs</li>
						<li>Port immersion</li>
					</ul>
				]]>
				</inclusions_desc>
​
				<terms><![CDATA[]]></terms>
				<img_map></img_map>
			</product>
​
			<!-- PRODUCT TWO -->
			<product id="banner-2001-cel">
				<title><![CDATA[Australia, Tasmania &amp; New Zealand]]></title>
				<offer><![CDATA[Our Agency Exclusive Offer: Book an Aqua Class or Concierge Class cabin and receive an additional $100 Shore Excursion Credit on applicable sailings.]]></offer>
				<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
​
				<cost><![CDATA[2,449]]></cost>
				<taxes><![CDATA[217.42]]></taxes>
				<departing><![CDATA[Oct 28, 2020]]></departing>
				<duration><![CDATA[12 nights]]></duration>
				<pricing><![CDATA[Price is per person based on double occupancy.]]></pricing>
				<currency><![CDATA[USD]]></currency>
​
				<ship><![CDATA[Celebrity Solstice]]></ship>
				<category><![CDATA[Concierge Class]]></category>
				<embarkation><![CDATA[Roundtrip]]></embarkation>
				<disembarkation><![CDATA[Sydney]]></disembarkation>
​
				<img_hero><![CDATA[prod-cel-02-ca.jpg]]></img_hero>
​
				<amenities_title><![CDATA[]]></amenities_title>
				<amenities_desc><![CDATA[]]></amenities_desc>
				<exclusives_title><![CDATA[Ports of Call]]></exclusives_title>
				<exclusives_desc>
				<![CDATA[
					<ul>
						<li>Sydney, Australia; Hobart, Tasmania; Milford Sound, New Zealand; Akaroa, New Zealand;  Wellington, New Zealand; Sydney, Australia </li>
					</ul>
				]]>
				</exclusives_desc>
				<inclusions_title><![CDATA[Inclusions]]></inclusions_title>
				<inclusions_desc>
				<![CDATA[
					<ul>
						<li>Accommodation</li>
						<li>Award-winning cuisine</li>
						<li>Pools</li>
						<li>Fitness centre &amp; classes</li>
						<li>Entertainment</li>
						<li>Children&rsquo;s clubs</li>
						<li>Port immersion</li>
					</ul>
				]]>
				</inclusions_desc>
​
				<terms><![CDATA[]]></terms>
				<img_map></img_map>
			</product>
​
			<!-- PRODUCT THREE -->
			<product id="banner-2001-cel">
				<title><![CDATA[Italy &amp; Best of Greek Islands]]></title>
				<offer><![CDATA[Our Agency Exclusive Offer: Book an Aqua Class or Concierge Class cabin and receive an additional $100 Shore Excursion Credit on applicable sailings.]]></offer>
				<description><![CDATA[]]></description>
​
				<cost><![CDATA[3,909]]></cost>
				<taxes><![CDATA[88]]></taxes>
				<departing><![CDATA[Aug 07, 2020]]></departing>
				<duration><![CDATA[10 nights]]></duration>
				<pricing><![CDATA[Price is per person based on double occupancy.]]></pricing>
				<currency><![CDATA[USD]]></currency>
​
				<ship><![CDATA[Celebrity Edge]]></ship>
				<category><![CDATA[Concierge Class]]></category>
				<embarkation><![CDATA[Roundtrip]]></embarkation>
				<disembarkation><![CDATA[Rome]]></disembarkation>
​
				<img_hero><![CDATA[prod-cel-03-ca.jpg]]></img_hero>
​
				<amenities_title><![CDATA[]]></amenities_title>
				<amenities_desc><![CDATA[]]></amenities_desc>
				<exclusives_title><![CDATA[Ports of Call]]></exclusives_title>
				<exclusives_desc>
				<![CDATA[
					<ul>
						<li>Sicily (Messina), Italy; Santorini, Greece; Athens (Piraeus), Greece; Mykonos, Greece; Rhodes, Greece; Chania (Souda), Crete, Greece; Naples, Italy</li>
					</ul>
				]]>
				</exclusives_desc>
				<inclusions_title><![CDATA[Inclusions]]></inclusions_title>
				<inclusions_desc>
				<![CDATA[
					<ul>
						<li>Accommodation</li>
						<li>Award-winning cuisine</li>
						<li>Pools</li>
						<li>Fitness centre &amp; classes</li>
						<li>Entertainment</li>
						<li>Children&rsquo;s clubs</li>
						<li>Port immersion</li>
					</ul>
				]]>
				</inclusions_desc>
​
				<terms><![CDATA[]]></terms>
				<img_map></img_map>
			</product>
		</products>
​
		<brandcolor>002C74</brandcolor>
		<iframe_height></iframe_height>
		<id_ezine><![CDATA[banner-01]]></id_ezine>
		<file><![CDATA[]]></file>
	</element>
<!--END: 2001 CEL-->

<!--BEGIN: 2001 HAL-->
	<element date="2001" id="banner-2001-hal">
		<country><![CDATA[ca]]></country>
		<tactic><![CDATA[banner]]></tactic>
		<year><![CDATA[20]]></year>
		<month><![CDATA[01]]></month>
		<id_live><![CDATA[02]]></id_live>
​
		<supplier><![CDATA[Holland America Line<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></supplier>
		<directory><![CDATA[hal]]></directory>
​
		<title><![CDATA[View &amp; Verandah. Move Up, Get More&mdash;Upgrade Event.]]></title>
		<intro><![CDATA[Encounter fascinating peoples, places and cultures the world over on a classic-style cruise.]]></intro>
		<offer><![CDATA[
			Choose from 500+ sailings and receive:

			<ul>
				<li>Free stateroom upgrades</li>
				<li>Up to US$500 Onboard Spending Money</li>
				<li>Free or reduced fares for kids</li>
				<li>10% off select shore excursions </li>
				<li>50% reduced deposit </li>
			</ul>

			Plus, book a suite and receive prepaid gratuities!
		]]></offer>
		<content><![CDATA[
			<p>Book a summer cruise to Alaska, Europe and beyond and receive FREE stateroom upgrades, up to US$500 onboard spending money, shore excursion discounts, prepaid gratuities and more. Plus, book by January 17, 2020, and get a $50 Beverage Card.</p>
		]]></content>
​
		<terms id="banner-2001-hal">
			<consumer><![CDATA[
				*Fares and View &amp; Verandah offers are based on Promo(s) NV/VV/ZV. Featured fares are per person based on double occupancy, cruise or Land+Sea Journeys only.  Fares are in Canadian dollars. Taxes, Fees &amp; Port Expenses are included and range from CAD$123.50 to CAD$1,378.00. Subject to availability. Offers are per stateroom based on double occupancy, for 1st and 2nd guests sharing a stateroom and exclude 3rd/4th guests, except as provided herein. Offers are available for new bookings only, apply only to the cruise portion of Alaska Land+Sea Journeys, are not combinable with any other discounts and are not transferable or refundable.  Offers are applicable on select 2020 &amp; 2021 departures. Stateroom Upgrades are available in select stateroom categories and are subject to availability of the staterooms in the higher category. Onboard Spending Money amounts vary by cruise length. Onboard spending money is in U.S. dollars and is non-refundable, non-transferable, not for cash value, expires at the end of the cruise, and may not be used in the casino. Kids or Third/fourths Offer is based on sharing a stateroom with 1st and 2nd guests, valid on select sailings, and are based on Promo NV. Taxes, fees, &amp; port expenses apply to all extra guests. Shore Excursion Offer applies only to select shore excursions on select sailings, purchased in advance of embarkation, prior to March 14, 2020. Reduced Deposit is valid for new bookings only. Bookings made on voyages requiring immediate final payment are not eligible for a reduced deposit. Suite Offer: Prepaid gratuities (hotel service charges): Holland America Line pre-pays room gratuities on behalf of guests. Gratuities for bar, dining room wine accounts, or spa/salon services are not included. Beverage Card Offer expires January 17, 2020 and is valued at US$50 per person and is applicable to all guests. Card is non-transferable, refundable, nor redeemable for cash. For full terms &amp; conditions please refer to your travel advisor. For more information about our stateroom categories, suite descriptions, and deck plans, please refer to the appropriate Holland America Line brochure. Offers are capacity controlled, and may be modified or withdrawn without prior notice. Other restrictions may apply. View &amp; Verandah offers end February 28, 2020. Ships' Registry: The Netherlands.
			]]></consumer>
​
			<agent><![CDATA[]]></agent>
		</terms>
​
		<products>
			<!-- PRODUCT ONE -->
			<product id="banner-2001-hal">
				<title><![CDATA[Great Alaskan Explorer]]></title>
				<offer><![CDATA[US$75 onboard spending money per stateroom!]]></offer>
				<description><![CDATA[Board this convenient Vancouver roundtrip cruise and experience nature&rsquo;s awesome sculpting power at Tracy Arm and Hubbard Glacier. Visit Homer, the &ldquo;Halibut Capital of the World.]]></description>
​
				<cost><![CDATA[2,959]]></cost>
				<taxes><![CDATA[included]]></taxes>
				<departing><![CDATA[Jul 13, 2020]]></departing>
				<duration><![CDATA[14 days]]></duration>
				<pricing><![CDATA[Price is per person based on double occupancy.]]></pricing>
				<currency><![CDATA[CAD]]></currency>
​
				<ship><![CDATA[Maasdam]]></ship>
				<category><![CDATA[Interior with complimentary upgrade to ocean view!]]></category>
				<embarkation><![CDATA[Roundtrip]]></embarkation>
				<disembarkation><![CDATA[Vancouver]]></disembarkation>
​
				<img_hero><![CDATA[prod-hal-01-ca.jpg]]></img_hero>
​
				<amenities_title><![CDATA[]]></amenities_title>
				<amenities_desc><![CDATA[]]></amenities_desc>
				<exclusives_title><![CDATA[]]></exclusives_title>
				<exclusives_desc><![CDATA[]]></exclusives_desc>
				<inclusions_title><![CDATA[]]></inclusions_title>
				<inclusions_desc><![CDATA[]]></inclusions_desc>
​
				<terms><![CDATA[]]></terms>
				<img_map></img_map>
			</product>
​
			<!-- PRODUCT TWO -->
			<product id="banner-2001-hal">
				<title><![CDATA[Newfoundland &amp; New England Discovery]]></title>
				<offer><![CDATA[
					Up to US$50 onboard spending money per stateroom!]]></offer>
				<description><![CDATA[First of the Vista-class ships, Zuiderdam boasts classic nautical lines and finishes, modern amenities and a spectacular art and antique collection.]]></description>
​
				<cost><![CDATA[3,379]]></cost>
				<taxes><![CDATA[included]]></taxes>
				<departing><![CDATA[Sep 7, 2020]]></departing>
				<duration><![CDATA[10 days]]></duration>
				<pricing><![CDATA[Price is per person based on double occupancy.]]></pricing>
				<currency><![CDATA[CAD]]></currency>
​
				<ship><![CDATA[Zuiderdam]]></ship>
				<category><![CDATA[Obstructed ocean view with complimentary upgrade to verandah!]]></category>
				<embarkation><![CDATA[Boston]]></embarkation>
				<disembarkation><![CDATA[Quebec City]]></disembarkation>
​
				<img_hero><![CDATA[prod-hal-02-ca.jpg]]></img_hero>
​
				<amenities_title><![CDATA[]]></amenities_title>
				<amenities_desc><![CDATA[]]></amenities_desc>
				<exclusives_title><![CDATA[]]></exclusives_title>
				<exclusives_desc><![CDATA[]]></exclusives_desc>
				<inclusions_title><![CDATA[]]></inclusions_title>
				<inclusions_desc><![CDATA[]]></inclusions_desc>
​
				<terms><![CDATA[]]></terms>
				<img_map></img_map>
			</product>
​
			<!-- PRODUCT THREE -->
			<product id="banner-2001-hal">
				<title><![CDATA[Greek Odyssey]]></title>
				<offer><![CDATA[
					Our agency exclusive hosted sailing: Complimentary shore excursion, traveller cocktail party, and company of a gracious onboard host.]]></offer>
				<description><![CDATA[Rome is your launching point to the wonders of ancient Greece and its picturesque isles. Cap off your journey with an overnight stay in romantic Venice.]]></description>
​
				<cost><![CDATA[3,179]]></cost>
				<taxes><![CDATA[included]]></taxes>
				<departing><![CDATA[Jun 27, 2020]]></departing>
				<duration><![CDATA[12 days]]></duration>
				<pricing><![CDATA[Price is per person based on double occupancy.]]></pricing>
				<currency><![CDATA[CAD]]></currency>
​
				<ship><![CDATA[Nieuw Amsterdam]]></ship>
				<category><![CDATA[Obstructed ocean view with complimentary upgrade to verandah!]]></category>
				<embarkation><![CDATA[Rome]]></embarkation>
				<disembarkation><![CDATA[Venice]]></disembarkation>
​
				<img_hero><![CDATA[prod-hal-03-ca.jpg]]></img_hero>
​
				<amenities_title><![CDATA[]]></amenities_title>
				<amenities_desc><![CDATA[]]></amenities_desc>
				<exclusives_title><![CDATA[]]></exclusives_title>
				<exclusives_desc><![CDATA[]]></exclusives_desc>
				<inclusions_title><![CDATA[]]></inclusions_title>
				<inclusions_desc><![CDATA[]]>
				</inclusions_desc>
​
				<terms><![CDATA[]]></terms>
				<img_map></img_map>
			</product>
		</products>
​
		<brandcolor>29417D</brandcolor>
		<iframe_height></iframe_height>
		<id_ezine><![CDATA[banner-02]]></id_ezine>
		<file><![CDATA[]]></file>
	</element>

<!--END: 2001 HAL-->
​
</root>
