<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>

<!-- BEGIN: 1911 AVL-CA -->
<article date="1911" id="01">
	<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
	<pub_date><![CDATA[November 2019]]></pub_date>
	<dir_year><![CDATA[19]]></dir_year>
	<dir_month><![CDATA[11]]></dir_month>
	<id_article><![CDATA[01]]></id_article>
​
	<author><![CDATA[Avalon Waterways<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></author>
	<id_supplier><![CDATA[avl]]></id_supplier>
​
	<title><![CDATA[YOU Navigate. WE&rsquo;LL STEER.]]></title>
	<teaser><![CDATA[Avalon Waterways<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></teaser>
	<lead><![CDATA[In 2020, Avalon Waterways is inviting travellers to chart their own course, at their own pace, before or after their cruise with its new <strong>YourWay</strong> program.  Utilizing sister companies Monograms and Globus, Avalon Waterways is making it easier than ever before for cruisers to customize their European river cruise vacation from start to finish.]]></lead>
	<body><![CDATA[
		<p>In 2020, using Avalon&rsquo;s YourWay options, travellers can book their cruise and then add-on &hellip;</p>

		<ol>
			<li>An <strong>Avalon Waterways land extension</strong> featuring expert, guided sightseeing; </li>
			<li>A <strong>Monograms independent vacation package</strong> that comes with hand-picked hotel accommodations, city sightseeing and the on-site services of a Local Host;</li>
			<li>A <strong>Globus escorted touring vacation</strong> with included sightseeing, hotel accommodations, transportation and coach driver, Tour Director and certified Local Guides.</li>
		</ol>

		<p>&ldquo;With our new YourWay program, we&rsquo;re making it easier for travellers to extend their river cruise vacation with land itineraries that are perfectly suited to their preferences and budget,&rdquo; said Pam Hoffee, managing director of Avalon Waterways. &ldquo;No matter which YourWay extension our guests choose, we will take care of details like ship-to-hotel transportation, hotel accommodations and sightseeing in the world&rsquo;s most fascinating cities &ndash; from Paris to Prague and Budapest to Berlin.&rdquo; The extensions are available either before or after the Avalon cruise.</p>

		<p>In addition, with its exclusive onboard Avalon Choice menu on every river cruise itinerary, travellers have their pick of the widest array of included excursions, from classic sightseeing to immersive discoveries and active adventures.</p>

		<ol>
			<li><strong>CLASSIC.</strong> A local expert guides guests through the history and heritage of local destinations to marvel at legends, lore and architecture of iconic and historic sites.</li>
			<li><strong>DISCOVERY.</strong> Travellers are invited to engage in inspiring and interactive activities designed to cater to their interests &ndash; from cooking classes to painting workshops and encounters with local providers and vintners. Discovery excursions help travellers immerse themselves in culture.</li>
			<li><strong>ACTIVE.</strong> Avalon guests can embark on energetic excursions &ndash; from a guided jogging tour of Amsterdam to biking, paddling and hiking their way through each destination &ndash; keeping in motion and on the go.</li>
		</ol>

		<p>And for those who prefer to explore ashore independently, the company&rsquo;s AvalonGO App helps travellers explore each port of call throughout their cruise with a detailed, daily schedule of the itinerary, a list of nearby attractions (featuring hours of operation, historical facts and more), maps, directions as well as local caf&eacute;s, restaurants, bars and entertainment options. &ldquo;With the flexibility to choose exactly where to go before and after a cruising vacation, plus the freedom of Avalon Choice onboard each and every cruise, Avalon Waterways is helping travellers see the world the way they&rsquo;ve always envisioned,&rdquo; said Hoffee.</p>
	]]></body>
​
	<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
​
	<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/hero/advertorial-01.jpg</hero_src>
	<hero_caption><![CDATA[YOU Navigate. WE&rsquo;LL STEER.]]></hero_caption>
	<hero_credit><![CDATA[Avalon Waterways<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></hero_credit>
	<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/advertorial-01.jpg
	</article_src>
	<article_caption><![CDATA[YOU Navigate. WE&rsquo;LL STEER.]]></article_caption>
	<article_credit><![CDATA[Avalon Waterways<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></article_credit>
​
	<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
	<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
	<tile_new>none</tile_new>
​
	<tags>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
	</tags>
</article>
<!-- BEGIN: 1911 AVL-CA -->

<!-- BEGIN: 1911 CEN -->
	<article date="1911" id="02">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[November 2019]]></pub_date> <!-- Mmm = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[19]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[11]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[02]]></id_article>
​
		<author><![CDATA[Central Holidays&trade;]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[cen]]></id_supplier>
​
		<title><![CDATA[5 Amazing Less-Traveled European Destinations for Your Next Trip]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Central Holidays&trade;]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Seeing Paris&rsquo; Eiffel Tower or visiting Italy&rsquo;s Colosseum for the first time is a thrill. But it&rsquo;s more soul-satisfying touring with lesser crowds and more magic moments.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>Here are 5 off the beaten path Europe destinations for your next trip:</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/advertorial-02-01.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Valletta, Malta</h4>
					<p>Sandwiched between the Marsamxett and Grand Harbour is the fortified city of Valletta. You can explore this fabulous Maltese capital without much of a stretch as it&rsquo;s a little city. Valletta is known for its varied attractions - and with new additions, it has been named Europe&rsquo;s Capital of Culture.</p>
					<p>Bursting with history, Valletta is regarded as a UNESCO World Heritage Site. Start your tour at Saint John's, which is a history-rich and eye-catching church that showcases the success of the Maltese Knights. In the 16th century, the Knights safeguarded Europe and the Catholics from the brutal attacks by the Ottoman Turks.</p>
					<p>Explore the cathedral&rsquo;s opulent, flamboyant Baroque interior. You can then walk down Republic Street to explore the immense Grand Master's Palace. Lastly, don&rsquo;t miss a visit to the Upper Barracca Gardens. Valletta&rsquo;s inner streets are packed with great stories and buildings. The Parliament buildings, the Manoel theatre, and St George&rsquo;s Square all deserve exploration.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>


			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/advertorial-02-02.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Coimbra and &Oacute;bidos, Portugal</h4>
					<p>Coimbra is the place for you if you&rsquo;re looking to supplement your beach time in Portugal with some astonishing history and breathtaking architecture that span nearly a millennium.</p>
					<p>This Portuguese town is characterized by its lively city center, the remarkable churches, and the Roman architecture. Enjoy educational highlights at one of Europe&rsquo;s oldest universities, established in 1290. You&rsquo;ll definitely love the University&rsquo;s spectacular library.</p>
					<p>Coimbra is home to some awe-inspiring churches such as the Igreja de Senhor da Pedra. Walk down the stone-paved narrow streets and explore the striking white-washed buildings.</p>
					<p>Step back in time by visiting the medieval walls of &Oacute;bidos and take in the atmospheric scene of a medieval village.  Splurge and spend the night at Coimbra&rsquo;s Pousada de &Oacute;bidos, one of the town's main attractions.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>


			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/advertorial-02-03.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Zadar, Croatia</h4>
					<p>From the golden-hued churches to stunning natural beauty and incredible cuisine, Zadar guarantees you a unique and memorable holiday experience. Located in the north of Croatia, this intriguing city is rich in history, culture, and nature in equal measures.</p>
					<p>Enjoy a tour through the city&rsquo;s old streets before stumbling upon the first Sea Organ, one of Zadar&rsquo;s contemporary architectural achievements. Soak up the Sea Organ&rsquo;s haunting sounds right on the solar-powered public dancefloor. A short distance from the historic city you&rsquo;ll explore plenty of nature and the emerald waters of Plitvice lakes without the tourist vibe.</p>
					<p>Famous for the Venetian and Roman remanants of its Old Town, make a visit to the Forum - the city&rsquo;s major meeting place. Rest in the shadow of a Roman column, where criminals were chained and publicly humiliated. Oh, and make sure you try out the city&rsquo;s ultra-fresh fish or Maraschino, a locally-made cherry liqueur.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>


			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/advertorial-02-04.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Piran, Slovenia</h4>
					<p>Piran&rsquo;s proximity to the sea and its rich history draw magical scenes and unsurpassed charm. Commonly known as the Venice of Slovenia for its enviable location on the Adriatic coast, the city offers a more relaxed alternative to other destinations. </p>
					<p>As part of the small Slovenian shoreline, the beaches are popular, and with the stupendous Portoro&#382; beach nearby, it makes for a great blend of history and sun lounging. The area nearby the city feels totally different, with olive groves, vineyards, and a quaint vibe.</p>
					<p>Comprised of red rooftops and white-hued buildings, a tour to Piran will make you feel like you&rsquo;ve walked right into a picturesque postcard. Walk through the old town on the charming narrow streets. At the town&rsquo;s main square, you&rsquo;ll be greeted by the statue of Giuseppe Tartini, a renowned composer and virtuoso violinist.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>


			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/advertorial-02-05.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Naxos, Greece</h4>
					<p>Naxos Island is one of Greece&rsquo;s hidden gems and it&rsquo;s worth a visit during your tour. It&rsquo;s located only an hour from Mykonos and a few more from Athens.</p>
					<p>The island boasts mouthwatering local delicacies, ancient hilltop villages, Byzantine history, and countless natural sand beaches. Thus, you&rsquo;ll have plenty to explore in this less-visited treasure. You&rsquo;ll surely fall in love with this island filled with all shades of blue under the sun.</p>
					<p>An easy and perfect place to start exploring Naxos&rsquo; charm is the old town. Wander down the seafront promenade; the place is packed with vibrant cafes and shops that have spectacular sunset views.</p>
					<p>With such a diverse landscape, Naxos grants a little more adventure compared to a standard, poolside island retreat.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>
		]]></body>
​
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
​
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/hero/advertorial-02.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[5 Amazing Less-Traveled European Destinations for Your Next Trip]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Central Holidays&trade;]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/advertorial-02.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[5 Amazing Less-Traveled European Destinations for Your Next Trip]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Central Holidays&trade;]]></article_credit>
​
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
​
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
<!-- END: 1911 CEN -->

<!-- BEGIN: 1911 CTK -->
	<article date="1911" id="03">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[November 2019]]></pub_date> <!-- Mmm = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[19]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[11]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[03]]></id_article>
​
		<author><![CDATA[Natalie Siagia, Contiki Traveler]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[ctk]]></id_supplier>
​
		<title><![CDATA[6 Benefits Of Travelling On A Group Tour]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[
			If you're reading this, you're probably wondering "why on earth should I consider a group trip with Contiki?" Well, what if we told you&hellip;
		]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			These days tours range from 15-30+ people depending on where you are travelling to.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<h4>You're never alone</h4>
			<p>Generally, you&rsquo;ll get a diverse mix of ages (with Contiki every traveler is always between the ages of 18-35), nationalities and characters in one vicinity, so you&rsquo;ll always find your own little wolf-pack within the group. If you&rsquo;re an inexperienced traveler, it&rsquo;s comforting to know that you&rsquo;re going to be looked after and make friends from all over the world, giving you that much-needed confidence boost so that the next time you travel you&rsquo;ll be all over it like a rash.</p>
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/advertorial-03-01.jpg">
			</figure>

			<h4>Insider's knowledge and a local guide</h4>
			<p>Imagine someone with you at all times who eliminates all your niggles and worries so you can just enjoy exploring new lands. On a group tour, you are with the industry&rsquo;s best trip managers and local expert guides &ndash; people who go through rigorous training (and we mean rigorous &ndash; think army boot camp style) to ensure that you are in the best possible hands at any time of the day (or night). Want to know where the best gelato in Italy is? Ask your guide. Want to go off-the-beaten path and see something cool? Ask your guide. They will help you unlock the history and insider knowledge of the world&rsquo;s greatest destinations, so you can get the absolute most out of your experience, without spending your whole time searching the internet or trawling guide books. Think of them as an encyclopedia, but for travel.</p>

			<h4>More time to yourself than you would think...</h4>
			<p>Perhaps one of the greatest myths circulating group travel is that you don&rsquo;t get a lot of &ldquo;free time.&rdquo; We know the contrary. Group travel has evolved over the years as people&rsquo;s habits and requirements have changed. It&rsquo;s no longer a case of following a guide through a packed city center as they hold an umbrella in the air that you have to follow religiously. Instead, it&rsquo;s about giving you options. Obviously you&rsquo;re going to want to do the &lsquo;must-do&rsquo;s&rsquo; which a group travel trip will sort for you, but equally you&rsquo;ve got total freedom to spend your &lsquo;me time&lsquo; how you please. So basically, best of  both worlds &ndash; the itinerary of dreams, and the choice to go off course. #Winning.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/advertorial-03-02.jpg">
			</figure>

			<h4>Value that packs a punch</h4>
			<p>At the end of the day, group travel is there to make your holiday seamless and effortless. Add to that a truly valuable experience with a heap of inclusions that means more money in your pocket for food, shopping, or cool experiences. Most often, accommodation, breakfast, transportation, a trip manager and exclusive access to sights is also included. Value central.</p>

			<h4>Hassle-free</h4>
			<p>Sit back, relax and enjoy the adventure because on group tours, it&rsquo;s hassle free. Navigating through a new country can sometimes be difficult. New languages, customs, and ways to get around. On group tours, you generally don&rsquo;t have to worry about organizing or planning as much &ndash; you can just go with the flow, cocktail in hand, and let someone else deal with the stress.</p>

			<h4>Find your future soulmate</h4>
			<p>Because let&rsquo;s face it &ndash; who really needs Tinder to find love when it&rsquo;s as simple as travelling the world and embracing single life. You&rsquo;re amidst a bunch of like-minded individuals, experiencing new cultures with a positive attitude &ndash; be open to whatever lies ahead. We&rsquo;ve heard of enough Contiki romances, marriages and babies to know that group tours, and constant human interaction can certainly help you find your future soulmate &ndash; or at least &ndash; start the conversation and form new friendships!</p>

			<p>Ready for the adventure of a lifetime?  With new wellness trips, train journeys, and even more unique local experiences you can only find with Contiki, Europe and the rest of the world awaits.  Make it a year to remember.</p>
		]]></body>
​
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
​
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/hero/advertorial-03.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[6 Benefits Of Travelling On A Group Tour]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Contiki]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/advertorial-03.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[6 Benefits Of Travelling On A Group Tour]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Contiki]]></article_credit>
​
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
​
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
<!-- END: 1911 CTK -->

</root>
