<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
​
	<article date="1911" id="01">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[ship]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[November 2019]]></pub_date> <!-- Mmm = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[19]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[11]]></dir_month>
		<file_ship><![CDATA[01]]></file_ship>
​
		<tab_class><![CDATA[active]]></tab_class> <!-- If there's more than one ship showcase, only the first showcase has the 'active' class -->
​
		<author><![CDATA[Viking]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[vik]]></id_supplier>
		<translator><![CDATA[]]></translator>
​
		<title><![CDATA[Embark on a Journey of Discovery]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[
			Viking<sup>&reg;</sup> brings you closer to the cultures of the world with destination-focused itineraries on the rivers of Europe, Russia, Ukraine, China, Southeast Asia and Egypt.
		]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			You are invited to sail with like-minded travelers on The Thinking Person&rsquo;s Cruise<sup>&reg;</sup>, a culturally rich, immersive experience designed to help you explore and engage with your destination. 
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>Plus, the Viking Inclusive Value covers just about everything&mdash;port charges, Wi-Fi, meals, lectures, onboard activities and shore excursions&mdash;so all you have to do is relax and enjoy a great journey. And the award-winning Viking Longships<sup>&reg;</sup> have set the standard in river cruising with spacious Veranda Staterooms, the largest suites in Europe, al fresco dining and more. Discover for yourself why Viking truly is The World&rsquo;s Leading River Cruise Line<sup>&reg;</sup>.</p>
		]]></body>
​
		<tab_group id_supplier="supplierID">
			<tab id="01">
				<id><![CDATA[01]]></id>
				<title><![CDATA[The Ship]]></title> <!-- Le navire -->
				<content><![CDATA[
<p><strong>THE SMALL SHIP EXPERTS</strong><br>
Viking takes you closer to your destination</p>
<p><strong>THE BEST WAY TO IMMERSE YOURSELF</strong> in new cultures is to explore the world by river. That is why we designed elegant, intimate ships with all the amenities of a fine hotel. Our ships gently carry you to the world&rsquo;s greatest cities, deliver you to the center of charming towns and villages, and connect you to your destination.</p>
<p><strong>TRAVEL WITH EASE.</strong> Unpack once and relax to an ever-changing canvas of breathtaking landscapes. Arrive in the center of town&mdash;often at Viking-owned dock locations&mdash;and stroll right off to begin exploring.  Viking reveals the true character of the world&rsquo;s historic waterways by delivering you to their doorsteps.</p>
<p><strong>INNOVATIVE SHIPS ENHANCE YOUR JOURNEY.</strong> Viking Longships have set the new standard in river cruising, expertly crafted to bring the outside in. With the most al fresco dining on the rivers and vast windows that bathe the interiors in sunshine, your destination and the exhilaration of the outdoors are always within reach.</p>
<p>Because we <em>own and operate our ships,</em> no detail escapes our attention. Join us, and learn why we have consistently been the most awarded river cruise line worldwide.</p>
				]]></content>
				<tab_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/ship-01-ship.jpg</tab_src>
				<tab_caption><![CDATA[The Ship]]></tab_caption>
				<class><![CDATA[active]]></class> <!-- The first tab has the 'active' class -->
			</tab>
​
			<tab id="02">
				<id><![CDATA[02]]></id>
				<title><![CDATA[Accommodations]]></title> <!-- Hébergement -->
				<content><![CDATA[
<p><strong style="text-decoration: underline;">UNPARALLELED STATEROOM CHOICES</strong>
<em>The Viking patented design allows for more variety than other ships</em></p>
<p><strong>YOUR PRIVATE SANCTUARY ON THE RIVER.</strong> Our innovative thinking provides you with <em>more choices and a more enriching experience.</em> Each of our spacious Viking staterooms offers a hotel-style bed topped with European linens and duvets. And you will feel pampered by bathrooms equipped with heated floors and premium Freyja<sup>&reg;</sup> bath products.</p>
<p><strong>STATEROOM FEATURES</strong><br>
<ul>
	<li>Outside staterooms with river view</p>
	<li>All Upper &amp; Middle Deck staterooms have a full veranda or French balcony (a floor-to-ceiling sliding glass door)</li>
	<li>Hotel-style bed with optional twin-bed configuration</li>
	<li>Free Wi-Fi (connection speed may vary)</li>
	<li>40" or 42" flat-screen Sony<sup>&reg;</sup> TV with infotainment system featuring Movies On Demand, plus CNBC, CNN, FOX, National Geographic &amp; more</li>
	<li>Telephone, safe, refrigerator, hair dryer &amp; individual climate control</li>
	<li>Voltage: 220V &amp; 110V (US outlet), plus USB ports</li>
	<li>Private bathroom with shower; heated floor and anti-fog mirror; premium Freyja bath products; robes &amp; slippers</li>
	<li>Bottled water replenished daily</li>
	<li>Laundry service</li>
</ul>
<p><em>*All amenities on board Viking Longships; amenities vary on other ships.</em></p>
<p><strong style="text-decoration: underline;">VIKING SUITES</strong><br>
<em>The first-ever true (two-room) suites on Europe&rsquo;s river ships</em></p>
<strong>THE ULTIMATE IN LAVISH COMFORT.</strong> Viking Longships offer river cruising&rsquo;s first-ever true suites, each with <strong>TWO FULL-SIZE ROOMS.</strong> These elegant spaces are the <em>largest suites on Europe&rsquo;s rivers and provide commanding views</em>, making your destination seem close enough to touch. Our innovative Viking 
Longships are the most desirable way to see Europe&rsquo;s great waterways.</p>
				]]></content>
				<tab_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/ship-01-accommodations.jpg</tab_src>
				<tab_caption><![CDATA[Accommodations]]></tab_caption>
				<class><![CDATA[]]></class>
			</tab>
​
			<tab id="03">
				<id><![CDATA[03]]></id>
				<title><![CDATA[Dining]]></title> <!-- Gastronomie -->
				<content><![CDATA[
<p><strong>DESTINATION - FOCUSED DINING</strong>
<em>The most al fresco dining on the rivers</em></p>
<p><strong>CUISINE AND WINE ARE PART OF EVERY VIKING JOURNEY.</strong> Both engage your senses and open a window to the essence of a place. Our highly trained chefs are passionate about food and committed to providing enriching culinary experiences, whether local specialties or American classics. Our ships&rsquo; dining areas are the ideal setting for hospitable, attentive and personalized service.<p>
<p><strong>FRESH FARE AND REGIONAL CUISINE</strong><br>
bring your destination to life. Locally sourced ingredients inspire our chefs to create authentic dishes. Our extensive wine list features a vintage created by our own vintner. And, <em>our signature &ldquo;Taste of&hellip;&rdquo; events</em> introduce you to the food and drink of the region, providing the perfect opportunity to sample local flavors.</p>
<p><strong>IMPECCABLE SERVICE AMID CASUAL ELEGANCE.</strong> Indulge in attentive table service in the upscale Restaurant, whether over a sumptuous breakfast buffet, a light salad midday or a relaxed multicourse dinner. <em>Open seating gives you freedom to dine with whomever you wish.</em> Enjoy more casual meals on the Sun Deck or Aquavit Terrace<sup>&reg;</sup>, our al fresco dining area.</p>
				]]></content>
				<tab_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/ship-01-dining.jpg</tab_src>
				<tab_caption><![CDATA[Dining]]></tab_caption>
				<class><![CDATA[]]></class>
			</tab>
​
			<tab id="04">
				<id><![CDATA[04]]></id>
				<title><![CDATA[Activities]]></title> <!-- Activités -->
				<content><![CDATA[
<p><strong style="text-decoration: underline;">ONBOARD ENRICHMENT</strong><br>
<em>Bringing culture and history to life</em></p>
<p>We are pleased to bring you a curated onboard experience to complement your time ashore.</p>
<p><strong>GUEST LECTURERS</strong> expertly shed light on your destination&rsquo;s art, architecture, geopolitics and more.</p>
<p><strong>DESTINATION PERFORMANCES</strong> represent the most iconic cultural performing arts of the region&mdash; whether it be Portuguese <em>fado</em>, Viennese opera or world-renowned Mariinsky Theatre performers from St. Petersburg.</p>
<p><strong>PORT TALKS</strong> provide an overview of your ports of call through informative multimedia presentations.</p>
<p><strong>COOKING DEMONSTRATIONS</strong> present recipes of regional treats and drinks&mdash; Austrian apple strudel, R&uuml;desheim Coffee and more&mdash;so you can take the flavors of your destinations home with you.</p>
<p><strong>CRAFT DEMONSTRATIONS</strong> reveal the centuries-old traditions of local artisans, from glassblowing and lace making to silk screen printing and wooden shoemaking.</p>
<p><strong>WINE TASTINGS</strong> introduce you to a wide selection of regional wines or vintages crafted by our own Viking vintner.</p>
<p><strong>CLASSICALAND REGIONAL MUSICIANS</strong>, from local ensembles to acclaimed choirs, perform well-known and lesser-known melodies.</p>
<p><strong style="text-decoration: underline;">ONSHORE EXPERIENCES</strong><br>
<em>With an included excursion in every port, plus The Viking Way of exploration</em></p>
<p><strong>THE VIKING WAY OF EXPLORATION</strong> offers behind-the-scenes insights and opportunities that set us apart. While we feature the expected and iconic in our included shore excursions and carefully curated optional tours, we also work hard to offer our guests <strong>LOCAL LIFE, WORKING WORLD</strong> and optional <strong>PRIVILEGED ACCESS<sup>&reg;</sup></strong> experiences.</p>
				]]></content>
				<tab_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/ship-01-activities.jpg</tab_src>
				<tab_caption><![CDATA[Activities]]></tab_caption>
				<class><![CDATA[]]></class>
			</tab>
​
			<tab id="05">
				<id><![CDATA[05]]></id>
				<title><![CDATA[Services]]></title> <!-- Services -->
				<content><![CDATA[
<p><strong>AWARD - WINNING SERVICE</strong><br>
<em>Genuine warmth and thoughtful attention</em></p>
<p><strong>ONLY THE VERY BEST.</strong> Our knowledgeable and highly experienced Swiss management oversees your entire journey and handpicks each member of our onboard team. Rigorous training and inspiring leadership make Viking the employer of choice, which allows us to select the very best people to care for you, from stateroom stewards to the Captain.</p>
<p><strong>PERSONALIZED ATTENTION.</strong> Can a reservations agent make booking your journey a pleasure? Will a waiter learn your favorite wine? Is it possible for members of your ship&rsquo;s staff to feel like close friends? Yes, if those individuals work for Viking. When you have the best people, you have the best service&mdash;and Viking has both. Our English-speaking international staff is trained to the highest standards. These loyal members of the Viking family, 90% of whom return year after year, ensure you the same quality cruise after cruise.</p>
<p><strong>OUR SERVICE GUARANTEE.</strong> We are so confident we will exceed your expectations that we are the only cruise line to guarantee its award-winning service. See our website for details.</p>
				]]></content>
				<tab_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/ship-01-services.jpg</tab_src>
				<tab_caption><![CDATA[Services]]></tab_caption>
				<class><![CDATA[]]></class>
			</tab>
​
			<tab id="06">
				<id><![CDATA[06]]></id>
				<title><![CDATA[Inclusions]]></title> <!-- Inclusions -->
				<content><![CDATA[
					<p></p>
				]]></content>
				<tab_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/ship-01-inclusions.jpg</tab_src>
				<tab_caption><![CDATA[Inclusions]]></tab_caption>
				<class><![CDATA[]]></class>
			</tab>
		</tab_group>
​
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/hero/ship-01.jpg</hero_src>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/11/article/ship-01.jpg</article_src>
​
		<tile_color>005DAB</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
	</article>
​
</root>