<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2101">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[spotlight]]></dir_name> <!-- spotlight, style, spotlight -->
		<pub_date><![CDATA[January 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- January = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[01]]></dir_month>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Rocky Mountaineer]]></author>
		<translator><![CDATA[]]></translator>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Ride the Rails through North America's Rocky Mountains in 2021]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[
			Go on an unparalleled scenic journey this year.
		]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Rocky Mountaineer is expanding its award-winning luxury train experience into the USA. The new route, <strong>Rockies to the Red Rocks</strong>, showcases the beauty of the Southwest. The two-day train journey will travel through the American Rockies, between Denver, Colorado, and Moab, Utah, showcasing enchanting hoodoos, inspiring deserts, and vast canyons. This route complements the three routes in Western Canada which connect Vancouver to the majestic Canadian Rockies.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/01/article/spotlight-01.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					Arches National Park, Moab. Credit Discover Moab.
				</figcaption>
			</figure>
			
			<h4>The Experience</h4>
			<p>Rocky Mountaineer offers unparalleled journeys in its spacious glass-domed train coaches thanks to the incredible scenery, delicious cuisine, friendly service, and social atmosphere<em>.</em>&nbsp;They have been welcoming guests to explore Western Canada for 30 years, and their new route will offer everything a Rocky Mountaineer train journey is renowned for.</p>
			<p>Onboard Rocky Mountaineer, everything is choreographed to make your journey feel special, effortless and unforgettable. On this newest route, the expansive SilverLeaf Service glass-dome coaches put you right in the heart of the stunning Southwest. From the comfort of your luxury seat, this journey of a lifetime offers impeccable service and storytelling from engaging Hosts, regionally inspired cuisine, and a front row seat to one of the most spectacular settings on the planet.</p>
			<p>Enhance your onboard experience with <strong>SilverLeaf Plus</strong>, which includes all the benefits of the exceptional SilverLeaf Service, plus exclusive access to a newly renovated lounge car. Featuring signature cocktails, the lounge car offers additional space indoors to relax and soak in the scenery as it passes you by, as well as a small outdoor viewing area. Additionally, enjoy an elevated dining experience with an additional course during select meals, and premium alcoholic beverages.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/01/article/spotlight-02.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					Onboard SilverLeaf Service*
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<h4>Route Highlights</h4>
			<p>The&nbsp;Rockies to the Red Rocks&nbsp;route showcases scenic views that are unique to the Southwest United States, as it travels between Colorado and Utah with options of traveling westbound or eastbound.&nbsp;</p>
			
			<div class="videoWrapper" style="padding-bottom: 45%;">
				<figure>
					<iframe width="853" height="480" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/zj8wSOBQXlM?rel=0&amp;showinfo=0" frameborder="0" allow="autoplay; encrypted-media" allowfullscreen></iframe>
				</figure>
			</div>
			
			<br/>
			<br/>
			
			<p>Between Denver and Glenwood Springs, guests will journey alongside the Colorado River and through a series of canyons. Highlights include the Big 10 curve,&nbsp;an engineering marvel built in&nbsp;the&nbsp;early 1900s,&nbsp;to enable trains to slowly gain elevation before reaching the Continental Divide; and a series of canyons offering rugged scenery of steep rock walls, including Byers Canyon and Red Canyon. The canyons offer opportunities to view roaming wildlife, including bighorn sheep, mountain lions, deer, marmots and birds.&nbsp;</p>
			<p>The journey between Glenwood Springs and Moab offers a variety of scenery from chromatic deserts, to red sandstone formations that twist through the bright blue sky. Glide over the great divide and take in the spectacular De Beque Canyon, Mount Garfield and glimpses of Arches National Park. Witness Mount Lincoln, the eighth-highest peak in the Rocky Mountains, on this journey of a lifetime.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/01/article/spotlight-03.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					Canyonlands National Park, Moab.  Credit: Discover Moab
				</figcaption>
			</figure>
			
			<h4>Further Exploration</h4>
			<p>Rocky Mountaineer is working with local hotels and tour operators to curate custom vacation packages that feature tours, activities, and stays in Denver and Moab, so guests can experience even more of the region. The route will operate from August to October 2021 and the two-day rail journeys, including a one-night hotel accommodation in Glenwood Springs. Contact your Ensemble Travel Advisor to secure a booking with only a $25 USD refundable deposit, with flexible booking terms.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/01/article/spotlight-04.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					Mount Robson in the Canadian Rocky Mountains*
				</figcaption>
			</figure>
			
			<h4>Western Canadian Routes</h4>
			<p>For those looking for views of snowy mountains and sparkling glacial lakes, join Rocky Mountaineer onboard a journey through the Canadian Rockies. Operating from April to October 2021, Rocky Mountaineer offers three distinctive rail routes in Canada connecting the Pacific city of Vancouver with the Canadian Rocky Mountains. These routes offer two onboard service choices: SilverLeaf and GoldLeaf Service.</p>
			<p>The two-day <strong>First Passage to the West</strong> route rolls along the historic tracks of Canada&rsquo;s first coast-to-coast railway between Vancouver and either Banff or Lake Louise in the Canadian Rockies. <strong>Journey through the Clouds</strong> travels between Vancouver and Jasper, with two days spent traversing some of the most remote landscapes in Canada, with scenery and wildlife largely untouched by humans. For those wanting to delve further into Western Canada&rsquo;s history and diverse landscapes, the three-day <strong>Rainforest to Gold Rush</strong> route takes a northerly path between Vancouver and Jasper, uncovering the stories of those seeking their fortune. Can&rsquo;t choose? Remember, each train journey can be travelled in either direction, or you can combine two of the Canadian rail routes for a Circle Journey.</p>
			<p>Simply put, Rocky Mountaineer is a must-do travel experience that offers an unparalleled journey through some of the world&rsquo;s most sought-after travel destinations.</p>
			
			<br/>
			
			<p>Contact your Ensemble Travel Advisor to secure a 2021 booking on any of Rocky Mountaineer&rsquo;s routes. For a limited time, book with the enhanced flexibility you need including a risk-free deposit, two free date changes, name changes and more.</p>
			<p>*Images of the interior and exterior of the train are from Rocky Mountaineer&rsquo;s Canadian route.</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/01/hero/spotlight.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Ride the Rails through North America's Rocky Mountains in 2021]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Destination Spotlight]]></hero_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/01/article/spotlight.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Ride the Rails through North America's Rocky Mountains in 2021]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Destination Spotlight]]></article_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<email_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/01/email/spotlight.jpg</email_src>
		
		<tile_color>C8232C</tile_color> <!--Spotlight:C8232C, Insider:FA6900, Travel Style:00B9F2 -->
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="north-america"><![CDATA[north-america]]></tag>
			<tag slug="train"><![CDATA[train]]></tag>
			<tag slug="adventure"><![CDATA[adventure]]></tag>
			<tag slug="education-learning"><![CDATA[education-learning]]></tag>
			<tag slug="family-vacations"><![CDATA[family-vacations]]></tag>
			<tag slug="sports-outdoors"><![CDATA[sports-outdoors]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>
