<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2101">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[style]]></dir_name> <!-- spotlight, style, insider -->
		<pub_date><![CDATA[January 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- January = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[01]]></dir_month>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Celebrity Cruises]]></author>
		<translator><![CDATA[]]></translator>
		
		<title><![CDATA[So Much More Than a Suite]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[
			Take your vacation experience to new heights - only on Celebrity.
		]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Welcome to The Retreat&reg; &mdash; the ultimate in luxury vacation experiences &mdash; only on Celebrity. The Retreat isn&rsquo;t a place. It isn&rsquo;t an amenity. It isn&rsquo;t a service. It&rsquo;s all of that and more. The Retreat is an unparalleled vacation experience that includes every stunning suite, a private restaurant, an exclusive lounge, and a sundeck&cross; that rivals any high-end resort. In fact, we&rsquo;re the only premium cruise line to offer all this to every guest of The Retreat aboard any of our award-winning ships.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>As a guest of The Retreat, you&rsquo;ll also enjoy a long list of thoughtfully curated amenities, starting with five perks that are now Always IncludedSM&mdash;a shore excursion credit, premium drinks, streaming Wi-Fi, tips, and an onboard credit to spend any way you like.&cross; Paired with a dedicated team of professionals who ensure you have everything you need for an unforgettable vacation, The Retreat is a luxurious way for you to discover the world.</p>
			
			<h4>Design by Kelly Hoppen</h4>
			<p>Design is extremely important in everything we do. So, in creating The Retreat venues, we collaborated with acclaimed designer Kelly Hoppen, MBE. With 40 years of experience at the forefront of the design industry, she&rsquo;s one of the most sought-after interior designers in the world. Kelly&rsquo;s globally renowned and ever-evolving style is underpinned by a subtle coordinated fusion of East meets West, featuring clean lines and neutral tones blended with charming warmth and sumptuous opulence.</p>
			<p>Kelly brought her extraordinary talent and fresh perspective to the project to create distinct spaces that completely surround you in luxury. From the high-end resort venues like The Retreat Lounge, Sundeck, and Pool to the intimate and inviting spaces including Luminae restaurant and the luxurious collection of suites, Kelly has created venues and suites for The Retreat on our Celebrity Edge Series ships &mdash; and across the fleet as part of the Celebrity Revolution &mdash; that stand apart from any other spaces at sea.</p>
			
			<h4>The Celebrity Revolution</h4>
			<p>Celebrity Edge&reg; introduced The Retreat to the world, and now we&rsquo;re taking that experience to the rest of our fleet as part of our $500 million Celebrity RevolutionSM. Every ship will be updated with the addition of The Retreat Sundeck, the redesign of The Retreat Lounge, and reimagined suite accommodation interiors. So, every ship will offer the same extraordinary vacation experiences &mdash; found only on Celebrity.</p>
			<p>The Retreat takes our passion for fine dining to delicious new heights at Luminae, the private restaurant for all guests of The Retreat. Open for breakfast, lunch, and dinner, the space features a boldly elegant design as distinctive as its cuisine. Not only is the restaurant exclusive, but so are its menus. Crafted by our Michelin-starred chef, the modern, eclectic cuisine served in Luminae is not available anywhere else on board, and the menu includes complimentary signature dishes from Chef Daniel Boulud, our Global Culinary Brand Ambassador.</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/01/article/style-01.jpg">
			</figure>
			
			<h4>The Retreat Sundeck</h4>
			<p>The Retreat Sundeck&cross; is a luxurious outdoor area that rivals any high-end resort. Designed by Kelly Hoppen, MBE, this spacious lounge area makes it easy to unplug with plush, stylish furniture and an inviting pool on Celebrity Edge&reg; Series ships. Dedicated attendants are at your service to make sure your every whim is tended to &mdash; cocktails, fresh towels, refreshing treats, you name it. This is a private escape within your escape, and it&rsquo;s available for all guests of The Retreat.</p>
			<p>&cross;The Retreat Sundeck is available on all Edge&reg; Series ships and all ships that have been revolutionized.</p>
			<p>The Retreat Lounge&sext;, designed by Kelly Hoppen, MBE, is available 24/7, and inside you&rsquo;ll discover a warm and inviting space. Here, you&rsquo;ll have access to an exclusive concierge who&rsquo;ll make any arrangements you need &mdash; on board and off. You&rsquo;ll also enjoy complimentary beverages, gourmet bites, and a comfortable place to read the latest best-seller, catch up on current events, watch the big game, or just kick your feet up and relax.</p>
			<p>&sext;The Retreat Lounge is referred to as Michael&rsquo;s Club on all non-revolutionized ships.</p>
			
			<h4>The Accommodations &mdash; Suites</h4>
			<p>Every suite surrounds you in luxury with expansive, stunningly designed spaces that feature floor-to-ceiling sliding doors and windows. When you enter, you&rsquo;ll discover a welcome bottle of champagne. That&rsquo;s just the start of your in-suite culinary delights. Throughout your vacation, your butler will deliver savories every afternoon. Enjoy priority seating for specialty restaurants (your butler can make every reservation for you, of course), and 24-hour complimentary room service with a premium room service menu. You&rsquo;ll enjoy premium drinks, so you can enjoy your favorite beverages throughout the ship, two complimentary bottles of spirits (of your choice), and mixers to enjoy cocktails in your suite. Your mini bar is stocked daily with complimentary beer, soft drinks, and water.&dagger; Even your wine will taste better served in the Riedel&reg; crystal glassware in your suite. Every delicious bite has been carefully thought through&mdash;right down to the custom chocolates we put on your pillow every night at turndown.</p>
			<p>We want you to feel right at home, so you&rsquo;ll find everything you need to relax in total comfort, from the premium furniture and loungers to our exclusive eXhaleTM bedding, featuring a luxurious Cashmere Mattress, to plush Frette robes, towels, and slippers. Even your bath amenities are of the highest quality to wrap you in luxury from head to toe. You&rsquo;ll be pleasantly surprised with every thoughtful detail you&rsquo;ll discover.</p>
			<p>You can stay connected throughout the ship with complimentary, streaming Wi-Fi. In your suite, you&rsquo;ll be entertained with large, flat-screen TVs and reserved seating for theater shows. Feel like sightseeing from your veranda? We have high quality binoculars for you to use. Need a bag to take your belongings with you to The Retreat Sundeck (or anywhere else you may be going)? For your convenience, we&rsquo;ll give you an exclusive tote bag custom designed by Nate Berkus.&ddagger; All the thoughtful details and luxurious elements create a space so comfortable and inviting, you may find it difficult to leave.</p>
			<p>There&rsquo;s nothing we love more than taking our vacation experiences to new heights, so the work we put into creating The Retreat experience was our pleasure &mdash; because we know it will be yours, as well.</p>
			<p>&dagger; Celebrity Suites and Sky Suites: additional fees apply for mini bar items.</p>
			<p>&ddagger; Available on Celebrity Edge Series ships only.</p>
			<p>Image Credit: Celebrity Cruises</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/01/hero/style.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[So Much More Than a Suite]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Travel Style]]></hero_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/01/article/style.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[So Much More Than a Suite]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Travel Style]]></article_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<email_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/01/email/style.jpg</email_src>
		
		<tile_color>00B9F2</tile_color> <!--Spotlight:C8232C, Insider:FA6900, Travel Style:00B9F2 -->
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="ocean-cruising"><![CDATA[ocean-cruising]]></tag>
			<tag slug="beach-sun"><![CDATA[beach-sun]]></tag>
			<tag slug="family-vacations"><![CDATA[family-vacations]]></tag>
			<tag slug="honeymoons"><![CDATA[honeymoons]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>
