<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>

	<!-- BEGIN: 2002 gow -->
	<article date="2002" id="01">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[February 2020]]></pub_date>
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[02]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[01]]></id_article>

		<author><![CDATA[Goway]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[gwa]]></id_supplier>

		<title><![CDATA[Five Thai Dishes to Eat in Bangkok While on a Thailand Vacation]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Goway]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Few cities reward a food odyssey more than Bangkok, where you can find new culinary delights at seemingly every food stall and restaurant in the city. A trip through the whole of Thailand is immensely rewarding if you have the time and money, but you don&rsquo;t need to leave the capital to experience the might of Thai cuisine.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-01-01.jpg">
			<figure>

			<h2>What are the best foods in Bangkok?</h2>
			<h3>Pad Thai</h3>

			<p>Pad Thai is probably the most popular Thai dish for westerners and I&rsquo;d be remiss if I didn&rsquo;t mention it off the top. It&rsquo;s also among the most popular street food dishes, and many Bangkokians feast on it for quick lunches during the work week. If you aren&rsquo;t already familiar with Pad Thai from fusion joints back home, it&rsquo;s a dish made from long rice noodles stir-fried with shrimp, bean sprouts, tofu, egg, chilies, peanuts, and fish sauce, and served alongside lime halves that you can use to flavour the noodles further. There are other variations to the dish, such as substituting chicken for shrimp for those who dislike shellfish, or serving it all wrapped up inside an egg, but the essentials are always the same. It&rsquo;s a hard dish to dislike, as the ingredients combine to create savoury flavours that are very addictive.</p>

			<p>You&rsquo;ll find Pad Thai on almost every single menu in Bangkok, but if you want the real deal, head to one of the popular street food areas, either the Sukhumvit Soi 38 Food Market (although many of these stalls have relocated due to construction) or Yaowarat Street (Chinatown), and buy it from a stall. If you&rsquo;re wanting to try the most famous Pad Thai in the city, and arguably the world, head to Thip Samai, just across the water from Wat Saket. The restaurant serves a variety of Pad Thais, including a popular style that&rsquo;s wrapped up in an egg omelette. The place has a Michelin Star, so expect lineups, although the chefs are good at turning around dishes as fast as possible.</p>

			<h3>Tom Yum Goong</h3>
			<p>Tom Yum Goong is so much more than simply Thai sour soup. And while Tom Yum Goong is on a lot of menus in North American Asian restaurants, these bland versions are pale imitations of the glories of the soup you&rsquo;ll find in Bangkok. Tom Yum Goong is a spicy, savoury, somewhat sour soup made from a broth infused with lemongrass, kaffir lime leaves, fish sauce, lime juice, chilies, and shrimp. Coconut or evaporated milk is often added to thicken the stock and add a creamy texture, but if you&rsquo;re lucky, the shrimp being used to make the dish will be fatty enough to add the creamy flavour itself. There are also variations of the soup made with pork instead of shrimp, so again, if you don&rsquo;t like seafood, you&rsquo;ll still find a Tom Yum Goong for you.</p>

			<p>You&rsquo;ll find Tom Yum Goong at both high-end restaurants and food stalls. It can be served in modest styrofoam bowls or large metal dishes set atop a flame to keep the soup consistently warm like a Chinese hotpot. If you&rsquo;re looking for specific restaurant suggestions, seek out Krua Apsorn near the Democracy Monument or one of the many Sombon Seafood locations. But you&rsquo;ll also find it at stalls all over the city, including the popular stall Tom Yum Goong Banglamphu, located a few blocks away from the party mecca of Khao San Road.</p>

			<h3>Som Tam</h3>
			<p>No Thai dish is as addictive or dangerous as Som Tam. I exaggerate, but this spicy papaya salad is so hot and delicious that you&rsquo;ll keep chowing it down even as the spice wreaks havoc on your mouth and stomach. But don&rsquo;t be daunted. Not all variations of Som Tam are blisteringly hot, so even if you aren&rsquo;t one for spice, odds are you&rsquo;ll find a Som Tam to enjoy. Som Tam is made from papaya that is thinly sliced by hand, or on a mandolin, and then crushed under a mortar and pestle to soften it up and combine it with the other ingredients, including tomatoes, long beans, chilies, garlic, fish sauce, and lime juice. Although the salad originated in Laos, it&rsquo;s popular in Thailand and has become a fixture of its cuisine.</p>

			<p>Like all of these dishes I&rsquo;ve mentioned, you can find Som Tam on most menus while on Thailand travel. If you&rsquo;re looking for specific suggestions, seek out Somtum Der Saladaeng just to the southwest of Lumphini Park or Som Tam Jay So a few blocks further west. Both of these restaurants are renowned for their salads as well as their other classic Thai dishes.</p>

			<h3>Thai Curry</h3>
			<p>Curry? That&rsquo;s it? I know&mdash;curry in and of itself is not a dish, but can describe an entire method of cooking in addition to the core ingredients of so many Asian dishes. But what I&rsquo;m specifically referring to are the core types of Thai curry: Yellow, Red, Green, and Massaman. At many restaurants in Bangkok (and at good Thai restaurants in North America), you&rsquo;ll have the option to choose between these different types. They&rsquo;re all delicious but they do vary.</p>

			<p>Massaman curry is the mildest of the Thai curries, and often uses red meats like beef, lamb, and mutton. If you&rsquo;re not one for spice, Massaman is a good choice. Yellow is spicier than Massaman, but not overwhelming, and often combined with coconut to create a great, creamy flavour. It gets its colour from turmeric that&rsquo;s added to the dish and is often served over rice or in soup dishes. Red curry is a bit spicier than yellow curry and uses chili powder and red curry paste to give its colour. Green curry is the spiciest of the Thai curries and gets its colour from Kaffir lime leaves, basil, and the fresh green chilies worked into it. It&rsquo;s also cooked with coconut milk, so green curry is a great option if you want both spice and sweetness.</p>

			<p>Curry is so common that you&rsquo;ll find it on menus in Bangkok. The aforementioned Krua Apsorn has good curries, as do spots like the aptly named Smooth Curry and Queen of Curry. It&rsquo;s important to point out that in North American restaurants, the levels of spiciness are often reversed, with red curry being the spiciest and green the least spicy. So if you&rsquo;re familiar with Thai curry from North American restaurants, you may need to readjust what you order in Bangkok.</p>

			<h3>Boat Noodles</h3>
			<p>Boat Noodles or Kway Teow Rua are quintessentially Bangkokian dishes and you won&rsquo;t find anything resembling them in restaurants in North America. These small bowls of slow-cooked broth, meat, dried herbs, and noodles get their name from the boats that used to serve them along the canals and rivers of the city in decades past. They&rsquo;re typically made with pork or beef and come with a lot of broth that infuses the noodles with flavour.</p>

			<p>Today, they&rsquo;re popular street food items and can be had for shockingly low prices that are equivalent to around 40 cents. Of course, the bowls are very small, so you may want to order a few if you&rsquo;re especially hungry. You&rsquo;ll find a lot of good restaurants and stalls selling Boat Noodles around Victory Monument. But any of the aforementioned hotspots for street food will have stalls selling them as well.</p>

			<p>Please contact your travel advisor to learn more.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-01-02.jpg">
			<figure>
		]]></body>

		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/hero/advertorial-01.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Five Thai Dishes to Eat in Bangkok While on a Thailand Vacation]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Goway]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-01.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Five Thai Dishes to Eat in Bangkok While on a Thailand Vacation]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Goway]]></article_credit>

		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>

	</article>
	<!-- END: 2002 gow -->

	<!-- BEGIN: 2002 hal -->
	<article date="2002" id="02">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[February 2020]]></pub_date>
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[02]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[02]]></id_article>

		<author><![CDATA[Holland America Line]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[hal]]></id_supplier>

		<title><![CDATA[Holland America Line, We Are Alaska]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Holland America Line]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Experience the beauty of Alaska as you wander ashore to explore towns alive with history and rich in native culture.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-02-01.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h2>We are Alaska</h2>
					<p>When Holland America Line says they are Alaska, it&rsquo;s more than a slogan. They have been taking guests to the Great Land for more than 70 years, before Alaska was a state. Back in 1947, word of Alaska&rsquo;s soaring glaciers, snowcapped mountains and incredible wildlife was just starting to spread. And today, Holland America Line continues to set the standard in providing the ultimate Alaska experience.</p>

					<p>Slip through quiet fjords lined by pristine forest, learn the legacy of the Haida and Tsimshain in historic Ketchikan or hop on a helicopter in Juneau and hover over the mighty Mendenhall Glacier. Do all of this in just one week. In two, you can see even more&mdash;from bear-watching on Kodiak Island and cruising the Inside Pasage to fishing for halibut in Homer and paying homage to mighty Hubbard, the largest tidewater glacier in North America.</p>

					<p>There&rsquo;s nowhere else on Earth quite like Alaska and no better way to see it than on board one of Holland America Line&rsquo;s perfectly sized ships. The ideal size for exploring Alaska, their ships are designed to get you closer to each wonder, from the breathtaking Inside Passage to awe-inspiring Glacier Bay National Park.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-02-02.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h2>At Sea</h2>
					<p>On an Alaska cruise, Holland America Line offers unrivaled experiences in food, wine and spirits as part of every voyage. Whether dining in their specialty restaurants or the exceptional Dining Room, guests can enjoy a variety of exclusive offerings that showcase the flavors of Alaska and the Pacific Northwest. And, only Holland America Line has a Culinary Council<sup>&reg;</sup> of seven world-renowned chefs &mdash; plus experts in wine and spirits &mdash; who design their onboard dining experiences.</p>

					<p>Also on board, you&rsquo;ll enjoy Holland America Line exclusives, including regionally inspired cuisine and locally themed entertainment and activities, such as Alaska in Concert, a thrilling live program set against a backdrop of mesmerizing scenes from BBC Earth&rsquo;s Wild Alaska as well as informative discussions with Explorations Central Guides and your onboard naturalist. </p>

					<p>Sailing out of Vancouver in 2020, Koningsdam will make her Alaska debut. This Holland America Line ship offers the popular hallmarks of their perfectly sized ships, plus some unique Pinnacle-class ship exclusives including innovative new dining venues Nami Sushi and the award-winning, Rudi&rsquo;s Sel de Mer, as well as Music Walk<sup>&reg;</sup>. It also features dedicated single staterooms and family staterooms, with accommodations for up to five guests.</p>

					<p>Also on Koningsdam is the wine-blending venue, BLEND. It has a tasting table that accommodates 10 guests, who can create their own blend from a selection of five barrels of single-vineyard red wine. In addition to participating in the blending process, you&rsquo;ll also learn about wine from the ship&rsquo;s wine expert, who leads the blending session.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-02-03.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h2>Denali and the Yukon</h2>
					<p>Holland America Line gives you two ways to experience Alaska&rsquo;s incredible interior. Embark on a voyage where adventure waits at every turn with the only cruise company that combines the wonders of an Alaska cruise and the beauty of Denali with the rich history and majesty of the Yukon Territory. Extend your exploration and experience fascinating Gold Rush history and wild Yukon scenery. As you wander through frontier towns and travel through unspoiled wilderness, you&rsquo;ll come face to face with the must-see and seldom-seen treasures of the Yukon, delivered as only the experts at Holland America Line can. Also, on all of their Yukon + Denali Land+Sea Journeys you&rsquo;ll be accompanied by a professional Journey Host on the land portion, who will provide in-depth insights on the places you visit and make sure everything goes smoothly.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-02-04.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h2>Alaska In-Depth</h2>
					<p>If you want to dive even deeper into the culture and wildlife of Alaska, Holland America Line offers their Alaska EXC In-Depth&trade; Voyages. These 18 to 21-day journeys combine destination-intensive itineraries with opportunities for more immersive exploration that take you deeper into the culture and wildlife of the Great Land. At the heart of each voyage are six themes that let you customize your exploration based on your interests and passions. Embark on a thrilling photo safari to the Mendenhall Glacier. Let a local lead you on an insider&rsquo;s tour of Juneau&rsquo;s culinary scene. Thread through narrow inlets in a water-jet powered boat to observe sea otters, whales, brown bears and more in their natural habitat. No matter what you choose, you&rsquo;ll come away with an unforgettable new perspective on Alaska.</p>

					<p>With their spacious ships, exclusive onboard entertainment, unrivaled access and unmatched experience and insider knowledge, Holland America Line are the Alaska experts. So, if you&rsquo;re going to see Alaska, see all of it alongside those who know it best.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-02-05.jpg">
				<figcaption></figcaption>
			</figure>
		]]></body>

		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/hero/advertorial-02.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Holland America Line, We Are Alaska]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Holland America Line]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-02.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Holland America Line, We Are Alaska]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Holland America Line]]></article_credit>

		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>

	</article>
	<!-- END: 2002 hal -->

	<!-- END: 2002 uni -->
	<article date="2002" id="03">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[February 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- Mmm = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[02]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[03]]></id_article>

		<author><![CDATA[Uniworld]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[uni]]></id_supplier>

		<title><![CDATA[Venture Off The Beaten Path]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Uniworld]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			The world is full of wonderful places to explore and Uniworld is expanding their map every year. From the diverse flora and fauna of Peru, the imperial monuments of China and the vibrant villages Vietnam and Cambodia, to the larger-than-life history of Egypt and the sacred beauty of India, explore exotic destinations in unsurpassed luxury with Uniworld
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-03-01.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<p>Uniworld is venturing into South America for the first time with some exciting itineraries in Peru. They&rsquo;ve chartered a beautiful ship for these voyages, the luxurious and sustainably built Aria Amazon. Each of its 16 guestrooms has floor-to-ceiling windows, designed to immerse you in the breathtaking nature of the Pacaya-Samira National Reserve. Known as &ldquo;the Jungle of Mirrors&rdquo;, this reserve is home to diverse wildlife, exceptional landscapes and vibrant native culture.</p>

					<p>Uniworld has enhanced this trip into the Peruvian Amazon with the addition of trips to Machu Picchu, The Sacred Valley, Cusco and Lima for their <strong>Peruvian Amazon &amp; Machu Picchu Exploration</strong>. From bucket-list sights to captivating towns, these visits are the perfect way to round out a cruise through the Peruvian Amazon.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-03-02.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<p>From man-made marvels to stunning displays of natural beauty, China offers wonderous contrasts just waiting to be uncovered. Immerse yourself in its ancient monuments, futuristic cities, tiny villages and tranquil gardens. Trek the great wall, witness awe-inducing displays of acrobatics and enjoy feasts of crispy duck and juicy dumplings.</p>

					<p>On <strong>Highlights of China &amp; the Yangtze</strong>, explore China&rsquo;s ancient and fascinating history with trips to the Forbidden City, the Great Wall and Xi&rsquo;an&rsquo;s terracotta army. Or head to the Himalayas and explore Jokhang Temple, Potala Palace and the Sera Monastery on <strong>China, Tibet &amp; the Yangtze</strong>. Dive further into your adventures in China with more time in Shanghai and on the Yangtze, plus a stay in the &ldquo;Panda City&rdquo; of Chengdu, with <strong>Grand China &amp; the Yangtze.</strong></p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-03-03.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<p>Beaming with colorful floating villages and grand temples, Vietnam and Cambodia are equal parts compelling and complex. From the towering islands of Ha Long Bay to the ancient and inspiring Angkor Wat, there is no shortage of incredible sights and experiences on Uniworld&rsquo;s <strong>Timeless Wonders of Vietnam, Cambodia and the Mekong</strong> itinerary and its Hanoi extension.</p>

					<p>Endlessly exciting, Vietnam and Cambodia are richly multifaceted. Whether you begin your journey in bustling Ho Chi Minh or eclectic Siem Reap, you&rsquo;ll experience serene rivers, charming islands, centuries-old architectural masterpieces and so much more.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-03-04.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<p>Explore the ancient wonders of Egypt&rsquo;s sun-drenched landscape on the same route traversed by pharaohs and queens thousands of years ago. On <strong>Splendors of Egypt &amp; the Nile</strong>, dive into the fascinating history of Egypt with trips to the towering ruins of the Temple of Karnak, the Valley of the Kings and the pyramids of Giza.</p>

					<p>The glittering Nile River brings you through wide-open stretches of golden sands and grassy plains, spotted with the occasional ancient temple, for a cruise that is utterly relaxing, yet a grand adventure at the same time.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-03-05.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<p>Two completely different, but equally enticing voyages in India promise to capture your senses and inspire wonder. The first, <strong>India&rsquo;s Golden Triangle &amp; the Sacred Ganges</strong>, begins with five nights in ultra-luxurious hotels as you spend your days visiting such incredible sights as Jaipur&rsquo;s Pink City and witnessing the sun rise and set over the Taj Mahal. <strong>ME to WE &amp; the Sacred Ganges</strong> takes a more immersive route, bringing you to small farming villages, where you&rsquo;ll join community building projects and discover daily life in rural India.</p>

				<p>Both itineraries continue on to a cruise along the Ganges River, taking you to beautiful monuments, fascinating cultural sights and colorful villages. Each sailing includes Uniworld&rsquo;s <strong>Wellness Program</strong>, led by a certified and resident yogi, which celebrates the destinations ancient tradition of yoga with daily sessions focusing on different forms of the art, health classes and an accompanying wellness menu.</p>
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

		]]></body>

		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/hero/advertorial-03.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Venture Off The Beaten Path]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Uniworld]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-03.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Venture Off The Beaten Path]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Uniworld]]></article_credit>

		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>

	</article>
	<!-- END: 2002 uni -->

	<!-- BEGIN: 2002 gad -->
	<article date="2002" id="04">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[February 2020]]></pub_date>
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[02]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[04]]></id_article>

		<author><![CDATA[G Adventures]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[gad]]></id_supplier>

		<title><![CDATA[We&rsquo;re All Family.]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[G Adventures]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Your family can discover the world together on the National Geographic Family Journeys with G Adventures collection of trips.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>National Geographic Family Journeys with G Adventures is a line of trips for adventure-loving families in search of a meaningful way to discover the world together. These itineraries are specially designed so travelers ages seven and up can explore a destination&rsquo;s rich and diverse characteristics. Each itinerary features unique, interactive activities inspired by National Geographic's expertise in photography and storytelling, wildlife, culture, history, and geography to encourage kids and adults alike to connect with the world around them. Families will enjoy enlightening experiences, the freedom to explore, quality time together&mdash;and they&rsquo;ll return home with a renewed sense of wonder.</p>
		]]></body>

		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/hero/advertorial-04.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[We&rsquo;re All Family.]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[G Adventures]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-04.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[We&rsquo;re All Family.]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[G Adventures]]></article_credit>

		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>

	</article>
	<!-- END: 2002 gad -->

	<!-- BEGIN: 2002 unc -->
	<article date="2002" id="05">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[February 2020]]></pub_date>
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[02]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[05]]></id_article>

		<author><![CDATA[UnCruise<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[unc]]></id_supplier>

		<title><![CDATA[Live your #travelgoals in Alaska with UnCruise Adventures]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[UnCruise<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Adventure is our name and it&rsquo;s our passion. Uncover playgrounds that offer the richest, wildest experiences by hike, paddle, and with locals.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>Step into tiny worlds and soak in big skies in Alaska&rsquo;s green playground. Let painted mountains set the stage for your explorations. Within our routes we're ready to turn, pause, and seize opportunity. Linger for whale sprays and bow riding dolphins. How will you define adventure?</p>

			<p><strong>Active</strong> [ak&middot;tiv] Mountain-goat scrambles, hours-long kayaking, slow and inquisitive snorkeling... Excursions are as hard-charging or as slow-paced as you like.</p>

			<p><strong>Bushwhacking</strong> [bush&middot;wak&middot;ing] No trail; To attempt a wild and woolly hike in Alaska that typically involves deer trails, bear scat, muskeg, and climbing over logs and through brush.</p>

			<p><strong>Connection</strong> [kuh&middot;nek&middot;shuhn] Meet your people. Small ships acquaint you with like-minded travelers and places that tug your heartstrings. Bonds are hard to define but easy to spot hugging it out at the end&mdash;from co-explorers to friends for life.</p>

			<p><strong>Inclusive</strong> [in&middot;kloo&middot;siv] Excursions, adventure equipment, transfers, baggage handling, and yes, all food and beverages (alcohol too), even heart-tugging photos from your trip are covered in the fare. Truly no hidden costs.</p>

			<p><strong>Small ships</strong> [smaal ships] Laid back; 22-86 guests. That's it. You get to know your travel comrades quickly, and yet there's always a quiet corner or empty space on the bow to scout for wildlife and take it all in.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-05-01.jpg">
			<figure><br>

			<p>Travel <strong>Alaska's Glacier Country</strong>. With a full day in Glacier Bay National Park, explore islands, glaciers, and forests. Bushwhack in the Tongass National Forest. Kayak in remote inlets eyes peeled for eagles, sea otters, harbor seals, sea lions, and seabirds.</p>

			<p>Traverse <strong>Northern Passages &amp; Glacier Bay</strong> where you&rsquo;ll whale watch and hike the Tongass and Glacier Bay National Park like Alaskans. Skiff, kayak, and paddle board through fjords and inlets.</p>

			<p>Or why not double the fun spending two weeks in Southeast Alaska on <strong>Fjords of Alaska Cruise&mdash;Ultimate Expedition</strong>? Experience everything you crave about Alaska&mdash;birding, beachcombing, and bushwhacking&mdash;with more time to kayak and hike in this powerful place. Take in Tlingit culture at Kiksetti Totem Park and Chief Shakes Tribal House. Plus more glaciers and a day in Glacier Bay National Park.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-05-02.jpg">
			<figure><br>

			<p><strong>What are guests saying about Alaska with UnCruise?</strong><br>
			<em>&ldquo;Exceptional! Excellent! Can't find the words&hellip; Seeing the &lsquo;Unseen&rsquo; of my lifetime.&rdquo;</em> - L Gorski, Grosse Pointe, MI (Alaska, 2019)</p>

			<p><em>&ldquo;(The highlights were) being the only boat to experience this place during our visit. Watching a glacier calve from 1/4 mile from its face... and listening too! Kayaking to the back of one of the bays, alone, closing your eyes...with nature at your fingertips.&rdquo;</em> - A Stroppini, Reno, NV (Alaska, 2019)</p>

			<p><strong>Explore Alaska with UnCruise Adventures</strong><br>
			Ask your travel advisor about current promotions.</p>
		]]></body>

		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/hero/advertorial-05.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Live your #travelgoals in Alaska by small ship with UnCruise Adventures]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[UnCruise<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/advertorial-05.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Live your #travelgoals in Alaska by small ship with UnCruise Adventures]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[UnCruise<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></article_credit>

		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>

	</article>
	<!-- END: 2002 unc -->

</root>