<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>

	<!-- BEGIN: 2002 cel -->
	<article date="2002" id="01">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[recipe]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[February 2020]]></pub_date>
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[02]]></dir_month>
		<id_recipe><![CDATA[01]]></id_recipe>
​
		<tab_class><![CDATA[active]]></tab_class>
​
		<author><![CDATA[Celebrity Cruises<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[cel]]></id_supplier>
		<translator><![CDATA[]]></translator>
		<cookbook><![CDATA[]]></cookbook>
​
		<title><![CDATA[Grilled Ribeye Steak Rutabaga Puree, Roasted Root Vegetables, Brown Butter Bearnaise Sauce]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[The exclusive restaurant for Suite Class.]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Exclusive and cutting edge, the globally inspired menus at Luminae are not available in any other restaurant on board. And, you&rsquo;ll see each one only once&mdash;because every day features a fresh, new menu.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[]]></body>
​
		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Ribeye Cooking Recipe]]></title>
			<ingredients><![CDATA[
				<h4>Ingredients</h4> <!-- Ingrédients -->
				<p>Yield: 1 Portions<p>
				<ul>
					<li>1 ea. Beef Ribeye Steak, 10 oz.</li>
					<li>1 oz. Butter, cubes</li>
					<li>2 ea. Thyme Sprig</li>
					<li>1 ea. Garlic Cloves, crushed</li>
					<li>2 tbs. EVOO</li>
					<li>Salt and Ground Black Peppercorn to taste</li>
				</ul>
			]]></ingredients>
​
			<prep><![CDATA[
				<h4>Preparation</h4> <!-- Préparation -->
				<ol>
					<li>Day before remove bones from ribeye and trimming some of the fat.</li>
					<li>Cut by half lengthwise, and thigh wrap in plastic film to with cylinder shape. Keep into the cooler overnight.</li>
					<li>Cut into10 oz. slice per portion.</li>
					<li>When order come in.</li>
					<li>Heat a non-stick pan to smoking point.</li>
					<li>Add EVOO and sear the ribeye all around until golden color.</li>
					<li>Then add butter, thyme and garlic to the pan and when butter melt, continuously baste the ribeye with the aromatic butter until desired cooking temperature if cooking point is below medium.</li>
					<li>If order is above medium finish to cooked into the oven at 170 C until desired cooking point.</li>
					<li>Remove ribeye from the hot pan and transfer to a sheet pan. Reserve and rested for 5 to 8 minutes.</li>
					<li>Just before plating, place the ribeye into the oven at 160 C for 2 minutes.</li>
					<li>Then cut the end cuts and plated.</li>
				</ol>
			]]></prep>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Rutabaga Puree Recipe]]></title>
			<ingredients><![CDATA[
				<h4>Ingredients</h4> <!-- Ingrédients -->
				<ul>
					<li>3 ea. Garlic Cloves, finely chopped</li>
					<li>4 oz. White Onions, finely chopped</li>
					<li>1,2 lb. Rutabaga, peeled and cut into small dices</li>
					<li>1 ea. Bay Leave</li>
					<li>3 ea. Thyme Sprig</li>
					<li>1 qt. Chicken Stock</li>
					<li>3 oz. Butter</li>
					<li>3 oz. Butter, cold cubes (for emulsify the puree)</li>
					<li>Salt and Ground Black Peppercorn to tasted</li>
				</ul>
			]]></ingredients>
​
			<prep><![CDATA[
				<h4>Preparation</h4> <!-- Préparation -->
				<ol>
					<li>Place 3 oz. of butter over a rondo.</li>
					<li>Heat and melt the butter; add garlic, bay leave, onions and thyme.</li>
					<li>Cooked until onions are well tender and translucent.</li>
					<li>Add rutabaga and stir well.</li>
					<li>Add chicken stock, bring to a boil.</li>
					<li>Coked until rutabaga is totally over cooked.</li>
					<li>Remove bay leave and thyme stems and discard.</li>
					<li>Place cooked rutabaga and rest of liquid into the Vitaprep.</li>
					<li>Blend to puree, add butter cubes at the same time you blend on high speed.</li>
					<li>Adjust seasoning and pass thru the chinois.</li>
					<li>Cool down quickly and reserve into the cooler until needed.</li>
				</ol>
			]]></prep>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Brown Butter Recipe]]></title>
			<ingredients><![CDATA[
				<h4>Ingredients</h4> <!-- Ingrédients -->
				<p>Yield: 30 Portions<p>
				<ul>
					<li>2 lbs. Butter</li>
				</ul>
			]]></ingredients>
​
			<prep><![CDATA[
				<h4>Preparation</h4> <!-- Préparation -->
				<ol>
					<li>Start melting butter over medium heat.</li>
					<li>Use a pan with a light-colored bottom so you can keep track of the color. Swirl the pan occasionally to be sure the butter is cooking evenly.</li>
					<li>As the butter melts, it will begin to foam.</li>
					<li>The color will progress from lemony-yellow to golden-tan to, finally, a toasty-brown.</li>
					<li>Once you smell that nutty aroma, take the pan off the heat and transfer the browned butter into a heat-proof bowl to cool.</li>
					<li>The milk solids will cook faster and you'll see them settle on the bottom of the pan like the dregs in a bottle of wine. When you transfer the brown butter to a new container, try to leave as much of this sediment in the pan as possible.</li>
				</ol>
			]]></prep>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Brown Butter B&eacute;arnaise Sauce Recipe]]></title>
			<ingredients><![CDATA[
				<h4>Ingredients</h4> <!-- Ingrédients -->
				<p>Yield: 20 Portions<p>
				<ul>
					<li>1 &frac14; cup Brown Butter</li>
					<li>3 oz. Egg Yolk</li>
					<li>1 tbs. Fresh lemon juice</li>
					<li>&frac12; cup Red Wine Vinegar</li>
					<li>1 oz. Fresh Tarragon Sprig </li>
					<li>2 tbs. Water</li>
					<li>Salt and Ground White Pepper to taste</li>
				</ul>
			]]></ingredients>
	​
			<prep><![CDATA[
				<h4>Preparation</h4> <!-- Préparation -->
				<ol>
					<li>In a Saut&eacute; pan bring to simmer the Vinegar and tarragon and reduce to half.</li>
					<li>Pass the vinegar thru the chinois and place in a large mixing bowl. 3. Add the Lemon Juice and Eggs.</li>
					<li>Vigorously whisk the egg yolks, vinegar and lemon juice together until the mixture is thickened and doubled in volume.</li>
					<li>Place the bowl over a saucepan containing barely simmering water.</li>
					<li>Water should not touch the bottom of the bowl.</li>
					<li>Continue to whisk rapidly. Be careful not to let the eggs get too hot or they will scramble. </li>
					<li>Slowly drizzle in the melted brown butter and continue to whisk until the sauce is thickened and doubled in volume.</li>
					<li>Remove from heat, add salt and pepper to taste.</li>
					<li>Cover and place in a warm spot until ready to use.</li>
					<li>If the sauce gets too thick, whisk in a few drops of warm water before serving.</li>
				</ol>
			]]></prep>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Veal Demi Glaze Recipe]]></title>
			<ingredients><![CDATA[
				<h4>Ingredients</h4> <!-- Ingrédients -->
				<p>Yield: 2 Quarts<p>
				<ul>
					<li>2 lbs. Beef and Veal Trimmings </li>
					<li>4 lbs. Veal Chunks Bones</li>
					<li>4 lbs. Vegetable Mirepoix (Carrots, Leeks, Onions, Celery)</li>
					<li>2 ea. Garlic Heads, cut in half</li>
					<li>6 oz. Tomato Paste</li>
					<li>4 btl. Dry Red Wine</li>
					<li>3 gl. Ice Cubes &bull; 4 ea. Bay Leaf</li>
					<li>2 ea. Thyme Sprig &bull; 2 ea. Rosemary Sprig</li>
					<li>1 tbs. Black Peppercorn</li>
					<li>Vegetable Oil as needed</li>
					<li>Cornstarch Slurry as needed</li>
					<li>Salt as needed</li>
				</ul>
			]]></ingredients>
​
			<prep><![CDATA[
				<h4>Preparation</h4> <!-- Préparation -->
				<ol>
					<li>Reheat the oven to 450 F.</li>
					<li>Place veal chunk bones over a sheet pan and roasted at 170 C until golden brown color. Reserved.</li>
					<li>Season Beef trimmings with salt.</li>
					<li>In a large rondo, bring a small amount of vegetable oil to the smoking point.</li>
					<li>Sear the beef trimmings in small amounts until golden brown on all sides. Remove trimmings from rondo leaving the fat on the rondo.</li>
					<li>Place the mirepoix, herbs, peppercorn, garlic and bay leave into the rondo and cooked on high heat until well caramelized.</li>
					<li>Add the tomato paste and caramelized well.</li>
					<li>Place back all the trimimings and veal bones to the rondo.</li>
					<li>Deglaze the sheet pan where we roast the bones with one bottle of red wine, scraping the bottom of the pan to remove the fond.</li>
					<li>Add deglazing jus to the pot together with the rest of the wine. 11. Reduce the wine until almost dry.</li>
					<li>Add the ice.</li>
					<li>Bring to a boil and reduce to a simmer.  Skim well.</li>
					<li>Simmer for allow flavors to infuse, around 8 hours and until desired consistency. Skim occasionally.</li>
					<li>Pass thru a chinois to another rondo, bring to a boil.</li>
					<li>Add cornstarch slurry if needed. Then simmer for 20 more minutes.</li>
					<li>Pass again thru the chinois. 18. Adjust seasoning with salt if necessary.</li>
				</ol>
			]]></prep>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Beef Gravy Recipe]]></title>
			<ingredients><![CDATA[
				<h4>Ingredients</h4> <!-- Ingrédients -->
				<p>Yield: 1 quart<p>
				<ul>
					<li>1 cups Red Wine</li>
					<li>3 cups Veal Demi Glaze</li>
					<li>1 cup Porto Wine</li>
					<li>2 oz. Butter, cubes</li>
					<li>3 ea. Thyme Sprig</li>
					<li>&frac34; cups Shallots, fine chopped</li>
					<li>Salt to taste</li>
				</ul>
			]]></ingredients>
​
			<prep><![CDATA[
				<h4>Preparation</h4> <!-- Préparation -->
				<ol>
					<li>Place butter, thyme and shallots into a saucepan with pinch of salt.</li>
					<li>Cook and stir shallots over medium-low heat until caramelized and browned, stir occasionally.</li>
					<li>Add red wine and Porto wine and bring to a simmer.</li>
					<li>Reduce heat to low; cook until wine is nearly evaporated and pan juices are thick and slightly syrupy.</li>
					<li>Add veal demi glaze, return to a simmer, and cook until reduced by half and sauce is slightly thickened.</li>
					<li>Seasoned as needed and pass thru the chinois.</li>
					<li>Reserve for service over bain marie.</li>
				</ol>
			]]></prep>
		</item>

		<item>
			<title><![CDATA[Pan Roasted Baby Vegetables Recipe]]></title>
			<ingredients><![CDATA[
				<h4>Ingredients</h4> <!-- Ingrédients -->
				<p>Yield: 10 Portions<p>
				<ul>
					<li>10 ea. Red Baby Beetroot, peeled stem on and cut in half</li>
					<li>10 ea. Yellow Baby Carrots, peeled stem on and cut in half</li>
					<li>10 ea. Baby Carrots, peeled stems on and cut in half lengthwise</li>
					<li>20 ea. Snap Peas, blanched</li>
					<li>10 ea. Snow Peas, blanched</li>
					<li>&frac14; cup EVOO</li>
					<li>2 ea. Thyme Sprig</li>
					<li>5 ea. Garlic Cloves, crushed</li>
					<li>Salt and Ground Black Peppercorn to taste</li>
				</ul>
			]]></ingredients>
​
			<prep><![CDATA[
				<h4>Preparation</h4> <!-- Préparation -->
				<ol>
					<li>Blanch all veggies separately to al dente and shock in ice bath.</li>
					<li>In a large non-stick saut&eacute; pan heat oil and add herbs and garlic.</li>
					<li>Warm up until fragrance come out and increase the heat to high and adds vegetables.</li>
					<li>Cook and stir until vegetables are hot enough and golden color.</li>
					<li>Always saut&eacute; the beets and purple carrots separate from the rest of veggies to avoid colored the rest of veggies.</li>
				</ol>
			]]></prep>
		</item>
​
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
​
		<sidebar><![CDATA[]]></sidebar>
​
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/hero/recipe-01.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Grilled Ribeye Steak Rutabaga Puree, Roasted Root Vegetables, Brown Butter Bearnaise Sauce]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Celebrity Cruises<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/02/article/recipe-01.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Grilled Ribeye Steak Rutabaga Puree, Roasted Root Vegetables, Brown Butter Bearnaise Sauce]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Celebrity Cruises<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></article_credit>
​
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
	</article>
	<!-- END: 2002 cel -->

</root>
