<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	
<article date="1910" id="01">
	<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
	<pub_date><![CDATA[October 2019]]></pub_date>
	<dir_year><![CDATA[19]]></dir_year>
	<dir_month><![CDATA[10]]></dir_month>
	<id_article><![CDATA[01]]></id_article>
	
	<author><![CDATA[Belmond]]></author>
	<id_supplier><![CDATA[bmd]]></id_supplier>
	
	<title><![CDATA[Belmond Grand Hibernian – Grand Tour of Ireland]]></title>
	<teaser><![CDATA[Belmond]]></teaser>
	<lead><![CDATA[
		Brimming with all the Georgian charm of a classic Dublin saloon, the Belmond Grand Hibernian train winds through Ireland's breathtaking landscape in luxurious style. 
	]]></lead>
	<body><![CDATA[
		<p>Depart on the Grand Tour of Ireland on Belmond Grand Hibernian and experience dramatic landscapes, regal castles and captivating towns, all whilst revelling in the elegant carriages of Ireland's only luxury sleeper train.</p>
		<p>Allow yourself to be enchanted by the irresistible charms of the Emerald Isle. Delve into the rich history with choices of private tours and excursions. Visit Hillsborough Castle and the world famous Jameson Distillery, or watch an impressive sheepdog demonstration in Galway. Spend time exploring the riverside city of Cork and the vibrant allure of Galway.</p>

		<figure class="article-tile">
			<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/article/advertorial-01-01.jpg">
		</figure>

		<p>The train&rsquo;s grand interiors echo classic Georgian architecture and the ambience of a Dublin saloon. Elegant en-suite cabins have a light and airy design, enriched with the warmth of traditional tweed finishes. You&rsquo;ll see our Celtic Knot symbol in all the small details. Follow it through each carriage and find yourself in the Observation Car, where large picture windows frame breath-taking views. </p>
		

		<figure class="article-tile">
			<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/article/advertorial-01-02.jpg">
		</figure>

		<p>Thirsty for a tipple while you&rsquo;re here? Our barman is on hand with a range of world-class malts and fine-wines at his fingertips. Or perhaps the evening&rsquo;s entertainment calls for a Guinness while you sway to Irish folk tunes. Dining on board is a taste sensation, with our sublime menus rivalling Dublin&rsquo;s top venues. Each dish celebrates Ireland&rsquo;s finest local produce, served with modern flair in dining cars Wexford and Sligo.&nbsp;</p>
		<p>Each day brings new experiences for pioneering adventurers.</p>
		<p>This unforgettable six-night journey allows each guest to experience this magical country that brims with rich heritage and lyrical spirit. </p>
	]]></body>
	
	<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

	<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/hero/advertorial-01.jpg</hero_src>
	<hero_caption><![CDATA[Belmond Grand Hibernian – Grand Tour of Ireland]]></hero_caption>
	<hero_credit><![CDATA[Belmond]]></hero_credit>
	<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/article/advertorial-01.jpg</article_src>
	<article_caption><![CDATA[Belmond Grand Hibernian – Grand Tour of Ireland]]></article_caption>
	<article_credit><![CDATA[Belmond]]></article_credit>
	
	<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
	<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
	<tile_new>none</tile_new>

	<tags>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
	</tags>
</article>
	
<article date="1910" id="02">
	<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
	<pub_date><![CDATA[October 2019]]></pub_date>
	<dir_year><![CDATA[19]]></dir_year>
	<dir_month><![CDATA[10]]></dir_month>
	<id_article><![CDATA[02]]></id_article>
	
	<author><![CDATA[Classic Vacations]]></author>
	<id_supplier><![CDATA[clv]]></id_supplier>
	
	<title><![CDATA[Classic Vacations]]></title>
	<teaser><![CDATA[Classic Vacations]]></teaser>
	<lead><![CDATA[
		Bringing the world closer, one vacation at a time.
	]]></lead>
	<body><![CDATA[
		<p>Classic Vacations delivers superior customer satisfaction. What started in 1978 as a travel company focused on Hawaii has grown to include 11 regions and over a hundred destinations worldwide. </p>
		<p>Classic Vacations packages are only available through your Travel Advisor, and they have a history of success in helping their partners plan first-rate vacations for millions of clients, just like you. Experiences you can&rsquo;t find anywhere else. </p>
		<p>They offer a full line of accommodations, from mid-tier to luxury (including suites, villas, and residences), competitive pricing, first class and private transportation options, and unique tours and excursions in Asia, Australia, Canada, Caribbean, Costa Rica, Dubai, Europe, Fiji, Hawaii, Maldives, Mexico, New Zealand, Seychelles, and Tahiti. </p>
		<p>Every product created by Classic Vacations, every supplier they partner with, and tool they develop is with you in mind&mdash;and Travel Advisors have always relied on Classic to help create exceptional travel experiences for their clients.</p>
		<p>The Classic Vacations product line is elaborate, but working with them is easy. Contact your travel advisor today and ask about a travel experience by Classic Vacations. </p>
	]]></body>
	
	<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

	<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/hero/advertorial-02.jpg</hero_src>
	<hero_caption><![CDATA[Bringing the world closer, one vacation at a time.]]></hero_caption>
	<hero_credit><![CDATA[Classic Vacations]]></hero_credit>
	<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/article/advertorial-02.jpg</article_src>
	<article_caption><![CDATA[Bringing the world closer, one vacation at a time.]]></article_caption>
	<article_credit><![CDATA[Classic Vacations]]></article_credit>
	
	<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
	<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
	<tile_new>none</tile_new>

	<tags>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
	</tags>
</article>
	
<article date="1910" id="03">
	<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
	<pub_date><![CDATA[October 2019]]></pub_date>
	<dir_year><![CDATA[19]]></dir_year>
	<dir_month><![CDATA[10]]></dir_month>
	<id_article><![CDATA[03]]></id_article>
	
	<author><![CDATA[Adventures by Disney]]></author>
	<id_supplier><![CDATA[abd]]></id_supplier>
	
	<title><![CDATA[Adventures by Disney® Provides Exclusive Sailing on AmaWaterways™]]></title>
	<teaser><![CDATA[Adventures by Disney ]]></teaser>
	<lead><![CDATA[
		Explore some of Europe&rsquo;s most magnificent destinations as you sail along the Rh&ocirc;ne, Seine, Rhine and Danube Rivers on an <span style="font-style: italic;">Adventures by Disney</span> River Cruise vacation with AmaWaterways&trade;, a leader in luxury river cruising.
	]]></lead>
	<body><![CDATA[

		<figure class="article-tile">
			<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/article/advertorial-03-01.jpg">
		</figure>
  
		<p>The <em>Adventures by Disney</em> River Cruises were designed for families. The itineraries offer a variety of experiences that parents, children and teens can enjoy&mdash;ranging from active excursions, castle and museum tours and unique onboard activities to Disney movie nights for Junior Adventurers and wine tasting for adults.</p>
		<p><strong><em>Adventures by Disney</em></strong><strong> River Cruise Destinations </strong><br />
			Choose one of our exciting <em>Adventures by Disney</em> River Cruises&mdash;and create unforgettable memories on your family vacation!</p>
		<ul>
			<li>Seine River Cruise <br />
				A 10-day/9-night, all-inclusive adventure through France</li>
			<li>Rh&ocirc;ne River Cruise <br />
				An 8-day/7-night, all-inclusive adventure through France</li>
			<li>Rhine River Cruise <br />
				An 8-day/7-night, all-inclusive adventure to 6 destinations in 4 countries&mdash;France, Germany, Switzerland and The Netherlands</li>
			<li>Danube River Cruise <br />
				An 8-day/7-night, all-inclusive adventure to 8 destinations in 4 countries&mdash;Germany, Austria, Slovakia and Hungary</li>
		</ul>

		<br/>

		<p>As to Disney artwork/properties: &copy;Disney</p>
	]]></body>
	
	<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

	<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/hero/advertorial-03.jpg</hero_src>
	<hero_caption><![CDATA[Adventures by Disney® Provides Exclusive Sailing on AmaWaterways™]]></hero_caption>
	<hero_credit><![CDATA[Adventures by Disney ]]></hero_credit>
	<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/article/advertorial-03.jpg</article_src>
	<article_caption><![CDATA[Adventures by Disney® Provides Exclusive Sailing on AmaWaterways™]]></article_caption>
	<article_credit><![CDATA[Adventures by Disney ]]></article_credit>
	
	<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
	<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
	<tile_new>none</tile_new>

	<tags>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
	</tags>
</article>
	
<article date="1910" id="04">
	<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
	<pub_date><![CDATA[October 2019]]></pub_date>
	<dir_year><![CDATA[19]]></dir_year>
	<dir_month><![CDATA[10]]></dir_month>
	<id_article><![CDATA[04]]></id_article>
	
	<author><![CDATA[Windstar]]></author>
	<id_supplier><![CDATA[win]]></id_supplier>
	
	<title><![CDATA[The $250 Million Star Plus Initiative]]></title>
	<teaser><![CDATA[Windstar]]></teaser>
	<lead><![CDATA[
		<strong>So Much More Than A Paint Job.</strong> This $250 Million Initiative Transforms Our Star Class Room For Stretching Out.
	]]></lead>
	<body><![CDATA[
		<blockquote style="font-style: italic; font-size: 1.0em;">
			&ldquo;They just don&rsquo;t build ships like this anymore. We are keeping the best elements and designs from these iconic vessels and re-envisioning them for the modern guest.&rdquo;<br />
			&mdash; <strong>Ray Chung, Director Of Design, The Johnson Studio At Cooper Carry</strong>
		</blockquote>

  		<p><strong>WHEN OUR GUESTS TELL US</strong> they want more of what they love on Windstar, we take it as seriously as captain&rsquo;s orders. That&rsquo;s why we&rsquo;ve embarked on a comprehensive renovation of our three all-suite Star Class ships &mdash; Star Breeze, Star Legend and Star Pride. So you get even more suites to choose from, more delight on deck, and more to explore on board.</p>
		<p>You&rsquo;ll love our beautiful new teak sundeck and iconic, cascading pool, 50 new impeccably-designed suites, gorgeous new bathrooms in all suites, and exciting menus at our new dining venues. There are also improvements behind the scenes that will help our crew serve you even better and make our Star Class ships more environmentally friendly than ever. </p>
		<p>Like all of our small ships, our Star Class, holding only 312 guests, will continue to call at some of the world&rsquo;s smallest and most interesting ports. And you&rsquo;ll still enjoy the intimate environment and highly-personalized service that Windstar offers with our enviable ratio of crew to guests.</p>
		
		<blockquote style="font-style: italic; font-size: 1.0em;">
			&ldquo;The Initiative is not about getting bigger, it&rsquo;s about offering our guests more of what they love about Windstar. Each ship will carry 312 guests total which nearly matches the capacity for Wind Surf.<br />
			<br>
			The additional capacity keeps us squarely in the under 350 category. We will continue to offer the world&rsquo;s best small ship experience but with more amenities that our guests have been asking us for like additional dining and an expanded spa and fitness center. We are making these improvements to ensure these beloved ships may continue to operate well into the future.&rdquo;<br />
			&mdash; <strong>John Delaney, President, Windstar Cruises</strong>
		</blockquote>
	
		<h4>NOW, YOU&rsquo;LL GET EVEN MORE OF WHAT YOU LOVE</h4>
		<ul>
			<li>Fifty new suites with new configurations and new 1,374 square-foot Grand Owner&rsquo;s Suite</li>
			<li>All existing suites will receive all-new bathrooms with new modern design touches</li>
			<li>New artful and eclectic Spanish restaurant, <em>Cuadro 44 by Anthony Sasso</em></li>
			<li>New casual outdoor grill venue, <em>Star Grill by Steven Raichlen</em></li>
			<li>Expanded spa and more spacious fitness center with new motion studio</li>
			<li>Beautiful new elevated pool and whirlpool</li>
			<li>Expanded public spaces and open deck areas</li>
			<li>New enlarged Veranda restaurant with enhanced interior seating</li>
			<li>Interactive TV system in all suites with hundreds of movie choices</li>
			<li>Enhanced shopping experience with high-end jewelry gallery</li>
			<li>Refreshed and updated public restrooms</li>
		</ul>

		<figure class="article-tile">
			<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/article/advertorial-04-01.jpg">
			<figcaption>
				<h4>YOU&rsquo;VE GOT 50 BRAND NEW SUITES TO CHOOSE FROM</h4>
				Want to snuggle up to the sea with a bed beside the window? Or combine a new Owner&rsquo;s Suite Midship to create a three-bedroom, two-balcony floor plan? With the addition of 50 new stunning, comfortable suites, new furnishings, open living spaces for entertaining and relaxing, and welcoming ambience, your private retreat and home base for your travels awaits.
		   		
				<h4>NEW SUITE CATEGORIES</h4>
				We&rsquo;ve configured the layout to give you more of what you want &mdash; space, style, views and convenience.

				<ul>
					<li>Grand Owner&rsquo;s Suite</li>
					<li>Owner&rsquo;s Suite Midship</li>
					<li>Deluxe Suite</li>
					<li>Star Balcony Suite</li>
					<li>Star Ocean View Suite</li>
					<li>Star Porthole Suite</li>
				</ul>
			</figcaption>
		</figure>

		<figure class="article-tile">
			<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/article/advertorial-04-02.jpg">
			<figcaption>
				<h4>FRESHEN UP IN A FRESH NEW BATHROOM</h4>
				Nothing beats the start of a new day in a new port, so we&rsquo;ve taken a renewed approach to getting ready with redesigned bathrooms in ALL suites on the ship. With new sinks, new mirrors, new tile, modern touches, and many with new walk-in showers, it&rsquo;s sure to start your day off with a smile.
			</figcaption>
		</figure>

		<p><strong>SOAK IT ALL IN.</strong><br />
			While other cruise lines might use a transformation as an opportunity to add a few water slides, we chose to enhance your experience of the sea and sky with a gorgeous elevated pool and whirlpool.</p>
		<p>We&rsquo;ve expanded the sundeck so you have more room to sunbathe and relax. What&rsquo;s more, you can also explore the brand <em>new Star Grill by Steven Raichlen</em>, or sip on a Star Bar cocktail.</p>
		<p><strong>RECHARGE IN OUR COMPLETELY REVAMPED SPA.</strong><br />
			After an exhilarating day of hiking, watersports, or exploring the world&rsquo;s most interesting ports like a local, you can retreat to our beautiful new spa with serene treatment rooms, fitness center, motion studio, and salon.</p>
		<p>Want to indulge in a massage with techniques from around the world? Take an invigorating yoga class? Jump on a treadmill for a quick run with a view of the pool? Get spruced up for a night out? This is your haven on board.</p>

		<figure class="article-tile">
			<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/article/advertorial-04-03.jpg">
			<figcaption>
				<h4>WHAT YOU LOVE STAYS THE SAME (OR GETS EVEN BETTER)</h4>
				<em>Amphora</em> restaurant remains just the way our guests love it, still in its prime mid-ship location. <em>Veranda</em> restaurant will offer a new, expanded buffet with additional indoor seating. The Watersports Platform is untouched and as fun as ever. The Lounge, Compass Rose, Yacht Club Caf&eacute;, and Atrium continue to offer spaces to convene and relax that are as inviting as ever.</p>

				<h4>THE MOST INVENTIVE, MODERN GRILL AT SEA</h4>
				<blockquote style="font-style: italic; font-size: 1.0em;">
					&ldquo;I&rsquo;ve spent my life traveling the world&rsquo;s barbecue trail to bring my readers and viewers the ultimate in global grilling. What better way to share my discoveries than on a Windstar cruise ship bound for new adventures?&rdquo;&rdquo;<br>
					<strong>&mdash; Steven Raichlen</strong>
				</blockquote>

				<h4>GRILLED. SMOKED. SLOW-ROASTED ON THE ROTISSERIE</h4>
				You can tell a lot about a culture by the way it grills. You&rsquo;ll find all your traditional grilled and barbecued favorites (and discover new dishes from around the globe) <em>at Star Grill by Steven Raichlen</em> &mdash; our new casual outdoor restaurant brought to you in partnership with the man who reinvented barbecue.<br>
				<br>
				For Raichlen, a multi-award-winning writer, lecturer, and international TV host, barbecue isn&rsquo;t a pastime, it&rsquo;s a calling. The founder of Barbecue University and Barbecue Hall of Famer hosts the popular <em>Project Fire</em> and <em>Project Smoke</em> shows on Public Television. His 31 books &mdash; many of them <em>New York Times</em> bestsellers &mdash; have won five James Beard Awards, three IACP / Julia Child Awards, and have been translated into 17 languages.<br>
				<br>
				Now you can taste for yourself where Raichlen&rsquo;s curiosity for world barbecue takes him. Just steps away from the popular <em>Star Bar</em>, the <em>Star Grill by Steven Raichlen</em> offers alfresco dining with seating for 95, with two carving stations. Experience traditional and world barbecue with a modern twist, from maple sriracha chicken wings to Danish smoked shrimp, from Hill<strong> </strong>Country brisket to lemongrass pork &mdash; or on sea days, enjoy a mid-morning Fr&uuml;hschoppen with artisanal grilled sausage and pretzel rolls.<strong> </strong>Served<strong> </strong>with a sea view!</p>
			</figcaption>
		</figure>

		<figure class="article-tile">
			<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/article/advertorial-04-04.jpg">
			<figcaption>
				<h4>ART OF SPANISH CUISINE. MASTERED ON BOARD</h4>
				<blockquote style="font-style: italic; font-size: 1.0em;">
					&ldquo;I&rsquo;ve spent a lifetime studying Spanish food and culture, working in several Catalan kitchens, traveling the Iberian landscape and learning from and getting inspired by the masters: everyone from the Roca Brothers of El Celler de Can Roca to the unmatchable Pablo Picasso. This new venture with Windstar will be the perfect vehicle to showcase the universally enticing flavors of Spain and its coastal seas. I&rsquo;m extremely excited and honored to be involved with this innovative company.&rdquo;<br>
					<strong>&mdash; Anthony Sasso</strong>
				</blockquote>
				<br>
				<strong>YOU WON&rsquo;T HAVE TO </strong>travel any further than Deck 6 to find a little bit (or bite) of Spain with our new specialty restaurant, <em>Cuadro 44 by Anthony Sasso</em>. A 13- year veteran of Casa Mono in New York City, where he earned the restaurant a Michelin star ten times, and an alumni of Windstar&rsquo;s culinary-themed cruise program, Sasso knows his way around the kitchen and the galley. His newest creation is an inventive take on modern Spanish cuisine just for Windstar.<br>
				<br>
				Savor flavors of Spanish local culture as you dine family style in intimate surroundings that encourage sharing and camaraderie. Sit at a cozy chef&rsquo;s counter or communal table and pass around regional dishes like jamon iberico de bellota (24 month aged pork leg raised solely on acorns), or a favorite dessert of Madrid, churros y chocolate, cinnamon and sugar fritters served with spicy hot chocolate and fresh seasonal fruit.<br>
				<br>
				It&rsquo;s a delicious way to experience the best coastal regions of Spain &mdash; no matter where your Windstar cruise is headed.	
			</figcaption>
		</figure>
	]]></body>
	
	<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

	<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/hero/advertorial-04.jpg</hero_src>
	<hero_caption><![CDATA[The $250 Million Star Plus Initiative]]></hero_caption>
	<hero_credit><![CDATA[Windstar]]></hero_credit>
	<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/19/10/article/advertorial-04.jpg</article_src>
	<article_caption><![CDATA[The $250 Million Star Plus Initiative]]></article_caption>
	<article_credit><![CDATA[Windstar]]></article_credit>
	
	<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
	<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
	<tile_new>none</tile_new>

	<tags>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
	</tags>
</article>
	
</root>