<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	
<element date="1910" id="banner-1910-wjv">
	<country><![CDATA[ca]]></country>
	<tactic><![CDATA[banner]]></tactic>
	<year><![CDATA[19]]></year>
	<month><![CDATA[10]]></month>
	<id_live><![CDATA[01]]></id_live>

	<supplier><![CDATA[WestJet Vacations]]></supplier>
	<directory><![CDATA[wjv]]></directory>
	
	<title><![CDATA[Receive special added values at Grand Velas Los Cabos]]></title>
	<intro><![CDATA[Embrace the feeling of luxury.]]></intro>
	<offer><![CDATA[
		Receive special added values with a minimum 5-night stay at Grand Velas Los Cabos.
	]]></offer>
	<content><![CDATA[
		<p>Embrace the feeling of luxury and receive the below added values with your stay at Grand Velas Los Cabos:</p>
		<ul>
			<li>One select SE Spa treatment per room, per stay in all room types. See hotel concierge for details.</li>
			<li>One SE Spa Water Journey (hydrotherapy) access for adult, per stay in the Grand Class Suite Oceanfront room type. Advance reservations are required and can be made by email or at the concierge.</li>
			<li>$50 SE Spa credit per adult, per night. Applicable to massage, facial or body wrap treatments with a duration of 50 minutes or more.</li>
			<li>10% off at the Hotel Boutique. Not applicable at the Spa Boutique.</li>
			<li>Kids 4-12 years old stay 50% off with paying adults in Ambassador Suite Ocean View, Ambassador Pool Suite Ocean View and Grand Class Suite Oceanfront room types.</li>
			<li>Teens 13-15 years old stay 50% off with paying adults in Ambassador Suite Ocean View and Ambassador Pool Suite Ocean View room types.</li>
			<li>No connecting fees applicable on Ambassador and Ambassador Pool Suites Ocean View room types.</li>
		</ul>
		
		<br>
		<br>
		
		<p><strong>Book by:</strong> October 30, 2019 <br />
			<strong>Travel:</strong> Now - December 18, 2019<br />
			<strong>Participating hotel:</strong> Grand Velas Los Cabos, <em>Los Cabos </em>&#9733;&#9733;&#9733;&#9733;&#9733;<br>
			<strong>How to get this offer:</strong> Resort credit will be distributed to guests upon arrival at the time of check-in. Package price will automatically reflect the discount when searching for qualified vacations.</p>
			
		<br>

		<p><strong>Grand Velas Los Cabos</strong> is located near San Jos&eacute; del Cabo on the southern Baja California peninsula. This luxury resort has 307 suites with spectacular ocean views and excellent service, creating an unforgettable vacation experience for families, couples and groups!</p>
		
		<figure class="article-tile">
			<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.ca/im/ezine/img/19/10/banner/prod-wjv-01-ca.jpg">
		</figure>
		
	]]></content>
	
	<terms id="banner-1910-wjv">
		<consumer><![CDATA[
			Advance booking required. Non-refundable and non-transferable. Offer limited and subject to availability. Offer subject to change and expire without notice. New bookings only. Not valid on group bookings. Other restrictions may apply. Package price will automatically reflect the discount when booking qualifying room types. Spa credit cannot be combined with other Spa promotions. Spa credit is not applicable to SPA Boutique, beauty salon, hydrotherapy circuit nor spa cabanas. No connecting fees on select Suites is subject to availability upon request. Connecting suites available connect King Bedded Suites to Two Queen Bedded Suites. Both Suites have to be paid. Added values have no cash value and will expire upon check-out. Complimentary inclusions available at no extra cost. Inclusions can be changed or withdrawn at any time without notice. For any further details, please see hotel front desk. Quebec licensee. <strong>Ontario travel agents are covered by TICO. Mailing address: 6085 Midfield Road, Toronto ON L5P 1A2. TICO registration number: 50018683.</strong>
		]]></consumer>
		
		<agent><![CDATA[]]></agent>
	</terms>

	<brandcolor>HEXColor</brandcolor>
	<iframe_height></iframe_height>
	<id_ezine><![CDATA[banner-01]]></id_ezine>
	<file><![CDATA[]]></file>
</element>

<element date="1910" id="banner-1910-rci">
	<country><![CDATA[ca]]></country>
	<tactic><![CDATA[banner]]></tactic>
	<year><![CDATA[19]]></year>
	<month><![CDATA[10]]></month>
	<id_live><![CDATA[02]]></id_live>

	<supplier><![CDATA[Royal Caribbean International]]></supplier>
	<directory><![CDATA[rci]]></directory>
	
	<title><![CDATA[VACATION TOPPING EURO HOPPING]]></title>
	<intro><![CDATA[New Summer adventures in the Old World]]></intro>
	<offer><![CDATA[
		<ul>
			<li>30% Off Every Guest</li>
			<li>Kids Sail Free*</li>
			<li>Up to $100 USD Onboard Credit on select sailings </li>
		</ul>
	]]></offer>
	<content><![CDATA[
		<p>Put bold on the itinerary in Summer 2020 on a Mediterranean family adventure filled with all of Europe&rsquo;s greatest hits. When you sail with Royal Caribbean<sup>&reg;</sup>, you can go from gothic cathedrals in Spain to Roman relics in Italy. Volcano hikes in Santorini to strolls through the old town of Ephesus in Turkey. And keep the discoveries going strong in between shores with bold new thrills, delicious dining and awe-inspiring entertainment onboard Explorer of the Seas<sup>&reg;</sup> and the biggest ship in Europe, Allure of the Seas<sup>&reg;</sup> &mdash; both newly Amplified with all new family friendly features. Looking to check the best of the Baltic, British Isles, Scandinavia and Russia off your bucket list? Check out unforgettable itineraries onboard the returning regional Jewel of the Seas<sup>&reg;</sup>. The best part? You&rsquo;ll only need to unpack once. Come Seek the Royal Caribbean.</p>
	]]></content>
	
	<terms id="banner-1910-rci">
		<consumer><![CDATA[
			Price is per person, in CAD, cruise only, applies to select sailings, based on double-occupancy. Onboard Credit offer is valid for new, named group bookings made in Ensemble Headquarter Groups. Individual reservations may be transferred into an existing group, assuming required criteria are met. Offer includes up to $50 USD OBC per stateroom. Bookings will be eligible for an additional $50 OBC when group space is named and deposited 6 months prior to sailing. OBC is in USD, has no cash value, is non-transferable, not redeemable for cash, and will expire if not used by 10:00 PM on the last evening of the cruise. OBC will be applied automatically to all eligible reservations. &ldquo;30% Off Every Guest&rdquo; applies to select sailings departing on or after 11/1/19. &ldquo;30% Off Every Guest&rdquo; provides 30% off cruise fare for all guests in the stateroom. Kids Sail Free provides free cruise fare for 3rd guests and higher who are 12 years old or younger on select 4-night or longer Alaska, Bahamas, Bermuda, Canada, Caribbean, CaribNE, Coastal, Europe, Hawaii and Repositioning sailings departing between 9/1/19 &ndash; 5/15/19 and 8/31/20 &ndash; 12/17/20. Offer excludes 2019 Thanksgiving sailings (Sailings between 11/23/19 &ndash; 11/30/19), Holiday sailings (Sailings between 12/15/19 &ndash; 1/3/20), President&rsquo;s Day sailings (Sailings between 2/14/20 &ndash; 2/17/20), Spring Break sailings (Sailings between 3/14/20 &ndash; 3/23/20), Holy Week/Easter sailings (Sailings between 4/3/20 &ndash; 4/17/20) and 2020 Thanksgiving sailings (Sailings between 11/21/20 &ndash; 11/27/20). Taxes, fees, and port expenses are additional and apply to all guests. NRDB cancelled prior to final payment due date will receive a future cruise credit in the amount of the deposit minus a 100USD/CAD per person service fee (&quot;FCC&quot;). FCC is non-transferable and expires 12-months from issue date. 100USD/CAD per person service fee applies to changes to NRDB ship or sail date. Deposits made toward Guarantees and Grand Suites and higher categories are non-refundable and are subject to NRD Booking Terms. Offer applies to new, individual and named group bookings confirmed at prevailing rates. Offer open to residents of US, Canada, Puerto Rico and select countries in the Caribbean. Prices and offers are subject to availability and change without notice, capacity controlled, and may be withdrawn at any time. Refer to your travel advisor for complete terms and conditions. Royal Caribbean International reserves the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions and to change or update fares, fees and surcharges at any time without prior notice. Come Seek is a registered trademark of Royal Caribbean. &copy;2019 Royal Caribbean Cruises Ltd. Ships&rsquo; registry: Bahamas.
		]]></consumer>
		
		<agent><![CDATA[]]></agent>
	</terms>
		
	<products>
		<!-- PRODUCT ONE -->
		<product id="banner-1910-rci">
			<title><![CDATA[Western Mediterranean]]></title>
			<offer><![CDATA[Up to $100 USD in Onboard Credit*]]></offer>
			<description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
			
			<cost><![CDATA[1,669]]></cost>
			<taxes><![CDATA[142]]></taxes>
			<departing><![CDATA[May 24, 2020]]></departing>
			<duration><![CDATA[7 Nights]]></duration>
			<pricing><![CDATA[Price is per person based on double occupancy.]]></pricing>
			<currency><![CDATA[CAD]]></currency>
			
			<ship><![CDATA[Allure of the Seas<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></ship>
			<category><![CDATA[Balcony]]></category>
			<embarkation><![CDATA[Barcelona, Spain]]></embarkation>
			<disembarkation><![CDATA[Barcelona, Spain]]></disembarkation>
			
			<inclusions_title><![CDATA[Ports of Call]]></inclusions_title>
			<inclusions_desc><![CDATA[
				<p>Palma de Mallorca, Spain; Provence (Marseille), France; Florence/Pisa (La Spezia), Italy; Rome (Civitavecchia), Italy; Naples, Italy</p>
			]]></inclusions_desc>
			
			<img_hero><![CDATA[prod-rci-01-ca.jpg]]></img_hero>
		</product>

		<!-- PRODUCT TWO -->
		<product id="banner-1910-rci">
			<title><![CDATA[Greek Isles]]></title>
			<offer><![CDATA[Up to $100 USD in Onboard Credit*]]></offer>
			<description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
			
			<cost><![CDATA[2,019]]></cost>
			<taxes><![CDATA[123]]></taxes>
			<departing><![CDATA[Jun 5, 2020]]></departing>
			<duration><![CDATA[9 Nights]]></duration>
			<pricing><![CDATA[Price is per person based on double occupancy.]]></pricing>
			<currency><![CDATA[CAD]]></currency>
			
			<ship><![CDATA[Explorer of the Seas<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></ship>
			<category><![CDATA[Balcony]]></category>
			<embarkation><![CDATA[Rome, Italy]]></embarkation>
			<disembarkation><![CDATA[Rome, Italy]]></disembarkation>

			<inclusions_title><![CDATA[Ports of Call]]></inclusions_title>
			<inclusions_desc><![CDATA[
				<p>Chania (Souda), Crete, Greece; Mykonos, Greece; Santorini, Greece; Ephesus (Kusadasi), Turkey; Athens (Piraeus), Greece; Naples, Italy</p>
			]]></inclusions_desc>

			<img_hero><![CDATA[prod-rci-02-ca.jpg]]></img_hero>
		</product>

		<!-- PRODUCT THREE -->
		<product id="banner-1910-rci">
			<title><![CDATA[Artic Circle]]></title>
			<offer><![CDATA[Up to $100 USD in Onboard Credit*]]></offer>
			<description><![CDATA[ ]]></description>
			
			<cost><![CDATA[3,179]]></cost>
			<taxes><![CDATA[201]]></taxes>
			<departing><![CDATA[Jun 7, 2020]]></departing>
			<duration><![CDATA[11 Nights]]></duration>
			<pricing><![CDATA[Price is per person based on double occupancy.]]></pricing>
			<currency><![CDATA[CAD]]></currency>
			
			<ship><![CDATA[Jewel of the Seas<sup>&reg;</sup>]]></ship>
			<category><![CDATA[Balcony]]></category>
			<embarkation><![CDATA[Copenhagen, Denmark]]></embarkation>
			<disembarkation><![CDATA[Copenhagen, Denmark]]></disembarkation>
			
			<inclusions_title><![CDATA[Ports of Call]]></inclusions_title>
			<inclusions_desc><![CDATA[
				<p>Stavanger, Norway; Artic Circle (Cruising); Tromso, Norway; Honningsvag, Norway; Alesund, Norway; Flam, Norway; Geiranger, Norway</p>
			]]></inclusions_desc>

			
			<img_hero><![CDATA[prod-rci-03-ca.jpg]]></img_hero>
		</product>
	</products>

	<brandcolor>HEXColor</brandcolor>
	<iframe_height></iframe_height>
	<id_ezine><![CDATA[banner-02]]></id_ezine>
	<file><![CDATA[]]></file>
</element>
	
</root>