<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<!-- BEGIN: 2004 stc -->
	<article date="2004" id="03">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[April 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- April = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[04]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[03]]></id_article>

		<author><![CDATA[Star Clippers]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[stc]]></id_supplier>

		<title><![CDATA[Five Reasons to Sail with Star Clippers]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Star Clippers]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Sailing on Star Clippers leads to unforgettable experiences
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/article/advertorial-03-01.jpg">

			<p>Star Clippers tall sailing ships offer an experience that is at once modern and classic. Their ships embrace the romance of sailing the open ocean and marry it with all the comforts and trimmings of a luxury yacht. And perhaps most importantly, they offer a unique way for their guests to see favorite destinations in the Caribbean, Mediterranean and Southeast Asia through a new lens. Here are five reasons why sailing on a Star Clippers cruise leads to memories for a lifetime:</p>

			<p><strong>1. The experience is intimate.</strong><br>
			Star Clippers sailings offer an intimate experience. With less than 230 fellow passengers - instead of the 3,000 you find on large cruise ships - the small group size makes for a warmer and more authentic experience.</p>

			<p><strong>2. Star Clippers take you to smaller, exotic ports of call.</strong><br>
			Star Clippers whisk guests away to the less populated, more out-of-the-way places that the big ships simply cannot access, like a hidden harbor, a private beach, or a colorful local fishing village. There are no mass crowds, instead, guests have opportunities to share quiet moments away from the crowds; immerse themselves in local, exotic cultures; and spend more time off the ship exploring the destination.</p>

			<p><strong>3. Personalized service.</strong><br>
			The crew on Star Clippers are friendly and accessible.They know your name, your favorite drink, your culinary preferences, and more. With fewer guests onboard, experiences are more handcrafted and unique. Everything is immaculately maintained, and the staff is far from intrusive. Your steward knows exactly when you may need service or leave you to your privacy.</p>

			<p><strong>4. You will make amazing connections onboard.</strong><br>
			It&rsquo;s a close community onboard a Star Clippers ship, with plenty of interaction for those who want it. The environment is social and convivial, both on and off the ship, and guests often make life-long friends.</p>

			<p><strong>5. You will enjoy an authentic sailing experience.</strong><br>
			On a Star Clippers ship, you feel like you&rsquo;re sailing on your own private yacht. Embrace your inner sailor and help raise the sails and learn to tie a proper knot. Or, if you&rsquo;re feeling adventurous, spend the afternoon relaxing in the bowsprit net, or climb the mast to the Crow&rsquo;s Nest for a panoramic view.</p>

			<p>To book your next unique sailing adventure, contact your travel advisor today.</p>
		]]></body>

		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/hero/advertorial-03.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Five Reasons to Sail with Star Clippers]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Star Clippers]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/article/advertorial-03.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Five Reasons to Sail with Star Clippers]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Star Clippers]]></article_credit>

		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
	</article>
	<!-- END: 2004 stc -->

	<!-- BEGIN: 2004 gow -->
	<article date="2004" id="02">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[April 2020]]></pub_date>
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[04]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[02]]></id_article>

		<author><![CDATA[Goway]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[gow]]></id_supplier>

		<title><![CDATA[East African Safari vs Southern African Safari]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Goway]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Interested in enjoying an African safari? In East Africa, there are Kenyan safaris and Tanzanian safaris. In Southern Africa, you&rsquo;ll find safaris in South Africa and Botswana. There are over 1100 different species of animals, including reptiles and over 2600 species of birds. There is surely something for everyone.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<h2>Animals and Game Viewing</h2>

			<p>We all want to see the Big five &ndash; the lion, the leopard, the rhino, the elephant and the Cape buffalo. These are found in both the east and the south. In statistical terms, Tanzania has the largest quantity of game animals. One of the biggest concentrations of animals is in the Ngorongoro Crater, which is a wonderful game reserve. However, before heading off there, there are several other reasons to consider where to conduct your game viewing. For example, Lake Nakuru in Kenya is home to thousands of pink flamingos and Botswana has the largest number of elephants.</p>

			<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/article/advertorial-02-01.jpg">

			<p>Let&rsquo;s now consider how game viewing works. In Southern Africa, you will stay at a lodge or camp and it will be the organizer of your African safari. They will provide the vehicles and the guides who work for the lodge or camp. You will do your viewing within a certain radius of your accommodation and the territory will be known by the guide like the back of his or her hand. The game drives will be in the early morning and the late afternoon, avoiding the hottest parts of the day. There will be night game drives when you get to see the nocturnal activities of the animals. One lodge or camp should satisfy the most avid of safari visitors on a Southern Africa vacation. In the evening, you will probably spend time recapping the day with both your fellow travelers and your guide. If you are staying at a private lodge or camp, you will have the opportunity to enjoy a &ldquo;Sundowner.&rdquo; This experience happens towards the end of the afternoon drive when your guide will find a safe spot in the bush and set up a bar with a selection of drinks to be consumed while watching the sun set over this magical land.</p>

			<p>In East Africa, it is typical to stay at several lodges or camps in order to obtain the true safari experience. A couple of nights at a selection of game parks is the usual way to enjoy an East African safari. This means you will be travelling for several hours getting from one park to the next. Each game park exists in a designated area. The game drives will not be organized by the lodge/camp but by a local tour operator. There is nothing wrong with this &ndash; just pointing out the differences in organization. The safari itself could take up most of the day, again, just a different approach. The vehicles used in Southern Africa are open-sided land cruisers and sometimes, there are only a few feet between you and the wildlife (up close and personal). In East Africa, the vehicles are land cruisers which are usually fully enclosed, but open vehicles are also used especially on fly-in safaris.</p>

			<p>In addition to the organization of the safari, you may see a difference in the terrain. In Southern Africa, it could appear to be denser in vegetation, while in East Africa, the terrain is more open plain. The latter could be more suitable for observing herds of animals, but the bush can reveal all kinds of animals who are perhaps resting or avoiding the sun. Don&rsquo;t worry about that. Your guide will seek them out.</p>

			<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/article/advertorial-02-02.jpg">

			<p>Another difference to consider is how you will view the animals. The game parks in Southern Africa are fenced, meaning the animals can&rsquo;t stray outside. Don&rsquo;t get the impression that you are restricted to a small area. These game parks in most cases are quite vast. In East Africa, animals are free to roam wherever they like and are constantly on the move. This means you don&rsquo;t know what you are going to see exactly. However, remember there are great quantities of animals in this region. In Southern Africa, all wildlife reserves and game parks have strict rules on the number of safari vehicles that can view a particular animal or group of animals at once &ndash; generally no more than three. This is easy to enforce because all vehicles belong to lodges within the reserve and all lodges must follow reserve rules. The guides communicate over two-way radio to ensure that these rules are adhered to. On an East Africa safari, however, there is no limit to the number of jeeps at any particular sighting, so it could be that you will encounter a whole bunch of vehicles looking at, say, a pride of lions.</p>

			<p>Regardless of the differences between East African and South African safaris, both offer a unique opportunity to get close to nature. With Goway&rsquo;s African experiences, you can find the best safari to meet your needs and view all the animals you are hoping to see. Contact your travel advisor to find the right safari for you.</p>
		]]></body>

		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/hero/advertorial-02.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[East African Safari vs Southern African Safari]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Goway]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/article/advertorial-02.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[East African Safari vs Southern African Safari]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Goway]]></article_credit>

		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
	</article>
	<!-- END: 2004 gow -->

	<!-- BEGIN: 2004 CRE -->
	<article date="2004" id="01">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[April 2020]]></pub_date>
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[04]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[01]]></id_article>

		<author><![CDATA[Crystal]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[cre]]></id_supplier>

		<title><![CDATA[Experience Exhilarating and Intrepid Expeditions Aboard Crystal Endeavor&reg;]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Crystal]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Embark on an all-inclusive journey of intrepid discovery, exploring polar regions and remote landscapes, further than standard cruise ships can go.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>From the World&rsquo;s Most Awarded Luxury Cruise Line comes the world&rsquo;s most spacious luxury expedition yacht, Crystal Endeavor. The all-suite, all-verandah, with a sleek design built to PC6 Polar Class specifications and anchor-free dynamic positioning technology, is set to explore the farthest reaches of Earth. From Antarctica in 2020 to Alaska in 2021, Crystal Endeavor offers an array of expedition voyages - allowing for intrepid discovery of remote polar regions and little-known tropical destinations with alluring itineraries for every traveler.</p>

			<p>Hosted by Crystal&rsquo;s award-winning staff, attentive butlers and an experienced Expedition Team, with one of the highest staff-to-guest ratios in the industry (1 staff to 1 guest), a mere 200 guests will be exposed to rare wildlife sightings, intriguing cultures and the iconic landscapes.</p>

			<p>Inviting and elegant, Crystal Endeavor&rsquo;s 100 suites are enclaves of sophisticated luxury, among the largest and most spacious in expedition cruising. From the grandeur of the Expedition Suite to the decidedly chic Expedition Penthouse, all accommodations feature a private verandah and the personalized services of Crystal&rsquo;s European-trained butlers. Designed to be a welcoming home upon the sea on far-flung adventures around the globe, each suite is a statement of ingenuity and high-tech amenities.</p>

			<p>As the world&rsquo;s premier luxury expedition yacht, Crystal Endeavor offers an unrivaled standard of all-inclusive amenities and services. From acclaimed cuisine and the finest wines and spirits to insightful destination enrichment and expert-led conversations, nightly entertainment and myriad options for thrilling discovery ashore.</p>

			<p>The culinary experience aboard Crystal Endeavor is as adventurous as the journey, tempting the senses into a world of extraordinary flavors and discovery. Crystal&rsquo;s award-winning chefs craft Michelin-inspired cuisine with passionate perfection, ensuring the finest ingredients are on hand even in far-off destinations. With all-inclusive dining and open seating in all 6 venues, expert wine sommeliers and an endless pour of acclaimed vintages and premium spirits, each meal is indeed an adventure unto itself.</p>

			<p>From specialties both classic and modern in Waterside to Umi Uma&reg; &amp; the Sushi Bar &ndash; Nobu Matsuhisa&rsquo;s only sea-going restaurant &ndash; you are spoiled for choice.</p>

			<p>Dine at your leisure at the chic and spacious ambience of the elegant open-seating main dining room, Waterside, where intimate tables for two, four and more are set with contemporary elegance, the perfect stage for Crystal&rsquo;s acclaimed cuisine. Savor the Italian inspired cuisine at Prego or indulge your cravings at The Pantry, open 24 hours a day with self-service coffees, teas, wines and more.</p>

			<p>A stunning two-story, glass-enclosed Solarium showcases panoramic views while providing relaxing moments from its pool and Jacuzzi which is transformed at night to an elegant dining venue.</p>

			<p>Wellness is found in the Crystal Life Spa &amp; Salon, with fitness classes, pampering treatments, and a rejuvenating sauna. Stem to stern, Crystal Endeavor&rsquo;s innovative design of social spaces fuels a heightened spirit of adventure.</p>

			<p>Discover the signature venues onboard &ndash; Palm Court lounge, a contemporary elegant space with expansive forward views offers destination and enrichment presentations by day, and cocktails, dancing and entertainment by night. Or enjoy of an intimate lounge for cognacs, cigars and conversation at the Connoisseur Bar.</p>

			<p>Feel the excitement of luxury gaming amidst rare adventure at the Resorts World at Sea&reg; Casino, the only casino on an expedition yacht, complete with a private gaming room and offering favorites like blackjack, roulette and the latest in slot machines.</p>

			<p>Choose to explore with Crystal Endeavor and see the world&rsquo;s most intriguing destinations with extraordinary insight. Each journey is curated to showcase the unique aspects of a particular region, from rugged expeditions to softer, more immersive discoveries of little-explored landscapes and cultural wonders. Let your inner explorer guide you in choosing the voyage that speaks to your own personal sense of adventure.</p>

			<p>Choose from several thoughtfully curated tours for all levels of activity and immersion, from Cultural Discovery voyages &ndash; where you can delve into the cultural heart and iconic wonders of legendary lands and exotic isles to modern-day cities, renowned for their history, art and nature. Or choose to embark on a Remote Expedition, journeying to Earth&rsquo;s most faraway destinations, true expert-led expedition voyages, combining rugged adventure and Zodiac landings with rare discovery, extraordinary wildlife and stunning landscapes few have ever seen.</p>

			<p>Destination Exploration voyages create a deeply immersive landing in rarely-visited destinations &mdash; distant islands and coastal landscapes home to exceptional biodiversity, eco-treasures and wilderness, combined with visits to world-class cities featuring an expedition twist.</p>

			<p>With exclusive, off-the-beaten path itineraries and dozens of immersive Crystal Destination Discoveries&trade;, both complimentary and optional, there are no limits to the freedoms found on these enriching journeys.</p>

			<p>Stop by the Expedition Lounge &amp; Captain&rsquo;s Lounge, dedicated spaces designed to host informative presentations and conversations with the Crystal Endeavor Expedition Team. Plus, a Helicopter Lounge adjacent to the landing pad provides a luxurious space to prepare for aerial explorations aboard the yacht&rsquo;s two helicopters.</p>

			<p>Depending on the region explored, the Expedition Team is comprised of experts ranging from marine biologists and ornithologists to archaeologists and historians, as well as helicopter pilots and Zodiac operators. Throughout each journey, guests enjoy engaging, conversational lectures and daily briefings highlighting key sights and specialized destination information.</p>

			<p>Also enjoy of the 7-person submersible, Zodiacs, kayaks and snorkeling gear, allowing for extraordinary discovery.</p>

			<p>At the very heart of the Crystal Expedition Experience is a team of dedicated professionals chosen for their expertise, personality and shared passion for adventure. Aboard Crystal Endeavor, warm and friendly smiles set the stage for a journey of wondrous discovery, where every learned notion of luxury is anticipated and attended to with genuine virtue and service. With one of the highest staff-to-guest ratios in the industry, each interaction aboard Crystal Endeavor is not only highly personalized, but every detail, large and small, is delivered seamlessly, and always with sincere pleasure.</p>

			<p>Come aboard Crystal Endeavor, Where Luxury Roams Freely&mldr;</p>
		]]></body>

		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/hero/advertorial-01.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Experience Exhilarating and Intrepid Expeditions Aboard Crystal Endeavor&reg; ]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Crystal]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/article/advertorial-01.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Experience Exhilarating and Intrepid Expeditions Aboard Crystal Endeavor&reg; ]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Crystal]]></article_credit>

		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
	</article>
	<!-- END: 2004 CRY -->
</root>
