<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>

	<!-- BEGIN: 2004 cry -->
	<article date="2004" id="01">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[ship]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[April 2020]]></pub_date>
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[04]]></dir_month>
		<file_ship><![CDATA[01]]></file_ship>

		<tab_class><![CDATA[active]]></tab_class>

		<author><![CDATA[Crystal]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[cry]]></id_supplier>
		<translator><![CDATA[]]></translator>

		<title><![CDATA[<strong>Find Your State of Bliss aboard the World&rsquo;s Best&mldr;</strong><br>
		<em>Wish big, it&rsquo;s all included.</em>]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[
			articleTeaser
		]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			<p>Make holiday dreams come true in 2020 on an all-inclusive Crystal Cruise. Follow the sunshine to a collection of Caribbean isle treasures and celebrate the holidays amidst the warmth and welcome of Crystal&rsquo;s personalized service. Join <em>Crystal Serenity<sup>&reg;</sup></em> on a 13-night Holiday Caribbean voyage &ndash; Miami Roundtrip, departing on December 23 &ndash; featuring overnights in St. Marteen, offering extraordinary discovery and excellent value.</p>

			<p>Celebrate traditions of the season aboard the elaborately decorated ship hosting lavish feasts, grand entertainment and dedicated crew and services. Let Crystal curate a masterful journey to suit your individual taste in uncompromising style and luxury, offering heartfelt hospitality, exquisite cuisine and impeccable six-star service, dazzling entertainment and meaningful enrichment programs.</p>
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>2020 marks the beginning of a very exciting time for Crystal with the celebration of their 30th Anniversary and a limited-time collection of featured itineraries that span the globe. The 30th Anniversary collection features 2-for-1 fares, double Crystal Society Savings of 5% and New-to-Crystal Anniversary Savings of 2%, a host of exclusive shipboard events and celebratory gifts, including a special-edition 30th Anniversary Cookbook featuring Crystal&rsquo;s most beloved dishes.</p>

			<p>When Mary Tyler Moore christened Crystal&rsquo;s first ship&mdash;<em>Crystal Harmony<sup>&reg;</sup></em>, in Los Angeles in 1990, the vision was Crystal Clear: to break the mold of traditional cruising and create the very best luxury travel experience. Thirty years later, Crystal is the most trusted luxury cruise brand having earned more <em>Travel + Leisure</em> World&rsquo;s Best accolades than any other cruise line in history. Crystal remains true to its values and closed the decade with a stunning achievement: receiving <em>Cond&eacute; Nast Traveler&rsquo;s</em> Readers&rsquo; Choice Award for <strong>Best Medium Cruise Line</strong>&mdash;for the 26th time&mdash;as well as <strong>Best Small Cruise Line</strong> for Crystal Yacht Cruises and <strong>Best River Cruise Line</strong> for Crystal River Cruises.</p>

			<p>Inherent in the Crystal Experience are the nuanced underpinnings of luxury, both noticeable and discreet. When you step across the threshold of the World&rsquo;s Most Awarded Luxury Cruise Line, you will enjoy a generous roster of all-inclusive amenities and services. From Michelin-inspired cuisine and the finest wines to unique entertainment and an array of options for fitness or solitude, everything you can imagine is already included. A superior standard of service is at the heart of the Crystal Experience, delivered by the most highly awarded staff at sea. Come aboard and let them pamper you.</p>
		]]></body>

		<tab_group id_supplier="cry">
			<tab id="01">
				<id><![CDATA[01]]></id>
				<title><![CDATA[The Ship]]></title> <!-- Le navire -->
				<content><![CDATA[
					<p>Elegant, welcoming and award-winning, <em>Crystal Serenity<sup>&reg;</sup></em> is designed to explore the world in supreme comfort. With no more than 980 guests on-board at a time, <em>Crystal Serenity</em> elevates the very essence of ocean travel and luxury service. Days at sea allow time to pursue your personal interests with guilt-free abandon, enjoying myriad options for enrichment, entertainment and wellness. Traveling in beautifully appointed staterooms and suites, you&rsquo;ll also be treated to acclaimed cuisine, fine wines and spirits and an unsurpassed standard of genuine hospitality.</p>

					<p>Commanding the world&rsquo;s great oceans, <em>Crystal Serenity</em> enchants with unrivaled chic elegance. She welcomes travelers with her own celebrated design and inviting social spaces including new suites, more alternative dining venues and free, unlimited Wi-Fi. The unique design allows for some of the industry&rsquo;s highest service and space ratios, with exclusive amenities aboard, including Umi Uma<sup>&reg;</sup> by Nobu Matsuhisa and a Brazilian Churrascaria.</p>
				]]></content>
				<tab_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/article/ship-01-ship.jpg</tab_src>
				<tab_caption><![CDATA[The Ship]]></tab_caption>
				<class><![CDATA[active]]></class> <!-- The first tab has the 'active' class -->
			</tab>

			<tab id="02">
				<id><![CDATA[02]]></id>
				<title><![CDATA[Accommodations]]></title> <!-- Hebergement -->
				<content><![CDATA[
					<p>Lose yourself in elegant comfort. Expansive and gorgeous, butler-serviced suites and penthouses are the perfect place to call home for the holidays. And whether you choose to travel in a suite or a stateroom, you&rsquo;ll discover all the comforts of home, Penthouse suites and above are accompanied by the attentive service of a 24-hour personal butler to enhance your journey. Butler services include packing and unpacking, pressing and laundry, in-suite dining, reservations for shore excursions, spa and specialty restaurants.</p>

					<p>Live and dine in the gorgeous suites, where you can relax or socialize in the comfort of your well-appointed living room. Each sanctuary envelops you in splendid comfort and calm, with all that you need at your fingertips. From state-of-the-art technologies and interactive 24&rdquo; TVs to a variety of reading diversions and a well-personalized mini bar.  </p>

					<p>Enjoy Plush beds wrapped in the finest of linens, in a splendid master bedroom of dreamy queen-size beds, with private access to the expansive verandah. </p>

					<p>Beautiful, spacious bathrooms allow for all the conveniences of home. Including his &amp; her walk-in closets, a lavish master bath Jacuzzi, with stunning ocean views, bench and even a separate guest bath with discreet entry, now featuring French skincare Caudalie in-suite amenities.</p>

					<p>From your own private window to the world discover the enchanted wonder of new destinations each day.</p>
				]]></content>
				<tab_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/article/ship-01-accommodations.jpg</tab_src>
				<tab_caption><![CDATA[Accommodations]]></tab_caption>
				<class><![CDATA[]]></class>
			</tab>

			<tab id="03">
				<id><![CDATA[03]]></id>
				<title><![CDATA[Dining]]></title> <!-- Gastronomie -->
				<content><![CDATA[
					<p>With a focus on purity, quality and creativity, the culinary journey aboard each Crystal Experience transcends mere excellence and enters the sublime. This is especially so on the holiday voyages as lavish feasts are prepared to celebrate tradition, but always with an eye on innovation. From the sophisticated luxury of open-seating dining or the elegant simplicity of Afternoon Tea to 24-hour in-suite dining, an indulgent variety of choices appeals to every palate and mood.</p>

					<p>Inspired and innovative, an extraordinary culinary experience is enjoyed in an array of elegant, open-seating venues. From specialties both classic and modern in Waterside to Chef Nobu Matsuhisa&rsquo;s signature delicacies at Umi Uma &amp; the Sushi Bar &ndash;Nobu&rsquo;s only sea-going restaurant &ndash; you are spoiled for choice with up to 12 dining options. </p>

					<p>Dine at your leisure at the chic and spacious ambience of the elegant open-seating main dining room, Waterside, where intimate tables for two, four and more are set with contemporary elegance, the perfect stage for Crystal&rsquo;s acclaimed cuisine.</p>

					<p>Savor the Italian inspired cuisine at Prego or our exquisite Churrascaria Brazilian steakhouse, offering succulent cuts, ceviche and delicious Caipirinhas.</p>

					<p>Elevate your experience with the wine tastings and lectures by day and enjoy a perfectly wine-paired dinner at the Vintage Room at night prepared by the sommelier and featuring some of the rarest vintages in the world.</p>

					<p>Enjoy dining on cuisine that is created with passion for perfection and a zest for creativity all prepared using the freshest ingredients.</p>
				]]></content>
				<tab_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/article/ship-01-dining.jpg</tab_src>
				<tab_caption><![CDATA[Dining]]></tab_caption>
				<class><![CDATA[]]></class>
			</tab>

			<tab id="04">
				<id><![CDATA[04]]></id>
				<title><![CDATA[Activities]]></title> <!-- Activites -->
				<content><![CDATA[
					<p>The twilight hour aboard </m>Crystal Serenity</em> arrives with an air of anticipation and excitement &ndash; perhaps even more so during the holidays as the ship is decorated for the season and everything takes on a celebratory glow. Aperitifs and pre-dinner dancing are enjoyed in lounges, and dinner itself is an event rather than a meal. From elaborate Broadway-inspired shows to the intimate settings of the Piano Bar, the feeling is one of joyous, carefree and easy luxury.</p>

					<p>Choice is a defining characteristic of the Crystal Experience and it is said that time is among the greatest luxuries, where on sea days aboard <em>Crystal Serenity</em>, you will have plenty to pursue your passions and engage in exciting activities. From wellness classes, casinos, theatre to shopping venues, you can experience and array entertaining activities that will enhance your journey.</p>

					<p>Further your knowledge through enrichment workshops featuring thought leaders, world-class experts and lecturers. Learn a new skill or simply listen to a book reading from your favorite author. Or Fuel your spirit at a state-of-the-art fitness center, invigorate your mind with complimentary yoga, mat Pilates and more. Try personal training or find your bliss at the Feng Shui-inspired Crystal Life Spa.</p>

					<p>Peruse your interest or find a new hobby with progressive classes and workshops on a variety of topics &ndash; from wellness and wine to finance and art &ndash; allow you to follow your passions during your travels. Under expert tutelage, gather with new friends in this state-of-the-art, dedicated space to learn new things &ndash; about the world and about yourself.</p>

					<p>Discover the Avenue of the Stars. From exquisite jewels and high fashion to treasured mementos and resort wear, the boutiques and shops along the Avenue of the Stars feature selections from brands that find a familiar home in a sophisticated yet understated environment.</p>

					<p>Tap your inner explorer to engage in Crystal Destination Discoveries<sup>&reg;</sup> ashore. Active, leisurely and enriching, each is curated to showcase a destination in a manner that best appeals to your own sense of discovery and adventure. Choose from several thoughtfully orchestrated tours for all levels of activity and immersion, including Active Adventures like snorkeling and scuba diving in St. Lucia or an Island Safari adventure in Barbados to exploring Fortress National Park in St. Kitts and experiencing its scenic National Railway and so much more. For guests wishing to explore independently, Crystal Cruises also offers a private vehicle service and English-speaking guide.</p>

					<p>Also available, is the complimentary &ldquo;You Care. We Care.&rdquo; Voluntourism Adventures, which gives you the opportunity to improve the well-being of the people and places you visit.</p>
				]]></content>
				<tab_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/article/ship-01-activities.jpg</tab_src>
				<tab_caption><![CDATA[Activities]]></tab_caption>
				<class><![CDATA[]]></class>
			</tab>

			<tab id="05">
				<id><![CDATA[05]]></id>
				<title><![CDATA[Family]]></title> <!-- Famille -->
				<content><![CDATA[
					<p>With its dedicated spaces and acclaimed, age-specific children&rsquo;s programs for kids ages 3 to 17, Crystal is the luxury cruise line best suited for family travel during the holidays.</p>

					<p>Fantasia welcomes children ages 3-12, with games, crafts, popular Sony PlayStation<sup>&reg;</sup> and Xbox 360<sup>&trade;</sup> kiosks and large-screen televisions, board games and personal computers with entertainment and education. </p>

					<p>Waves, Uber-trendy, this &quot;teens only&quot; hang-out features Casalina chairs and Marimekko-patterned Fatboy bean bags. A video arcade keeps teens ages 13-17 entertained with Wii, PlayStation<sup>&reg;</sup>, Xbox, Kinect, wide-screen TVs and more.</p>

					<p><strong>CUISINE KIDS LOVE</strong></p>

					<p>Kids of all ages can enjoy the Junior Cruiser&apos;s menu, and the chefs are always pleased to prepare custom dishes. The Trident Grill serves complimentary hot dogs, hamburgers, pizza and more&mldr; and there&rsquo;s always Scoops Ice Cream Bar!</p>

					<p>In-room babysitting services for children 1 year and older are available on a first-come, first-served basis. Arrangements can be made through the Concierge and fees do apply.</p>
				]]></content>
				<tab_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/article/ship-01-family.jpg</tab_src>
				<tab_caption><![CDATA[Family]]></tab_caption>
				<class><![CDATA[]]></class>
			</tab>

			<tab id="06">
				<id><![CDATA[06]]></id>
				<title><![CDATA[Services]]></title> <!-- Services -->
				<content><![CDATA[
					<p>The cornerstone of the Crystal Experience<sup>&reg;</sup> is an exceptional standard of service provided by the most genuinely gracious staff at sea. Where attention to detail is crafted to every aspect of the journey, curated to cater the most ambitious, curious and adventurous spirits.</p>

					<p>Imagine returning home with a personalized movie of your trek through your favorite destinations, a digital photo documentary of your explorations and even your own daily blog. With free 24-hour Wi-Fi/Internet access, you can do it all. Working on 27&quot; Apple Macintosh computers, Crystal&rsquo;s team of experts offers complimentary instruction on topics ranging from basic computer skills on e-mail, Word, Excel to advanced digital photo finishing and website design at the Computer University at Sea.</p>

					<p>Beyond ships of award-winning design and a cuisine of Michelin-level envy, more than entertainment options on board and the enriching discoveries ashore&mldr; the very essence of Crystal lies within its people, professionals chosen for their winning personalities and dedication to service excellence. With industry-leading staff-to-guest service ratios, and a genuine concern for your complete happiness, the intangible luxury of superb service is likely to be among the greatest gifts you&rsquo;ll enjoy on a holiday cruise with Crystal.</p>
				]]></content>
				<tab_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/article/ship-01-services.jpg</tab_src>
				<tab_caption><![CDATA[Services]]></tab_caption>
				<class><![CDATA[]]></class>
			</tab>
		</tab_group>

		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/hero/ship-01.jpg</hero_src>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/04/article/ship-01.jpg</article_src>

		<tile_color>005DAB</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
	</article>
	<!-- END: 2004 cry -->
</root>
