<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2012">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[insider]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[December 2020]]></pub_date>
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[12]]></dir_month>
		
		<author><![CDATA[articleAuthor]]></author>
		<translator><![CDATA[]]></translator>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Book Your Bucket List with Globus family of brands]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[
			Discover the sights you must see, people you must meet, and experiences you must have.
		]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			With the new year just around the corner, many of us are dreaming about our travel goals for 2021 and even 2022. After a year full of cancelled plans and trips put on hold, we’re eager to pack up our suitcase and head off to somewhere exciting! With that in mind, we decided to chat with Stephanie Bishop, Managing Director of Globus family of brands, to find out how travelers can make their vacation dreams a reality.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p class="question"><strong>Q:</strong> Tell us a bit about Globus family of brands and what you offer.</p>
			<p>For more than 90 years, the Globus family of brands has greeted the most fascinating places around the world with unmatched intrigue, curiosity and wonder. Along the way, we&rsquo;ve discovered the sights travelers must see, encountered the people they must meet, engaged in the customs to try, and indulged in the cuisine to taste byway of touring vacations with Globus and Cosmos; Avalon Waterways&rsquo; river cruises, and on-your-own adventures from Monograms. From the world&rsquo;s heart-pumping cosmopolitan cities to heartwarming &ldquo;undiscovered&rdquo; towns, it is our greatest passion to share the joys we&rsquo;ve uncovered with travelers.</p>
			<p class="question"><strong>Q:</strong> For travelers ready to book their long-awaited bucket list trip, what do you recommend?</p>
			<p>There&rsquo;s no better time than today to pin, plot and plan the next getaway, including to bucket list destinations. We never know what the future will hold, but with our Peace of Mind Plan, we make it easy &ndash; and risk-free &ndash; for travelers to book dream destinations &ndash; and itineraries &ndash; now.</p>
			<p>The Globus family of brands goes beyond the guidebooks, beyond the expected, and well beyond the cobblestone streets of Europe to lead travelers to the wonders and joys of all seven continents &ndash; including the rainforests of South America, the national parks of North America, the Outback of Australia, the savannas of Africa, the neon-lit streets of Asia and even the icebergs of Antarctica. With an offering of more than 200 vacations to 68 countries, travelers can enjoy and explore almost anywhere in the world with a name they can count on. And, with an eye on ever-evolving travel trends, we&rsquo;re always adding new vacations to fulfill the bucket lists of tomorrow.</p>
			<p class="question"><strong>Q:</strong> For North American travelers looking to stay closer to home, what domestic options do you provide?</p>
			<p>It isn&rsquo;t necessary to cross oceans for adventure when there&rsquo;s so much to discover in Canada and the United States. Between North America&rsquo;s breathtaking national parks, cool emerging cities and tiny, historic towns, there&rsquo;s a surplus of sights travelers haven&rsquo;t seen &ndash; or truly experienced &ndash; in their own backyard.</p>
			<p>For 2021, we have increased our domestic offerings with Globus and Cosmos, including unveiling a new series of &ldquo;Undiscovered&rdquo; tours. On our &ldquo;Undiscovered North America&rdquo; vacations, we will take globetrotters down the less-traveled highways, legendary lanes, and scenic country roads to the special places and parks other tour companies don&rsquo;t visit. This NEW &ldquo;Undiscovered North America&rdquo; series includes five (5) NEW tours from both Globus and Cosmos as well as other popular getaways:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>NEW! Globus <em>Bourbon, Bridles &amp; Bluegrass </em>(8 days)</li>
				<li>NEW! Globus <em>Southern California Charms </em>(10 days)</li>
				<li>NEW! Globus <em>New England &amp; The Hudson Valley </em>(10 days)</li>
				<li>NEW! Cosmos <em>Exploring the Pacific Northwest </em>(9 days)</li>
				<li>Globus <em>Qu</em><em>&eacute;</em><em>bec In Depth with the Gasp</em><em>&eacute;</em><em> Peninsula </em>(11 days)</li>
				<li>Cosmos <em>Alaska &amp; the Yukon </em>(12 days)</li>
				<li>Cosmos <em>Historic Trails &amp; Blue Ridge Mountains </em>(14 days)</li>
				<li>Cosmos <em>Western Canada with Inside Passage </em>(13 days)</li>
			</ul>
			<p>For Canadians interested in Canada-only touring vacations, some of our favorites include:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Globus <em>Great Resorts of the Canadian Rockies </em>(7 days)</li>
				<li>Globus <em>Wonders of the Maritimes &amp; Scenic Cape Breton </em>(9 days)</li>
				<li>Globus <em>Newfoundland &amp; Labrador </em>(12 days)</li>
				<li>Globus <em>Great Canadian Rail Journey </em>(14 days)</li>
				<li>Cosmos <em>Ontario &amp; French Canada </em>(8 days)</li>
				<li>Cosmos <em>Heart of the Canadian Rockies </em>(10 days)</li>
			</ul>
			<p>In short, we have dozens of incredible vacations available for travelers wanting to explore the world closer to home. We have also unveiled a handful of off-season city getaways from Monograms for 2021, including 3-night stays in New Orleans, Nashville, San Diego and San Francisco.</p>
			<p class="question"><strong>Q:</strong> For travelers looking to have big experiences but with a smaller crowd, what do you recommend?</p>
			<p>In 2021, Globus and Cosmos are delivering big experiences for small groups. With Small-Group Discovery tours, we&rsquo;re making it easier than ever to explore the globe without the rest of the world in North America, Europe, Central and South America, Asia, Africa and select departures in the South Pacific. With an average of just 24 guests per tour departure, Small-Group Discoveries promise room to roam while getting up-close and personal with fascinating places.</p>
			<p class="question"><strong>Q:</strong> For travelers looking to travel privately, what are their options?</p>
			<p>Designed for parties from two to two dozen, Globus&rsquo; Private Touring program invites travelers to enjoy the benefits of taking a European tour, while handpicking their travel companions. Whether they&rsquo;re interested in gathering a party of friends for an overdue reunion or are planning a multigenerational family affair, both Globus and Cosmos Private Tours in Europe invite travelers to enjoy the journey in a new, more intimate way with a dedicated Tour Director, private transportation and local guides, VIP sightseeing and greater flexibility.</p>
			<p>Monograms also offers small group and private travel options across the globe, including Africa, Asia, South and Central America, and the South Pacific. For instance, travelers can choose private safaris in Kenya, Tanzania and South Africa with Monograms or fly south for incredible getaways in Costa Rica, Brazil and Peru where they may find themselves on their own or with a very small group of like-minded travelers.</p>
			<p><em>How have your offerings changed in response to the COVID-19 pandemic?</em></p>
			<p>The world has changed, but what remains certain is the Globus family of brands&rsquo; commitment to guest safety and peace-of-mind while traveling, including offering travelers worry-free, hassle-free and strings-free bookings with a <a href="https://www.globusjourneys.com/peace-of-mind/"><strong>Peace of Mind Travel Plan</strong></a><strong>. </strong>While on a trip, travelers can also enjoy many enhanced health and safety protocols with the company&rsquo;s new <a href="https://www.globusjourneys.com/on-trip-assurance/"><strong>On-Trip</strong><strong>Assurance</strong></a> program</p>
			<p>Leaving nothing to chance, our Global Health &amp; Safety Team has established <a href="https://www.globusjourneys.com/user/images/protocols.pdf"><strong>on-trip protocols</strong></a> that focus on travelers&rsquo; health and safety as well as the overall travel experience, including:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Pre-trip health screenings and temperature checks, plus daily health checks</li>
				<li>Social distancing whenever possible, thanks in part to Globus Go Beyond Devices</li>
				<li>Wearing masks when not social distancing isn&rsquo;t a possibility</li>
				<li>Touch-free meals (no self-service options at hotels or alike)</li>
				<li>Enhanced cleaning and disinfection standards and protocols at hand-picked hotels</li>
			</ul>
			<p>We have also used this &ldquo;time out&rdquo; to unveil more Small-Group Discovery tours worldwide and &ldquo;Undiscovered&rdquo; vacations in North America.</p>
			<p class="question"><strong>Q:</strong> BONUS: Why should travelers choose to travel with Globus family of brands?</p>
			<p>It&rsquo;s time to look forward to a day better than yesterday, to step away from everyday stresses and anticipate memories that await in new destinations &ndash; near or far. The Globus family of brands offers six safe and amazing ways to explore the world in 2021:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Off-Season Escapes thanks to our Escapes by Globus program: Vacations featuring lower temperatures, fewer crowds and better deals</li>
				<li>Private Touring options in Europe</li>
				<li>Small-Group Discoveries worldwide</li>
				<li>Off-the-Beaten-Path Adventures with our &ldquo;Undiscovered&rdquo; series of vacations in North America, Italy, the United Kingdom and the Mediterranean</li>
				<li>Boutique-style cruising with Avalon Waterways</li>
				<li>On-your-own experiences and customizable vacations with Monograms</li>
			</ul>
			<p>When the world is ready, we&rsquo;re ready to deliver the world &ndash; in a way, and at a pace, that fits travelers.</p>
			
			<br>
			
			<p style="font-size: 75%;">Image Credit: Globus family of brands / Cosmos</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/12/hero/insider.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Book Your Bucket List with Globus family of brands]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[On Location]]></hero_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/12/article/insider.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Book Your Bucket List with Globus family of brands]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[On Location]]></article_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<email_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/12/email/insider.jpg</email_src>
		
		<tile_color>FA6900</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="escorted-tours"><![CDATA[escorted-tours]]></tag>
			<tag slug="independent-travel"><![CDATA[independent-travel]]></tag>
			<tag slug="river-cruising"><![CDATA[river-cruising]]></tag>
			<tag slug="adventure"><![CDATA[adventure]]></tag>
			<tag slug="family-vacations"><![CDATA[family-vacations]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>
