<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	​
	<article date="2006" id="01">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[June 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- June = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[06]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[01]]></id_article>
		​
		<author><![CDATA[Le Boat]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[lbt]]></id_supplier>
		​
		<title><![CDATA[Le Boat: Leaders in Canal Boating and a Safer Choice for a Staycation This Summer]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Le Boat]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Now is the perfect time to consider a private boating holiday. No previous boat experience or boat license required. Perfect for those looking to get away from the crowds, explore nature and create an amazing holiday you will always remember.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/06/article/advertorial-01-01.jpg">
			</figure>
			
			<h4>Who is Le Boat?</h4>
			<p>Le Boat is a leader in canal boat rentals in Europe with more than 50 years of experience in the industry. With 950 boats stationed across a network of over 37 different departure bases in 8 European countries, Le Boat arrived in Canada in 2018 and now has a local fleet of 24 boats available for rental on <strong>Ontario&rsquo;s UNESCO World Heritage Rideau Canal.</strong></p>
			<h4><strong>No previous boating experience or boat license required.</strong></h4>
			<p>All Le Boat cruises are custom built to be easy to operate - if you can drive a car, you can drive a Le Boat cruiser rental. Le Boat teaches you how to captain your boat at your own pace on a flexible itinerary while sleeping on board. Travelers can choose a 3-5 night short boating break or a 7-10+ night vacation. All of Le Boat luxury boat rentals come with a fully equipped kitchen, fresh linens and bedding, and top deck sun deck.&nbsp;</p>
			<h4><strong>Is it safe to travel on a Le Boat post isolation restrictions?</strong></h4>
			<p>The safety of staff and customers is of utmost importance to Le Boat. All boats are thoroughly cleaned at the end of each use and the company has introduced additional cleaning and social distancing measure for extra protection while following Ontario&rsquo;s new Health and Safety Guidelines as they begin to reopen the economy.</p>
			<p>On the heels of the Government announcements and loosen travel restrictions, Le Boat, is preparing to welcome guests this summer when Parks Canada opens the <strong>UNESCO World Heritage Rideau Canal</strong> on <strong>June 1, 2020</strong>.</p>
			<p>&ldquo;Once it's safe to travel again, we believe that Le Boat is an ideal option for those looking to vacation closer to home this summer,&rdquo; said Lisa Mclean, North American Marketing Manager for Le Boat. &ldquo;Being on your own private cruiser allows you to sleep on board, set your own schedule, plan your own route and control your environment - you determine where you stop and whom you interact with, while you explore the beautiful and historic Rideau waterway.&rdquo;</p>
			<p>Le Boat luxury houseboat rentals are built for the novice boater in mind. With no previous boating experience or boating license required, anyone can captain their own Le Boat.</p>
			<p>&ldquo;Le Boat makes it as easy for people to be able to get outdoors and have an amazing getaway, all while exploring one of Ontario&rsquo;s best keep secrets ,&rdquo; said Mclean. &ldquo;If you can drive a car you can drive one of our boats, plus we provide you with suggested itineraries for a 3-5 night short break or 7-10+ night vacation. And with a fleet of 24 premier Horizon Cruises (five model sizes sleeping from 2-12 people) you can pick a boat that fits your party size and budget.&rdquo;</p>
			<h4><strong>Get away from the city and crowds to the wide-open spaces of the UNESCO Rideau Canal, Ontario</strong></h4>
			<p>The Rideau Canal is most famous for being the Guinness World Record holder of the world&rsquo;s largest skating rink in the winter but did you know that from May &ndash; October it transforms into a spectacular waterway of private islands, sandy beaches, protected wetlands, bookended by two vibrant cities and peppered with small, artisan villages along the way.&nbsp;</p>
			<p>The 202km of continuous waterway stretches from Kingston to Ottawa and is a vast network of pristine lakes, winding rivers and canals, all connected by a historical lock system.</p>
			<p>&ldquo;Cruising the Rideau by boat is the quintessential Canadian holiday,&rdquo; said Mclean, &ldquo;After this long period at home, this will allow people an opportunity to get away from it all &ndash; go off the beaten track with family &amp; friends without the worries of being in the busiest tourist areas the whole time. They can choose to visit the city, or stick to the small villages,&rdquo; She added. &ldquo;Le Boat offers a chance to relax and see new sights from the comforts of your own private yacht.&rdquo;</p>
			<h4><strong>Travel in comfort and style </strong></h4>
			<p>Le Boat&rsquo;s range of watercraft offers you everything you need for a comfortable stay on the water including a fully equipped kitchen, and private en-suite bathrooms with showers in every cabin. Spacious interior, top deck &ldquo;fun deck&rdquo; with sun shade and BBQ, making for the perfect setting to relax or stargaze with the family or group of friends.</p>
			<p>A private houseboat vacation is ideal for outdoor activities. One can enjoy a BBQ &amp; summer cocktail from the top deck at sunset, or enjoy fishing, kayaking, biking, swimming, or a hike on one of the many trails in the area.</p>
			<p>&ldquo;Sit back, relax, listen to the music and enjoy a fresh summer breeze from the comfort of the lounge chair, while you take in the breathtaking scenery as you cruise the Rideau Canal,&rdquo; says Mclean. &ldquo;We expect that once some of the restrictions have been lifted, people will take advantage of a Le Boat cruiser rental to create their own unforgettable vacation that they will remember for a lifetime.&rdquo;</p>
			<h4><strong>Be Safe and Go Boating with Confidence </strong></h4>
			<p>Le Boat thoroughly cleans each vessel at the end of each use. Additionally in preparation for when isolation restrictions are eased and for extra protection and the safety of customers and staff, they have introduced extra cleaning and social distancing measures. Le Boat has also stepped up in these uncertain times to offer booking terms that are as flexible as possible. You can book with confidence with Le Boat, knowing that you can cancel up <strong>to 48 hours</strong> prior to departure with their Go Boating with Confidence policy.</p>
			<h4><strong>This year for summer 2020 or next in 2021</strong></h4>
			<p>Whether you are ready to travel this year or next, Le Boat&rsquo;s 2021 season is also on sale now.</p>
			<p>Contact your travel advisor for the most up-to-date offers for both 2020 and 2021 departures.</p>
		]]></body>
		​
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		​
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/06/hero/advertorial-01.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Le Boat: Leaders in Canal Boating and a Safer Choice for a Staycation This Summer]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Le Boat]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/06/article/advertorial-01.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Le Boat: Leaders in Canal Boating and a Safer Choice for a Staycation This Summer]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Le Boat]]></article_credit>
		​
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
	​</article>
	
	<article date="2006" id="02">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[June 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- Mmm = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[06]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[02]]></id_article>
		​
		<author><![CDATA[Insight Vacations]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[ins]]></id_supplier>
		​
		<title><![CDATA[Discover Insight Vacations new series of trips created for women, by women]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Insight Vacations]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Cast aside your inhibitions and indulge your wanderlust on journeys that will connect you with other cultures, communities and companions.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>Insight Vacations is launching the first trip in our new series, Wander Women journeys. Join a diverse group of women travellers from all over the world on journeys that will immerse you in the local culture through unique Insight Experiences that reflect a wide range of interests.</p>
			<h4>#MakeTravelMatter</h4>
			<p>Did you know that the tourism industry supports empowering women all around the world? From community initiatives to small enterprises, collectives, and local businesses, tourism offers women the opportunity for economic advancement and self-sustainability. It also connects people all over the world with unique experiences that show us the perspectives of different cultures.</p>
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/06/article/advertorial-02-01.jpg">
			</figure>
			
			<p>Our proud female leadership team at Insight Vacations has worked to create itineraries that inspire women to travel together, enjoy unique experiences, and empower local women and their communities through sustainable tourism.</p>
			<h4>Discover our first wander women trip</h4>
			<p>For women travelers in search of new experiences, this soul-enriching journey inspires you to discover the beauty of India in the company of other women travelers from around the world.</p>
			<p>Explore India&rsquo;s majestic forts, monuments, and temples, its bustling bazaars filled with exquisite crafts, the beautiful landscapes and natural reserves, and above all else, the people and culture that make this place so special.</p>
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/06/article/advertorial-02-02.jpg">
			</figure>

			<p>On this journey, you&rsquo;ll appreciate the ancient traditions and modern innovations as we reveal India to you from the perspective of local people, including many inspiring women who are leaders in their communities.</p>
			<p>As a founding member of the non-profit TreadRight Foundation, Insight Vacations is committed to supporting the people, planet, and wildlife through responsible and mindful tourism practices.</p>
			<p>It&rsquo;s easy to travel sustainably. Are you willing to join us in our mission to #MakeTravelMatter? <a href="https://youtu.be/mkBQMdPebwY" target="_blank">Get a preview</a></p>
		]]></body>
		​
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		​
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/06/hero/advertorial-02.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Discover Insight Vacations new series of trips created for women, by women]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Insight Vacations]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/06/article/advertorial-02.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Discover Insight Vacations new series of trips created for women, by women]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Insight Vacations]]></article_credit>
		​
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
	</article>
	​
</root>
