<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2103" id="03">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[March 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- March = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[03]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[03]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Hurtigruten]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[hur]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[With Hurtigruten, Wellness is Well-Rounded]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[At Hurtigruten, we believe that wellness includes our planet, our communities, our bodies, and our minds.]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Over the past decade we have sought to become an environmentally responsible company, dedicated to sustainability and to protecting the precious habitats across our Earth. Now we are turning our attention to our individual wellness.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>Hurtigruten&rsquo;s Wellness Program was launched in 2019 to integrate activities that encourage physical, mental, and spiritual wellbeing on board our ships, adding to our existing excursions and expeditions that focus on connecting with nature. You will now find yoga, meditation, fitness, tai chi, art, music, massage, nutrition, and other wellness activities on selected voyages. At Hurtigruten, we believe that wellness includes our planet, our communities, our bodies, and our minds. We look forward to helping you to achieve a healthier and more natural lifestyle during our voyages.</p>
			
			<br/>
			<br/>

			<figure class="article-tile">
			<h4>Hurtigruten’s Sustainable, Hybrid Electric-Powered Expedition Ships</h4>
			<p>Learn about how you’ll enjoy a well-rounded wellness experience aboard Hurtigruten’s newest hybrid electric-powered expedition ships.</p>
			<iframe width="100%" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FGjep_mPR8I?rel=0" style="width: 100%; min-height: 500px;" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
			</figure>
			
			<br/>
			<br/>
			
			<h3>WELLNESS FOR OUR PLANET</h3>
			<p>As the world leader in expedition cruises, Hurtigruten has come a long way since first getting its start on the Norwegian coast 128 years ago.</p>
			<p>With the launch of the world&rsquo;s first custom-built hybrid electric-powered expedition ships, MS Roald Amundsen and MS Fridtjof Nansen, Hurtigruten leads the way in innovative technology for green and clean exploration to some of the most remote and spectacular coastlines on Earth.</p>
			<p>Each vessel is equipped with large battery packs, feature innovative green technology, and use electric propulsion to reduce fuel emissions by 20% &mdash;allowing guests to sail more quietly than ever before. These expedition ships are truly the first of their kind and take environmentally conscious expedition cruising to a new level.</p>
			<p>Hurtigruten has a great responsibility, which is incorporated into our mission to provide safe, unique, active, and sustainable travel experiences that create lifelong memories. To ensure the guests of tomorrow have the same travel experiences as the guests of today, we work hard to minimize the impact of our operations and promote sustainable innovation in the destinations we visit, by: supporting local communities; ensuring responsible consumption and production with the global partners we collaborate with; urgently combating climate change; and conserving the use of the oceans, seas, and marine resources for sustainable development.</p>
			<p>In fact, Hurtigruten was the first major travel company to remove single-use plastic from all of our ships, restaurants, and hotels. These areas are where we believe we can have the most positive impact as a cruise-ship industry leader and on society as a whole, both now and in the future.</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-03-01.jpg">
			</figure>

			<br/>
			<br/>

			<h3>WELLNESS FOR THE LOCAL COMMUNITIES WE VISIT</h3>
			<p>A Hurtigruten cruise is a journey for all your senses. Our chefs create superb dining from sustainable local and regionally-sourced produce, adding a delicious dimension to your travel.</p>
			<p>To tantalize your taste buds, our team of talented onboard chefs create sumptuous multi-course meals. Whether you choose to dine in the main onboard restaurant or upscale to the &agrave; la carte fine dining option, you&rsquo;ll find the cuisine varied, inspired, and downright delicious.</p>
			<p><strong>Cultural Cuisine <br /></strong>Exploration is about opening our minds to new customs, our eyes to new landscapes, and, yes, our mouths to new tastes. Our chefs may utilize unique herbs and spices or adopt traditional cooking techniques from the area, all to add authentic, local gastronomy to the meals they prepare for you on board. You can also expect some favorite Norwegian recipes on the menu, handed down through generations and a fitting homage to our long sea-faring heritage.</p>
			<p><strong>Local Flavors<br /></strong>Our chefs craft dishes that reflect the cuisine of the region we are sailing in, immersing you in the culture even more.</p>
			<p><strong>Plant-based<br /></strong>A range of tasty plant-based dishes are integrated as essential options into all of our menus.</p>
			<p><strong>Regional Suppliers<br /></strong>Sourcing food along the way helps to cut down the energy needed to transport ingredients and has the added benefit of supporting local small-scale suppliers.</p>
			<p><strong>Inspirational Lectures<br /></strong>The Expedition Team deliver themed lectures on how food and sustainability go hand in hand and often organize tasting sessions out on deck and during landings.</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-03-02.jpg">
			</figure>
			
			<br/>
			<br/>
			
			<h3>WELLNESS FOR OUR BODIES AND MINDS</h3>
			<p>A Hurtigruten expedition cruise features superb onboard facilities designed to help you stay active and rejuvenate for the next</p>
			<p>day&rsquo;s adventures in our Wellness Center. Aboard our new hybrid electric-powered ships, you can work out in our indoor gym and indulge in luxurious spa treatments as you explore.</p>
			
			<br/>
			
			<h4>Stay in Shape &ndash; Inside and Out</h4>
			<p><strong>Training with scenery<br /></strong>Tone up in our indoor gym, featuring rowing machines, fitness bikes, training stations, and free weights. Or enjoy our outdoor gym and the outdoor running track where you can work out in fresh air while watching beautiful scenery glide by. In warm waters, many of the voyages will offer daily yoga, tai chi, and meditation classes with a professional instructor on the outdoor decks, providing an opportunity for an inner journey as well.</p>
			
			<br/>
			
			<h4>A Wealth of Recreational Possibilities</h4>
			<p>Our expedition cruises are dedicated to satisfying all your senses. In the Wellness Center, you will find highly trained massage therapists ready to welcome you to a wide variety of relaxing services and treatments, designed to help you recover, relax and rejuvenate.</p>
			<p><strong>Rejuvenate and Refresh<br /></strong>After an exciting day of exploration or during a peaceful day at sea, there&rsquo;s nothing like indulging in a relaxing massage or treatment. Let our well-trained therapists welcome you to a luxurious and healthful experience, such as an aromatherapy body massage, a tension release treatment for your arms and feet, or the specially created Hurtigruten Signature treatment.</p>
			<p><strong>Sauna<br /></strong>The elegant onboard sauna features panoramic windows.</p>
			<p><strong>Indulge yourself in spectacular waters</strong><br>
			<p>Swim, soak, and truly relax among some of the most sublime scenery on Earth. Soak in the infinity pool or in one of two hot tubs, offering amazing views of glaciers, icebergs and wildlife.</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-03-03.jpg">
			</figure>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/hero/advertorial-03.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[With Hurtigruten, Wellness is Well-Rounded]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Hurtigruten]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-03.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[With Hurtigruten, Wellness is Well-Rounded]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Hurtigruten]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>
