<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2103" id="01">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[March 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- Mmm = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[03]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[01]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Celebrity Cruises]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[cel]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Celebrity's Galapagos Adventures: Untouched, Unspoiled, Unbelievable]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Disconnect and immerse yourself in The Galapagos Islands. Celebrity Cruises ensures all details are taken care of from shore excursions to luxurious accommodations.]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Located 600 miles off the coast of Ecuador, this archipelago of unspoiled, isolated islands will welcome you with its rugged charms and evolutionary wonders. Consisting of 19 islands and 42 islets that all rose from the sea as the product of volcanic eruptions, these islands are between 3 million and 4 million years old.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<br/>
			
			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 60px 0;">
				<h4>Destination Galapagos</h4>
				<p>Located 600 miles off the coast of Ecuador, this archipelago of unspoiled, isolated islands will welcome you with its rugged charms and evolutionary wonders.</p>
				<iframe width="100%" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/8UIE3Ln2kIY?rel=0" style="width: 100%; min-height: 500px;" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
			</figure>
			
			<p>Completely oceanic&mdash;meaning they&rsquo;ve never been connected to the mainland&mdash;the Galapagos Islands are truly a world apart. Settlers have carved out their lives on the lava rocks, pirates have profited, and scientists have explored. The history of the Galapagos is rich and diverse, with tales of basic survival and extraordinary discovery. For almost any modern adventurer, a journey through time to the Galapagos Islands is a dream vacation.</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 40px 0;">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-01-01.jpg">
			</figure>
			
			<p>The animals of the Galapagos are unlike any others on earth. Apart from having no natural fear of humans, they evolved in entirely unique manners, which are on full display daily for you to see. This includes enormous 100-year-old Galapagos giant tortoises, free-diving marine iguanas, the beautiful and animated blue-footed boobies, and a host of other exotic fauna found nowhere else on earth.</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 40px 0;">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-01-02.jpg">
			</figure>
			
			<p>A trip to the Galapagos Islands is so unique and full of monumental experiences that we don&rsquo;t want you to waste a single moment thinking about logistics or details. Our Galapagos adventures are blissfully all-inclusive, worry-free, and well-planned, right down to the last detail. So you can immerse yourself in centuries-old landscapes, catch rare bird sightings, or hang out with a giant 70-year-old tortoise for the day. We&rsquo;ve taken care of everything from hotel stays before and after your cruise, to flights, transfers, packages, meals, beverages, and shore excursions.</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/hero/advertorial-01.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Celebrity's Galapagos Adventures: Untouched, Unspoiled, Unbelievable]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Celebrity Cruises]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-01.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Celebrity's Galapagos Adventures: Untouched, Unspoiled, Unbelievable]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Celebrity Cruises]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
	
	<article date="2103" id="02">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[March 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- Mmm = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[03]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[02]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Cunard]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[cun]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Discover the world in unforgettable Cunard<sup>&reg;</sup> style.]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[A Cunard voyage is more than exploring incredible ports of call. It’s a journey filled with enriching opportunities. Join us to unwind at sea and experience the world.]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Cunard<sup>&reg;</sup> &mdash; A world of opportunities.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 60px 0;">
				<h4>Mareel Spa</h4>
				<p>A Cunard voyage is a perfect place to find relaxation.</p>
				<iframe width="100%" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/XNI5a6sia-I?rel=0" style="width: 100%; min-height: 500px;" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
			</figure>

			<h4>Escape the everyday with Cunard<sup>&reg;</sup>.</h4>
			<p>With wide-open spaces and enriching experiences, we invite you to enjoy a change of pace. The moment you step aboard a Cunard Queen, the hurry of the everyday slips away. Guests are invited to do as much or as little as they please, whether that means lounging with a book in hand on our spacious decks or attending a riveting lecture. There&rsquo;s no schedule on a Cunard voyage and you are free to choose what enriches your journey.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 40px 0;">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-02-01.jpg">
			</figure>

			<h4>Embrace a fresh perspective.</h4>
			<p>Each day brings new views and different experiences. On every voyage, the ocean horizon and calming sound of the waves escort guests from one port to the next, and exciting destinations invigorate the senses and awaken curiosity. No matter where you choose to sail, intriguing ports of call and fresh sea air accompany your voyage every step of the way.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 40px 0;">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-02-02.jpg">
			</figure>

			<h4>Feel free to take time away.</h4>
			<p>Cunard&rsquo;s breadth of luxurious amenities and attentive service invites you to relax and enjoy the ride. Soothing experiences at our onboard spa inspire blissful relaxation with pampering treatments and therapy pools complemented by vast ocean views. Our uncrowded areas, from the onboard library to the outdoor jogging track, are just some of the thoughtfully designed open spaces to put your mind at ease.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 40px 0;">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-02-03.jpg">
			</figure>

			<h4>Enjoy being pampered.</h4>
			<p>Our signature White Star Service<sup>&trade;</sup> is just one more way Cunard is able to personalize your journey to your preferences. No detail is too small, no request is too big for our attentive white-gloved crew, who ensures that you have everything you need for the unforgettable voyage you always imagined!</p>

			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 40px 0;">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-02-04.jpg">
			</figure>

			<h4>Discover enriching journeys crafted for discerning travelers.</h4>
			<p>Sailing with Cunard means you have access to exclusive Signature experiences. Our traditional Afternoon Tea delights with finger sandwiches, scones and pastries and the Cunard Insights&trade; program enhances your journey with thought-provoking discussions by explorers, celebrities, and more. Our Special Events voyages bring themes to life, including music, theater and fashion, on tailor-made sailings that offer an insightful and exciting look into a variety of topics.</p>
			<p>We look forward to welcoming you on board a Cunard Queen for a blissful journey of a lifetime.</p>
			
			<br/>
			
			<p>&copy; 2021 Cunard. Ships&rsquo; Registry: Bermuda.</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/hero/advertorial-02.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Discover the world in unforgettable Cunard<sup>&reg;</sup> style.]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Cunard]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-02.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Discover the world in unforgettable Cunard<sup>&reg;</sup> style.]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Cunard]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>

	<article date="2103" id="03">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[March 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- March = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[03]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[03]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Hurtigruten]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[hur]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[With Hurtigruten, Wellness is Well-Rounded]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[At Hurtigruten, we believe that wellness includes our planet, our communities, our bodies, and our minds.]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Over the past decade we have sought to become an environmentally responsible company, dedicated to sustainability and to protecting the precious habitats across our Earth. Now we are turning our attention to our individual wellness.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>Hurtigruten&rsquo;s Wellness Program was launched in 2019 to integrate activities that encourage physical, mental, and spiritual wellbeing on board our ships, adding to our existing excursions and expeditions that focus on connecting with nature. You will now find yoga, meditation, fitness, tai chi, art, music, massage, nutrition, and other wellness activities on selected voyages. At Hurtigruten, we believe that wellness includes our planet, our communities, our bodies, and our minds. We look forward to helping you to achieve a healthier and more natural lifestyle during our voyages.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 60px 0;">
			<h4>Hurtigruten’s Sustainable, Hybrid Electric-Powered Expedition Ships</h4>
			<p>Learn about how you’ll enjoy a well-rounded wellness experience aboard Hurtigruten’s newest hybrid electric-powered expedition ships.</p>
			<iframe width="100%" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/FGjep_mPR8I?rel=0" style="width: 100%; min-height: 500px;" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
			</figure>
			
			<h3>WELLNESS FOR OUR PLANET</h3>
			<p>As the world leader in expedition cruises, Hurtigruten has come a long way since first getting its start on the Norwegian coast 128 years ago.</p>
			<p>With the launch of the world&rsquo;s first custom-built hybrid electric-powered expedition ships, MS Roald Amundsen and MS Fridtjof Nansen, Hurtigruten leads the way in innovative technology for green and clean exploration to some of the most remote and spectacular coastlines on Earth.</p>
			<p>Each vessel is equipped with large battery packs, feature innovative green technology, and use electric propulsion to reduce fuel emissions by 20% &mdash;allowing guests to sail more quietly than ever before. These expedition ships are truly the first of their kind and take environmentally conscious expedition cruising to a new level.</p>
			<p>Hurtigruten has a great responsibility, which is incorporated into our mission to provide safe, unique, active, and sustainable travel experiences that create lifelong memories. To ensure the guests of tomorrow have the same travel experiences as the guests of today, we work hard to minimize the impact of our operations and promote sustainable innovation in the destinations we visit, by: supporting local communities; ensuring responsible consumption and production with the global partners we collaborate with; urgently combating climate change; and conserving the use of the oceans, seas, and marine resources for sustainable development.</p>
			<p>In fact, Hurtigruten was the first major travel company to remove single-use plastic from all of our ships, restaurants, and hotels. These areas are where we believe we can have the most positive impact as a cruise-ship industry leader and on society as a whole, both now and in the future.</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-03-01.jpg">
			</figure>

			<br/>
			<br/>

			<h3>WELLNESS FOR THE LOCAL COMMUNITIES WE VISIT</h3>
			<p>A Hurtigruten cruise is a journey for all your senses. Our chefs create superb dining from sustainable local and regionally-sourced produce, adding a delicious dimension to your travel.</p>
			<p>To tantalize your taste buds, our team of talented onboard chefs create sumptuous multi-course meals. Whether you choose to dine in the main onboard restaurant or upscale to the &agrave; la carte fine dining option, you&rsquo;ll find the cuisine varied, inspired, and downright delicious.</p>
			<p><strong>Cultural Cuisine <br /></strong>Exploration is about opening our minds to new customs, our eyes to new landscapes, and, yes, our mouths to new tastes. Our chefs may utilize unique herbs and spices or adopt traditional cooking techniques from the area, all to add authentic, local gastronomy to the meals they prepare for you on board. You can also expect some favorite Norwegian recipes on the menu, handed down through generations and a fitting homage to our long sea-faring heritage.</p>
			<p><strong>Local Flavors<br /></strong>Our chefs craft dishes that reflect the cuisine of the region we are sailing in, immersing you in the culture even more.</p>
			<p><strong>Plant-based<br /></strong>A range of tasty plant-based dishes are integrated as essential options into all of our menus.</p>
			<p><strong>Regional Suppliers<br /></strong>Sourcing food along the way helps to cut down the energy needed to transport ingredients and has the added benefit of supporting local small-scale suppliers.</p>
			<p><strong>Inspirational Lectures<br /></strong>The Expedition Team deliver themed lectures on how food and sustainability go hand in hand and often organize tasting sessions out on deck and during landings.</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-03-02.jpg">
			</figure>
			
			<br/>
			<br/>
			
			<h3>WELLNESS FOR OUR BODIES AND MINDS</h3>
			<p>A Hurtigruten expedition cruise features superb onboard facilities designed to help you stay active and rejuvenate for the next</p>
			<p>day&rsquo;s adventures in our Wellness Center. Aboard our new hybrid electric-powered ships, you can work out in our indoor gym and indulge in luxurious spa treatments as you explore.</p>
			
			<br/>
			
			<h4>Stay in Shape &ndash; Inside and Out</h4>
			<p><strong>Training with scenery<br /></strong>Tone up in our indoor gym, featuring rowing machines, fitness bikes, training stations, and free weights. Or enjoy our outdoor gym and the outdoor running track where you can work out in fresh air while watching beautiful scenery glide by. In warm waters, many of the voyages will offer daily yoga, tai chi, and meditation classes with a professional instructor on the outdoor decks, providing an opportunity for an inner journey as well.</p>
			
			<br/>
			
			<h4>A Wealth of Recreational Possibilities</h4>
			<p>Our expedition cruises are dedicated to satisfying all your senses. In the Wellness Center, you will find highly trained massage therapists ready to welcome you to a wide variety of relaxing services and treatments, designed to help you recover, relax and rejuvenate.</p>
			<p><strong>Rejuvenate and Refresh<br /></strong>After an exciting day of exploration or during a peaceful day at sea, there&rsquo;s nothing like indulging in a relaxing massage or treatment. Let our well-trained therapists welcome you to a luxurious and healthful experience, such as an aromatherapy body massage, a tension release treatment for your arms and feet, or the specially created Hurtigruten Signature treatment.</p>
			<p><strong>Sauna<br /></strong>The elegant onboard sauna features panoramic windows.</p>
			<p><strong>Indulge yourself in spectacular waters</strong><br>
			Swim, soak, and truly relax among some of the most sublime scenery on Earth. Soak in the infinity pool or in one of two hot tubs, offering amazing views of glaciers, icebergs and wildlife.</p>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-03-03.jpg">
			</figure>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/hero/advertorial-03.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[With Hurtigruten, Wellness is Well-Rounded]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Hurtigruten]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-03.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[With Hurtigruten, Wellness is Well-Rounded]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Hurtigruten]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
	
	<article date="2103" id="04">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[March 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- Mmm = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[03]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[04]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Oceania Cruises]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[ocn]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Dream. Plan. Discover. <br>Oceania Cruises' New Tropics & Exotics Collection!]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[The captivating voyages of Oceania Cruises&rsquo; new Tropics & Exotics Collection immerse you in the best of the iconic attractions, but also leave room for the discovery of the unexpected.]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Oceania Cruises&rsquo; 2022-2023 Tropics & Exotics Collection is an imaginatively curated array of voyages that explores the most coveted corners of the world. More than ever before, these voyages charting the Caribbean, South America, Asia, Africa, the South Pacific, Australia and beyond are the perfect inspiration for future travels.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<br/>
			<h4>2022-2023 Tropics &amp; Exotics Collection Highlights</h4>
			<ul>
			<li>127 itineraries with 284 total overnights that afford additional opportunities to immerse yourself in the cuisine, culture and history of these destinations</li>
			<li>With 40 Caribbean voyages, discover sun-filled escapes to the most coveted regions and an array of less-traveled islands such as Bonaire, Dominica and Guadeloupe</li>
			<li>In South America, contrast high-energy capitals such as Buenos Aires, Rio de Janeiro and Santiago de Chile with the wild beauty of Patagonia, the Amazon or Antarctica</li>
			<li>Explore iconic destinations and intriguing, off-the-beaten-path locales across Asia and Africa</li>
			<li>Fulfill lifelong travel dreams with unforgettable voyages to Tahiti, Australia and New Zealand</li>
			<li>Enjoy a diversity of enriching destination experiences with our Go Local Tours, culinary-focused excursions and tours that immerse you in sustainability and green practices around the world</li>
			</ul>
			<br/>
			<p>To view the eBrochure, click <a href="https://www.oceaniacruises.com/emags/2022_2023_collection_tropics_and_exotics_ta/page_1.html" target="_blank">here</a>.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 60px 0;">
				<h4>Imagine Your Next Voyage of Discovery with Oceania Cruises</h4>
				<p>Oceania Cruises&rsquo; new Tropics & Exotics Collection brings you the seas less traveled and offers a fascinating array of cultures and colorful landscapes designed to enchant even the most seasoned travelers.</p>
				<iframe width="100%" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/MW_DapUv6jQ?rel=0" style="width: 100%; min-height: 500px;" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
			</figure>

			<h4>Free Airport Transfers with OLife Choice</h4>
			<p>Take advantage of even more value with our <em>OLife Choice</em> Airfare promotion, which includes FREE Roundtrip Airport Transfers on each 2022-2023 Tropics &amp; Exotics Collection voyage. Remember that you can reserve your dream voyage with complete peace of mind since every cruise is covered by our Best Price Guarantee.</p>
			<p>&nbsp;</p>
			<h4>2 for 1 Cruise Fares &amp; Free Internet</h4>
			<p><strong><em>OLife Choice</em></strong> | Includes: Roundtrip Airfare* &amp; Airport Transfers</p>
			<p><em>Plus choose one</em>:</p>
			<ul>
			<li>Free Shore Excursions</li><li>Free Beverage Package</li><li>Free Shipboard Credit</li>
			</ul>
			
			<br>
			<p>Contact your Travel Advisor today for Terms and Conditions and more information!</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/hero/advertorial-04.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Dream. Plan. Discover. Oceania Cruises' New Tropics & Exotics Collection!]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Oceania Cruises]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-04.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Dream. Plan. Discover. Oceania Cruises' New Tropics & Exotics Collection!]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Oceania Cruises]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
	
	<article date="2103" id="05">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[March 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- Mmm = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[03]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[05]]></id_article>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Seabourn]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[sea]]></id_supplier>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Mindful Living Program On Board Seabourn, The World's Finest Ultra-Luxury Cruise Line]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[We have created a fleet-wide Mindful Living Program offering guests a holistic spa and wellness experience that integrates physical, social, environmental and spiritual well-being.]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			The new Spa and Wellness with Dr. Andrew Weil program that integrates physical, social, environmental and spiritual well-being is the first-ever of its kind at sea.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<figure class="article-tile" style="margin: 60px 0;">
				<h4>Seabourn Partnerships - Dr. Andrew Weil</h4>
				<p>This video highlights Seabourn's partnership with Dr. Andrew Weil. It features the Spa & Wellness program onboard, mindful living as a concept and why he chose to work with Seabourn.</p>
				<iframe width="100%" height="500" src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/YsPXLd_Oh-Q?rel=0" style="width: 100%; min-height: 500px;" frameborder="0" allow="accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture" allowfullscreen></iframe>
			</figure>
			
			<p>The program is led by the newly established position, The Mindful Living Coach. The Coach, will be a certified yoga and meditation practitioner who will inspire and educate all guests through various complimentary classes and gatherings throughout the voyage. Guests who choose to participate in this new program will have a cruise experience that is further enhanced by a holistic mind and body perspective.</p>
			<p>Central to the program is the daily practice of meditation and yoga through a selection of complimentary sessions. Guests can experience Mindful Meditation, which will introduce positive affirmations and mantras they can reflect on throughout the day. There will also be daily restorative yoga classes which will continue to focus upon the mantra and positive affirmations. Yoga classes will be varied, offering guests the ability to choose classes that focus on various physical issues, such as yoga to heal back and joint pain, headaches and body alignment, as well as yoga to enhance creativity, mental focus and happiness. Classes will focus on mind, body and spirit over a period of seven days, and will change daily with a new theme.</p>
			<br/>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-05-01.jpg">
			</figure>
			
			<br/>
			
			<p>Integral to the wellness program are enriching complimentary Mind and Body seminars designed to educate guests on philosophies and practices that are aligned with the program's mission. Each presentation will aim to empower guests with ideas and practices that enhance well-being and increase the awareness of connection between mind, body, environment and wellness. Seminars are created by Dr. Weil and Steiner's Wellness professionals, many of which will be based upon Dr. Weil's teachings, and will explore the fields of the healing arts.</p>
			<p>Onboard seminars include:</p>
			<ul>
			<li><strong>Spontaneous Happiness &amp; Spontaneous Healing:</strong> adapted from Dr. Andrew Weil's best-selling books.</li>
			<li>Anti-inflammatory foods: adapted from Dr. Andrew Weil's nutritional guidance.</li>
			<li>Healthy Aging: adapted from Dr. Andrew Weil's research in this area.</li>
			<li>Introduction to Mindful Meditation: learn what happens to the body and mind during meditation.</li>
			<li>Individualized one-on-one wellness sessions on select topics will also be available for a fee.</li>
			</ul>
			
			<br/>
			
			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-05-02.jpg">
			</figure>
			
			<br/>
			
			<p>The Mind and Body Wellness Program with Dr. Andrew Weil deepens the already wellness-focused Seabourn spa program that offers a wide range of body massages, facials, fitness and beauty treatments. Lending itself to the program is the powerfully aromatic Thai Poultice massages that use the traditionally prepared steamed herbs of Camphor, Kaffir Lime, Prai, Turmeric and Lemon Grass in muslin poultices to melt away stress and tension, or nourishing desecrated Coconut that nurtures the body with soothing fats and lipids. Guests will also find Deeper than Deep Hot Stone Massage, Bamboo Massage and Freestyle Massage to engage their minds and bodies. </p>
			
			<hr style="margin: 60px 0;">
			
			<p><em>Our highest priorities are compliance, environmental protection, and protecting the health, safety and well-being of our guests, crew and the people in the destinations we visit. Visit</em>&nbsp;<u><a href="http://seabourn.com/TravelSafe" target="_blank">Seabourn.com/TravelSafe</a></u>&nbsp;<em>to learn more.</em></p>
		]]></body>
		
		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/hero/advertorial-05.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Mindful Living Program On Board Seabourn, The World&rsquo;s Finest Ultra-Luxury Cruise Line]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Seabourn]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/advertorial-05.jpg
		</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Mindful Living Program On Board Seabourn, The World&rsquo;s Finest Ultra-Luxury Cruise Line]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Seabourn]]></article_credit>
		
		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>
