<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
	<article date="2103">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[spotlight]]></dir_name> <!-- spotlight, style, insider -->
		<pub_date><![CDATA[March 2021]]></pub_date> <!-- Mmm = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[21]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[03]]></dir_month>
		
		<author><![CDATA[Hawaiian Islands]]></author>
		<translator><![CDATA[]]></translator>
		
		<title><![CDATA[Hawaii Invites Travelers to Malama Hawaii]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[
			Take a trip that gives back – to Hawaii and to yourself.
		]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Hawaii Visitors and Convention Bureau, in partnership with the Hawaii Tourism Authority, announced the launch of Malama Hawaii – a heartfelt invitation to malama, or to take care of, our earth, each other and ourselves. As visitors look forward to traveling when the time is right, Hawaii asks them to take a trip that gives back – to Hawaii and to themselves.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>In an effort to inspire mindful travel, industry partners and volunteer organizations across the state have come together with an initiative that encourages visitors to give back to the destination. Volunteer projects range from reforestation and tree planting to self-directed beach cleanups, ocean reef preservation, and even creating Hawaiian quilts for the kupuna (elders). By making a positive impact, visitors will have a more enriching travel experience and can even enjoy a free extra night from participating hotels.</p>
			<p>&ldquo;Malama Hawaii is more than a promotion or campaign, it&rsquo;s the direction in which our brand is headed,&rdquo; said Hawaii Visitors and Convention Bureau President and CEO, John Monahan. &ldquo;Our goal is to attract mindful visitors who will leave Hawaii better than when they arrived. By doing so, visitors will experience a deeper connection and a vacation that really becomes more meaningful to them.&rdquo;</p>
			<h4>How the Malama Hawaii Program Works&nbsp;</h4>
			<p>Hotel partners across the state are offering special packages that include a volunteer opportunity either run on property or in partnership with a local non-profit. The attractive offers, most available through 2021, include a free extra night when participating in the designated volunteer activity. Each hotel is managing its own promotion and volunteer project, which follows strict state and county guidelines including wearing a mask, physical distancing, and limited group size.&nbsp;</p>
			<p>Beyond Hawaii hotels and resorts, other industry partners and volunteer organizations are joining the effort and creating meaningful travel experiences and initiatives. Following is an initial list of participating partners that will be updated on&nbsp;<a href="https://www.gohawaii.com/malama">gohawaii.com/malama</a>:</p>
			<ul>
				<li>Alaska Airlines</li>
				<li>&lsquo;Alohilani Resort Beach Waikīkī Beach</li>
				<li>Andaz Maui at Wailea Resort</li>
				<li>Fairmont Orchid, Hawaii</li>
				<li>Four Seasons Resort Maui at Wailea</li>
				<li>Grand Hyatt Kauai Resort &amp; Spa</li>
				<li>Hana-Maui Resort</li>
				<li>Hawaiian Legacy Reforestation Initiative</li>
				<li>Hilton Garden Inn Kauai Wailua Bay</li>
				<li>Hyatt Regency Maui Resort &amp; Spa</li>
				<li>Hyatt Regency Waikiki Resort &amp; Spa</li>
				<li>Marriott Hawaii: Properties statewide</li>
				<li>Outrigger Waikiki Beach Resort</li>
				<li>Pacific Whale Foundation</li>
				<li>Prince Waikiki</li>
				<li>Waikiki Beachcomber by Outrigger</li>
			</ul>
			
			<br/>
			<br/>
			
			<p>While the visitor experience might look and feel different, travelers can count on the transformative and positive impact of traveling to Hawaii to change their own lives, and the destinations they visit across the state, for the better.&nbsp;</p>
			<p>Hawaiian Legacy Reforestation Initiative Executive Director, Jeff Dunster added, &ldquo;Together we will provide guests with a unique opportunity to give back through the restoration of Hawaii's rarest native forests. These ecosystems exist nowhere else on earth, and now, with visitors&rsquo; help, we can all leave a lasting legacy for this generation and for generations to come.&rdquo;</p>
			<p>For more information about how you can&nbsp;<em>malama</em>&nbsp;Hawaii, visit&nbsp;<a href="https://www.gohawaii.com/malama">gohawaii.com/malama</a>.</p>
			<br/>
			<p style='font-size: 80%;'>Image Credit: The Hawaiian Islands</p>
		]]></body>
		
		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/hero/spotlight.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Hawaii Invites Travelers to Malama Hawaii]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Destination Spotlight]]></hero_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/article/spotlight.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Hawaii Invites Travelers to Malama Hawaii]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Destination Spotlight]]></article_credit> <!--Spotlight, Insider, Travel Style -->
		<email_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/21/03/email/spotlight.jpg</email_src>
		
		<tile_color>C8232C</tile_color> <!--Spotlight:C8232C, Insider:FA6900, Travel Style:00B9F2 -->
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>
		
		<tags>
			<tag slug="voluntourism"><![CDATA[voluntourism]]></tag>
			<tag slug="sports-outdoors"><![CDATA[sports-outdoors]]></tag>
			<tag slug="family-vacations"><![CDATA[family-vacations]]></tag>
			<tag slug="education-learning"><![CDATA[education-learning]]></tag>
			<tag slug="culture-history"><![CDATA[culture-history]]></tag>
			<tag slug="beach-sun"><![CDATA[beach-sun]]></tag>
			<tag slug="adventure"><![CDATA[adventure]]></tag>
			<tag slug="independent-travel"><![CDATA[independent-travel]]></tag>
			<tag slug="north-america"><![CDATA[north-america]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>
</root>
