<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>

<!-- BEGIN: 2003 ama -->

	<article date="2003" id="01">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[March 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- March = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[03]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[01]]></id_article>

		<author><![CDATA[AmaWaterways]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[amw]]></id_supplier>

		<title><![CDATA[Fill Your Heart with &ldquo;Ama&rdquo;!]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[AmaWaterways]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Award-winning AmaWaterways treats you to an unforgettable journey highlighted by exquisite regionally inspired cuisine, authentic included experiences and unparalleled service.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>Travelers often speak of leaving a piece of themselves behind in cities that have made their hearts skip a beat. But on an award-winning AmaWaterways river cruise, you won&rsquo;t ever return home with love lost. Instead, AmaWaterways makes it their personal mission to ensure your heart will grow while cruising legendary rivers through Europe, Southeast Asia and Africa.</p>

			<p>&ldquo;Ama&rdquo; means love &ndash; and AmaWaterways puts love in everything they do. It all starts with the warm hearts of their extraordinary crew, who welcome you aboard by whisking your luggage away so your vacation can officially begin. Before you know it, your friendly Cruise Manager has begun greeting you by name, your chef has your favorite omelet in the skillet and your waiter has brought your morning cup of coffee just the way you like it &ndash; because it fills their hearts to surprise and delight you.</p>

			<p>When you&rsquo;re ready to explore the world ashore, the most knowledgeable local guides take you to the heart of each destination and introduce you to the local culture on a variety of included excursions. Whether you prefer a gentle walking tour through a medieval town center, an active guided hike to a hilltop castle or an immersive Special Interest Tour such as a cooking demonstration or tasting, you&rsquo;ll experience the best each city or village has to offer in the way that suits you best.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-01-01.jpg">
			</figure>

			<p><strong>Keeping Your Heart Healthy &ndash; And Your Mind and Spirit Too</strong><br>
			AmaWaterways also ensures that every guest can enhance their best self while on board. With a professional Wellness Host aboard their ships in Europe and on the Mekong River, you&rsquo;ll find a variety of engaging wellness activities available. Join a group stretching class in the morning on the Sun Deck, or perhaps a dance class in the afternoon. Cardio and core strengthening options are also available, as are active wellness walks. While offerings vary based on your individual Wellness Host&rsquo;s expertise, you will always be welcomed, no matter what your age or activity level, into a fun and friendly environment. And if you prefer a gentler approach to wellness, heated sundeck pools and massage rooms will help bring you back to a peaceful state of mind.</p>

			<p><strong>Your Floating Hotel Awaits</strong><br>
			After the excursions earn your affection, your heart will swell as you&rsquo;re warmly welcomed &ldquo;back home&rdquo; &ndash; because you&rsquo;ve genuinely become a part of the AmaWaterways family. The Hotel Manager may hand you a refreshing chilled towel after your countryside bike ride or a hot herbal tea following your winter&rsquo;s trip to a local Christmas Market, because your ultimate comfort is one of the line&rsquo;s top priorities.</p>

			<p>One of the most special parts of river cruising is indulging in delicious food from the region you&rsquo;re sailing through. You&rsquo;ll be treated on board &ndash; at every meal &ndash; to exquisite locally-sourced cuisine and artfully plated dishes created by passionate chefs. Lunches and dinners are paired with complimentary hand-selected wines, or beer or soft drinks if you prefer. And during one extraordinary evening on board, you&rsquo;ll be treated to an exceptional multi-course tasting menu at The Chef&rsquo;s Table specialty restaurant, the only venue of its kind on the rivers.</p>

			<p><strong>New for 2020</strong><br>
			AmaWaterways offers exciting new Europe itineraries in 2020, each combining two rivers into one spectacular journey and both available aboard the line&rsquo;s new AmaSiena. Discover the storybook atmosphere of Germany&rsquo;s top-rated destinations on an unforgettable Treasures of the Main &amp; Rhine river cruise. W&uuml;rzburg, with its UNESCO-designated Residenz Palace, Bamberg with its famous smoked beer and Cologne&rsquo;s awe-inspiring cathedral are among the treasures you&rsquo;ll experience on the Main and Rhine rivers.</p>

			<p>Alternatively, storybook castles and breathtaking landscapes await on a Vineyards of the Rhine &amp; Moselle river cruise. From charming R&uuml;desheim in Germany&rsquo;s Rheingau wine region to quaint Bernkastel in the Riesling-rich Moselle Valley, guests are treated to a variety of enriching excursions. Combined with exquisite locally sourced cuisine, fine wines and unparalleled service, this cruise along two celebrated rivers is unforgettable.</p>

			<p>In addition, there are two new optional land programs this year: a 3-night exploration of the beautiful French Riviera in Nice, France, offered as part of our Colors of Provence itinerary and a 3-night experience in Istanbul, Turkey, offered as part of a Gems of Southeast Europe cruise and land adventure.</p>

			<p>Cruise with AmaWaterways in 2020 and fill your heart with &ldquo;ama.&rdquo; Contact your preferred travel advisor to receive exclusive savings and offers on select departures!</p>
		]]></body>

		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/hero/advertorial-01.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Fill Your Heart with &ldquo;Ama&rdquo;!]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[AmaWaterways]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-01.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Fill Your Heart with &ldquo;Ama&rdquo;!]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[AmaWaterways]]></article_credit>

		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>

		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>

	</article>

<!-- END: 2003 ama -->

<!-- BEGIN: 2003 tfg -->

	<article date="2003" id="02">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[March 2020]]></pub_date>
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[03]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[02]]></id_article>

		<author><![CDATA[Trafalgar]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[tfg]]></id_supplier>

		<title><![CDATA[France: A Timeless Destination That Will Never Go Out Of Style]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Trafalgar]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			From the very first day, it&rsquo;s easy to see why France attracts more visitors than any other country on Earth.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>Coco Chanel once said, &lsquo;a girl should be two things: classy and fabulous&rsquo;. Coco may have been talking about fashion, but she could equally have been referring to her home country, France. Timeless, elegant and beautiful, France is a destination synonymous with good food, sophisticated locals, gorgeous stretches of coastline, and one of the most romantic cities in the world. It is a European bucket list must, which is probably why over 90 million tourists make the trip each and every year. If France is high up on your travel agenda, Trafalgar&rsquo;s France travel guide will help you decide where&rsquo;s best to go&hellip;</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-02-01.jpg">
				<h4>Paris</h4>
				Whoever first uttered the words &lsquo;a bad day in Paris is still better than a good day anywhere else&rsquo;, wasn&rsquo;t far wrong. The city of lights (and love) is as iconic as they come, and just wandering the streets here you instantly walk a little straighter, allowing the timeless elegance and style of the city to work its magic on you. Paris is home to some of the world&rsquo;s most famous attractions including the Louvre, the Eiffel Tower, the Arc de Triumph and the Notre Dame Cathedral, whilst walks along the Seine or a visit to the resplendent Palace of Versailles, are both Parisian musts.
				<br><br>
				Icons ticked, you should then spend some time getting to know the culture of the city. A visit to Montmartre and its world-famous Artist&rsquo;s Square will have you walking in the footsteps of Lautrec and Picasso, whilst a night spent at the Moulin Rouge will get even the greatest of introverts up dancing, singing and high kicking with the best of them.
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-02-02.jpg">
				<h4><strong>Lyon</strong></h4>
				Sitting on the junction of the Rh&ocirc;ne and Sa&ocirc;ne rivers, the UNESCO World Heritage city of Lyon boasts a history dating back over 2000 years. Medieval and renaissance architecture give the city an impressively historic feel, the centrepiece of which is the magnificent Roman Amphitheatre. Yet whilst Lyon&rsquo;s grand buildings and pretty pastel facades will impress you, what you&rsquo;ll remember from your time here is the food. Claiming the title &lsquo;gourmet capital of France&rsquo; is no mean feat in a country obsessed with food, but Lyon&rsquo;s vast array of imaginative restaurants and regional specialties have helped the city seal the deal.
				<br><br>
				Want to taste the very best Lyon has to offer? Opt for Trafalgar&rsquo;s &lsquo;Beaujolais Gourmet Dinner and Old Town Discovery&rsquo; experience, which includes a scenic evening drive along the Sa&ocirc;ne River, and a mouthwatering three course dinner (with local wines) cooked by a top Lyonnais chef.
			</figure>


			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-02-03.jpg">
				<h4>French Riviera</h4>
				No France travel guide would be complete without mention of the eternally beautiful French Riviera. Hugging the Mediterranean, this South Easterly corner of France offers some of the best weather of the entire country, not to mention fresh seafood and a more sedate pace of life. The likes of Monaco and Nice are some of the blockbuster attractions here but dig a little deeper (or travel with a company who pride themselves on taking you off the beaten track) and you&rsquo;ll also discover how culturally rich this corner of the country is. The tiny and picturesque hilltop town of St Paul de Vence is especially worthy of a visit, known for being the laid-back escape bolt hole for creatives and actors past and present.
			</figure>


			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-02-04.jpg">
				<h4>Loire Valley</h4>
				A destination instantly recognisable to wine connoisseurs, the Loire Valley is where to go for a delicious tipple, especially if you&rsquo;re partial to a dry white. One of France&rsquo;s leading wine producing regions, this lush and beautiful area is distinguished by vineyards, rolling farmland and vast chateaus. If you&rsquo;re travelling with Trafalgar, you&rsquo;ll be treated to an extra special Be my Guest experience at the regal Ch&acirc;teau de Villandry. Take your time roaming the exquisite Renaissance gardens that surround the estate and try not to get lost in the maze!
			</figure>


			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-02-05.jpg">
				<h4>Normandy</h4>
				Synonymous with the D-Day landings, Normandy is a destination of huge importance not just for those with an interest in history, but for every one of us who had a family member touched by the destruction of the World Wars. It was here in 1944 that the largest seaborne invasion in history happened, and where many tragically sacrificed their lives for the freedom we get to enjoy today.
				<br><br>
				Omaha Beach is of particular importance, and it&rsquo;s here you can still see the remains of German bunkers dotted along the beach. The D-Day landing zone is also fascinating, giving visitors the opportunity to learn all about how the operation was planned and executed.
			</figure>

		]]></body>

		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/hero/advertorial-02.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[France: A Timeless Destination That Will Never Go Out Of Style]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Trafalgar]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-02.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[France: A Timeless Destination That Will Never Go Out Of Style]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Trafalgar]]></article_credit>

		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>

		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>

	</article>

<!-- END: 2003 tfg -->

<!-- BEGIN: 2003 hwi -->

	<article date="2003" id="03">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[March 2020]]></pub_date> <!-- March = Full month name (ie. January) -->
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[03]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[03]]></id_article>

		<author><![CDATA[The Hawaiian Islands]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[hwi]]></id_supplier>

		<title><![CDATA[Discover Hawaii]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[The Hawaiian Islands]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Six Hawaiian Islands. Six unique experiences.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>From crystal blue waters to&nbsp;stunning green cliffs and black sand beaches, Hawaii&rsquo;s wealth of natural beauty is the breathtaking&nbsp;backdrop for unforgettable experiences that reward those who delve a little deeper - into vibrant cultures full of welcoming aloha, a thriving food scene and thrilling outdoor adventures. There&rsquo;s so much more to Hawaii than what you&rsquo;ve heard about.</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-03-01.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Kauai</h4>
					&ldquo;Rejuvenating&rdquo; is a word often used to describe Kauai and its immersive natural beauty. The raw energy of the soaring cliffs along the emerald Napali Coast. The expansive vistas of the Waimea Canyon. And the soothing ripples of the Wailua River winding through forest. The northernmost and greenest of the Hawaiian Islands is a place to put down your phone and forget about your worries. Breathe deep. Unwind. And rediscover a special connection to nature on this beautiful, tropical island.
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-03-02.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Oahu</h4>
					This is where culture meets creativity. In the lively center of the Hawaiian Islands, luxury and leisure, excitement and adventure can all be found in just the right proportion to suit you. Oahu is famous for iconic Waikiki Beach, Pearl Harbor and the surfing mecca on the North Shore, but there&rsquo;s much more to this storied destination. From festivals that celebrate Hawaiian culture to major events at the pinnacle of sports and entertainment, there&rsquo;s always something to do. Even disappear, into the lush tropical beauty that abounds from mountain to ocean. Discover the next food trend before it goes global, from the up-and-coming chefs and mixologists staking Oahu&rsquo;s claim as a culinary capital. And schedule some free time on your itinerary, when you can go with the flow and soak in the buzz and energy of Oahu.
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-03-03.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Maui</h4>
					Maui is where larger-than-life experiences meet small town charm. This is the best of both worlds, offering a unique blend of sophistication and simplicity.&nbsp;Taste the fresh bounty produced year-round by the farms and lush gardens surrounding the quaint communities of Upcountry Maui. Wind down your day at the exclusive Haleakala National Park to witness an epic sunset&nbsp;from the top of the world. Or simply lounge poolside at a luxurious resort, from Kapalua to Wailea. From friendly folks to picturesque landscapes, there&rsquo;s no end to the unique welcome you&rsquo;ll find on Maui.
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-03-04.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Island of Hawaii</h4>
					Take a road trip on the youngest and largest of the Hawaiian Islands. Nearly twice as big as all of the other Hawaiian Islands combined, the island of Hawaii&rsquo;s sheer size and diversity are awe-inspiring. You can see some of the most pivotal sites in Native Hawaiian history and visit a volcano, all while traveling through all but four of the world&rsquo;s different climate zones. From the crystal blue waters of Kona and Kohala Coast to the black sands of Punaluu to the lush botanical gardens and waterfalls of the Hamakua Heritage corridor. There is so much more to see and do on this rich, storied island that invites exploration&ndash;and adventure.
				</figcaption>
			</figure>
		]]></body>

		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/hero/advertorial-03.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Kauai]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[The Hawaiian Islands]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-03.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Discover Hawaii]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[The Hawaiian Islands]]></article_credit>

		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>

		<tags>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
			<tag slug="xxx"><![CDATA[xxx]]></tag>
		</tags>
	</article>

<!-- END: 2003 hwi -->

<!-- BEGIN: 2003 lin -->

	<article date="2003" id="04">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[March 2020]]></pub_date>
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[03]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[04]]></id_article>

		<author><![CDATA[Lindblad Expeditions]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[lin]]></id_supplier>

		<title><![CDATA[5 Awesome Alaska Activities for Kids &amp; Teens]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Lindblad Expeditions]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Give your kids a breath of fresh Alaska!
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>Lindblad Expeditions&rsquo; exclusive family program is the only one of its kind in Alaska travel. Developed in conjunction with National Geographic Education, it&rsquo;s designed to help kids and teens develop the attitudes, skills, and knowledge of an explorer. And most of all&mdash;it delivers glacier-sized fun! Here are just some of the amazing activities they can do on your memory-making family expedition:</p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-04-01.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Earn a Zodiac Driver&rsquo;s License</h4>
					What&rsquo;s cooler than zipping around glittering icebergs or zooming past a raft of sea otters in a Zodiac? Taking the reins and steering the craft yourself! With help from a naturalist, kids will learn how to cruise through the water like a master navigator. When the lesson&rsquo;s complete they&rsquo;ll take home their official driver&rsquo;s license&mdash;now that&rsquo;s something they&rsquo;ll want to show and tell!
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-04-02.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Direct a nature documentary</h4>
					Kids can work with a Lindblad-National Geographic certified photo instructor to experiment with time-lapse, slo-mo, and other cool video features on their smartphone as they head out into the field. Will they focus on soaring bald eagles with a six-foot wingspan or capture the thunderous spectacle of a calving glacier? Get a close-up of a giant bear track on the trail or pan across a river teeming with salmon? Using their observation skills and imagination they&rsquo;ll learn to tell a unique story of the wild wonders around them.
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-04-03.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Explore Like a True Scientist</h4>
					Every kid receives an exclusively developed and designed Field Notebook to record their daily observations. They&rsquo;ll keep track of wildlife sightings, from breaching humpback whales to boisterous Stellar sea lions; and jot down stories, notes, and sketches as things inspire them on a hike, a kayak, or while observing from the ship&rsquo;s bow. Different activities earn them &ldquo;points&rdquo; all on their way to becoming a National Geographic Global Explorer.
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-04-04.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Be Part of a Plankton Tow</h4>
					Plankton are a key source of food for whales, fish, and other large marine life who make their home in Alaska. Kids can head out in a Zodiac and help drop a special plankton net into the sea to gather up some specimens. Back on-board ship they&rsquo;ll examine their catch under a microscope and discover what makes these very important, free-floating organisms tick.
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-04-05.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>Make an Ice Cream Glacier Sundae</h4>
					Glaciers form in places like Alaska and Antarctica where more snow falls each winter than melts each summer. These enormous rivers of ice can be tricky to understand but kids will discover how they work in the most delicious way possible&mdash;by making ice cream sundaes!
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<p>Ready to plan the perfect Alaska adventure for the whole family? Contact your Travel Advisor and ask about Lindblad Expeditions and the National Geographic Global Explorers Program.</p>
		]]></body>

		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/hero/advertorial-04.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[5 Awesome Alaska Activities for Kids &amp; Teens]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Lindblad Expeditions]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-04.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[5 Awesome Alaska Activities for Kids &amp; Teens]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Lindblad Expeditions]]></article_credit>

		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>

	</article>

<!-- END: 2003 lin -->

<!-- BEGIN: 2003 tvi -->

	<article date="2003" id="05">
		<dir_name><![CDATA[advertorial]]></dir_name>
		<pub_date><![CDATA[March 2020]]></pub_date>
		<dir_year><![CDATA[20]]></dir_year>
		<dir_month><![CDATA[03]]></dir_month>
		<id_article><![CDATA[05]]></id_article>

		<author><![CDATA[Travel Impressions]]></author>
		<id_supplier><![CDATA[tvi]]></id_supplier>

		<title><![CDATA[Unlimited-Luxury<sup>&reg;</sup> for All-Adult Romance]]></title>
		<teaser><![CDATA[Travel Impressions]]></teaser>
		<lead><![CDATA[
			Secrets Resorts &amp; Spas offer adults an extra measure of romance and sensuality in exquisite luxury beachfront settings. Guests immerse themselves in Unlimited-Luxury<sup>&reg;</sup> where everything is included.
		]]></lead>
		<body><![CDATA[
			<p>Secrets Resorts &amp; Spas offer adults an extra measure of romance and sensuality in exquisite luxury beachfront settings. Guests immerse themselves in Unlimited-Luxury<sup>&reg;</sup> where everything is included. This plus elegantly appointed rooms and suites with 24-hour concierge and room services, multiple gourmet restaurants and lounges serving top-shelf spirits, elegant amenities and endless day and evening activities, provide the ultimate backdrop for unparalleled pampering, romantic rendezvous and lasting memories for couples and honeymooners.</p>

			<p>The magic of Secrets Resorts &amp; Spas emanates from its luxurious all-adult atmosphere combined with its spectacular oceanfront settings &mdash; regarded among the very finest anywhere. Spacious rooms and suites welcome you with timelessly elegant furnishings and comforts.</p>

			<p>To this, add the joys of extraordinary gourmet dining, world-class spas and a long list of recreational choices, fitness options and top flight entertainment. Most importantly, everything is offered with exemplary personal service in a casual, yet sophisticated style.</p>

			<p>Best of all, Secrets Resorts &amp; Spas lavish you with the privileges of Unlimited-Luxury<sup>&reg;</sup>. This means you may dine, snack and enjoy top-shelf spirits as often as you wish, whenever you wish. The commitment of our staff to the excellence of your vacation experience is unmatched.</p>

			<p>There is simply no better place to share your romantic Secrets.</p>

			<p><strong>WELCOME TO THE WORLD OF SECRETS RESORTS &amp; SPAS</strong></p>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-05-01.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>MEXICO</h4>
					<strong>Secrets Akumal Riviera Maya</strong> &ndash; Ideally located in the heart of the Riviera Maya along the famed white-sand beaches and calm, clear waters of Akumal, fuses elegant and original design with nature&rsquo;s elements.
					<br>
					<strong>Secrets Aura Cozumel</strong> &ndash; In a perfect blend of luxury and excitement, Secrets Aura Cozumel is the ultimate romantic, adults-only, all-suite resort located on the island of Cozumel.
					<br>
					<strong>Secrets Capri Riviera Cancun</strong> &ndash; Here on over 70 tropical beach front acres on the Riviera Maya is a vision of classic Mediterranean architecture with stunning ocean views.
					<br>
					<strong>Secrets Huatulco Resort &amp; Spa</strong> &ndash; Idyllically set on the pristine Bah&iacute;a de Conejos, a secluded bay jeweled by exotic rock formations and the sapphire waters of the Pacific.
					<br>
					<strong>Secrets Maroma Beach Riviera Cancun</strong> &ndash; The spectacular 500 acre seascape will be yours at this all-suite resort.
					<br>
					<strong>Secrets Playa Mujeres Golf &amp; Spa Resort</strong> &ndash; Set within an exclusive gated community just 10 minutes from downtown Cancun lies an all-adult, all-suites oceanfront masterpiece.
					<br>
					<strong>Secrets Puerto Los Cabos Golf &amp; Spa Resort</strong> &ndash; The oceanfront location sits on the miles of unspoiled beach that has made the Baja California peninsula world famous for its deep sea sport fishing, golfing and celebrity lifestyle.
					<br>
					<strong>Secrets Silversands Riviera Cancun</strong> &ndash; The all-suite resort brings a gleaming new look and atmosphere to Riviera Maya&rsquo;s most desired beaches.
					<br>
					<strong>Secrets The Vine Cancun</strong> &ndash; Like a marvelous wine created by the perfect balance of nature, hand selected elements and masterful care - a magnificent beach, elegant rooms, suites &amp; amenities that delight the heart.
					<br>
					<strong>Secrets Vallarta Bay Puerto Vallarta</strong> &ndash; The oceanfront resort is an all-adult, all-suites showcase just steps away from the art galleries, shopping and night life of &ldquo;El Malec&oacute;n,&rdquo; the area&rsquo;s famous boardwalk, and just 5 minutes from the scenic colonial city of Puerto Vallarta.
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-05-02.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>DOMINICAN REPUBLIC</h4>
					<strong>Secrets Cap Cana Resort &amp; Spa</strong> &ndash; Perfectly situated in the exclusive gated community of Cap Cana, bringing the highest level of luxury to the crystal blue waters and magnificent sugar-sand Juanillo Beach, in the Dominican Republic.
					<br>
					<strong>Secrets Royal Beach Punta Cana</strong> &ndash; This all-adult, all-suite sanctuary is exactly what you&rsquo;ve been fantasizing about. A spectacular meandering pool winds its way through manicured gardens towards 700 yards of sugar white beach.
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-05-03.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>JAMAICA</h4>
					<strong>Secrets St. James Montego Bay</strong> &ndash; Together with its counterpart, Secrets Wild Orchid, gives you a dual fantasy world in which to play, relax and reconnect. The stunning British Colonial architecture honors Jamaica&rsquo;s history and heritage.
					<br>
					<strong>Secrets Wild Orchid Montego Bay</strong> &ndash; One of two worlds that combine to create Secrets Montego Bay. Its contemporary design reflects the magic of the surrounding islands. You will also enjoy full access to its elegantly traditional &ldquo;other half&rdquo;.
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-05-04.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>ST. MARTIN</h4>
					<strong>Secrets St. Martin Resort &amp; Spa</strong> &ndash; The modern design of the resort takes its inspiration from the island&rsquo;s radiant surroundings, steeped in Caribbean-European and French roots.
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			<figure class="article-tile">
				<img class="img-responsive" src="https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-05-05.jpg">
				<figcaption>
					<h4>COSTA RICA</h4>
					<strong>Secrets Papagayo Costa Rica</strong> &ndash; Set on Papagayo Bay along the Pacific coast of Costa Rica, this resort sits on a black, volcanic sand beach, which when coupled with lush, mountainous surroundings provides a stunning backdrop for an intimate, relaxing and romantic getaway
				</figcaption>
			</figure>

			</p>ALL-ADULTS UNLIMITED-LUXURY<sup>&reg;</sup><br> HAVE IT ALL &mdash; ALL THE TIME.<p>
		]]></body>

		<body_2><![CDATA[]]></body_2>

		<hero_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/hero/advertorial-05.jpg</hero_src>
		<hero_caption><![CDATA[Unlimited-Luxury<sup>&reg;</sup> for All-Adult Romance]]></hero_caption>
		<hero_credit><![CDATA[Travel Impressions]]></hero_credit>
		<article_src>https://www.ensembletravel.com/assets/img/ezine/20/03/article/advertorial-05.jpg</article_src>
		<article_caption><![CDATA[Unlimited-Luxury<sup>&reg;</sup> for All-Adult Romance]]></article_caption>
		<article_credit><![CDATA[Travel Impressions]]></article_credit>

		<tile_color>A8CB17</tile_color>
		<tile_class>opaque-100</tile_class>
		<tile_new>none</tile_new>

	</article>

<!-- END: 2003 tvi -->

</root>